<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<posts>
  <row Id="1" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-05-22T18:39:40.113" Score="9" ViewCount="76" Body="&lt;p&gt;There have been a couple questions today about wanting to find a specific type of library for a specific purpose. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I find that these questions aren't too useful, considering it is going to vary widely based on where the asker is located, and what specific thing they are looking for - it seems like these sorts of questions would be too localized, or not constructive. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thoughts? Opinions?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="22" LastEditorUserId="26" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-05-23T17:00:26.437" LastActivityDate="2012-05-23T17:00:26.437" Title="Are questions about finding specific types of libraries on topic?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;scope&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="1" FavoriteCount="1" />
  <row Id="2" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-05-22T19:24:01.697" Score="10" ViewCount="188" Body="&lt;p&gt;A lot of questions on this site are naturally going to be asking about personal experiences along the lines of &quot;how does your library handle [this specific thing]?&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While I don't think that that is inherently a bad thing (after all, it is one of the reasons this site was created in the first place!), I do think that there need to be some guidelines put in place, otherwise questions might easily devolve into things with 20 different answers that are all valid, but ultimately not entirely helpful.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Stack Exchange blog post about subjective questions, &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.stackoverflow.com/2010/09/good-subjective-bad-subjective/&quot;&gt;Good Subjective, Bad Subjective&lt;/a&gt; talks a lot about this very issue. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It talks about needing long answers, not just one line anecdotes - work to give all the information you can, the more detailed the better. Share what you have done, not just your thoughts - backing up your ideas with practical experiences makes the answers all the richer.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These are just a few of the guidelines the post mentions, and I think it would be definitely something to keep in mind as we move forward in the beta. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I do think that there is a definite home on this site for subjective material, but I do think we also, as a community, need to begin (even today!) to think about what is acceptable and what isn't - naturally, this might change over time as more and more people begin to use the site, but having these discussions to form our site earlier on is a lot easier than having to make decisions later on.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What are your thoughts, fellow Libraries users? How do we feel about subjective questions?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="22" LastActivityDate="2012-05-23T02:11:13.753" Title="How do we want to handle subjective questions?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" AnswerCount="3" FavoriteCount="1" />
  <row Id="3" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="2" CreationDate="2012-05-22T19:40:07.017" Score="6" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;How does your library handle [this specific thing]?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Try to generalize more into&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;How should &lt;em&gt;any&lt;/em&gt; library handle &lt;em&gt;this concept or problem?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Which is kinda-sorta covered in&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/how-to-ask&quot;&gt;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/how-to-ask&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;h3&gt;Make it relevant to others&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;p&gt;We like to help as many people at a time as we can. Make it clear how your question is relevant to more people than just you, and more of us will be interested in your question and willing to look into it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In short, &lt;strong&gt;don't be shy about editing questions to make them more broadly useful to other people!&lt;/strong&gt; And also nudge in comments as necessary.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="42" LastActivityDate="2012-05-22T19:40:07.017" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="4" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="23" CreationDate="2012-05-22T19:43:42.633" Score="0" ViewCount="74" Body="&lt;p&gt;I can think of useful tags that seem pretty normal TO ME:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Circulation&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Cataloguing (or &quot;Cataloging&quot;)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Administration (or &quot;Management&quot;)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Interlibrary Loan&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;etc. And I suspect it's a Good Thing that we'll have a &lt;em&gt;de facto&lt;/em&gt; folksonomy as well. (Ask Sandy Berman about rigidly controlled subject vocabularies sometime, especially if you don't know why you're asking him.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So what suggestions would you like to offer for standard question-subject tags?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="38" LastActivityDate="2012-05-23T20:38:40.983" Title="Should we aim for a semi-controlled vocabulary for tags?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;tagging&gt;&lt;subjects&gt;&lt;folksonomy&gt;&lt;controlled-vocabulary&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="5" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="2" CreationDate="2012-05-22T20:03:13.343" Score="11" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;There's an important difference between &lt;em&gt;subjective&lt;/em&gt; questions and &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;bad&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; subjective questions. As you already linked:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.stackoverflow.com/2010/09/good-subjective-bad-subjective/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Good subjective, Bad Subjective&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip; is a good read.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;em&gt;anecdotal&lt;/em&gt; style question you mentioned &amp;mdash; one that seeks to &lt;strong&gt;poll the community&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;mdash; is where you tend to run into the most problems. What is your favorite [X]? What does your library do about [X]? Even if the the answers are not literally one-liners, those types of questions generally do not make great questions for this type of Q&amp;amp;A. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A good acid test to spot these &quot;polls&quot; or &quot;conversation starters&quot; are questions where just about &lt;em&gt;everyone&lt;/em&gt; is equally qualified to pile in their random thoughts on the subject. The question doesn't have an &lt;em&gt;actual&lt;/em&gt; answer, but is generally just opening a broad topic of discussion for everyone to toss in their thoughts.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;You should only ask practical, answerable questions based on actual problems that you face. Chatty, open-ended questions diminish the usefulness of our site &amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip; from a blog post which fleshes this issue out a bit more specficially &amp;mdash;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.stackoverflow.com/2011/01/real-questions-have-answers/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Real questions have answers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="81" LastEditorUserId="81" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-05-22T20:33:15.953" LastActivityDate="2012-05-22T20:33:15.953" />
  <row Id="6" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="9" CreationDate="2012-05-22T20:58:01.310" Score="1" ViewCount="80" Body="&lt;p&gt;What kind of questions are appropriate to ask for somebody who works at a book store? &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Example subjects:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Book store classification systems&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Bookseller's and customer interaction &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Stocking, i.e. suggestions for seasonal book selling&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Floor planning and store environment&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Promotion and events&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="96" LastActivityDate="2012-05-28T05:39:37.520" Title="Are book store questions on topic?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;scope&gt;" AnswerCount="4" />
  <row Id="7" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1" CreationDate="2012-05-22T21:50:05.210" Score="2" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;While geography is a factor with specific libraries, Interlibrary Loan can be very useful in overcoming that barrier, as well as directly contacting the library itself. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I think it is important to know what libraries are in existence because often times the smaller and very specialized libraries are the ones that get overlooked and forgotten. By creating and answering questions about specific types of libraries and their purpose, we are collecting this information into one place which is the purpose of stack exchange. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So, I think it is important to ask and find specific libraries of specific types.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="97" LastActivityDate="2012-05-22T21:50:05.210" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="8" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="4" CreationDate="2012-05-22T22:14:19.720" Score="3" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I don't argue to use an existing classification instead of user-provide tags, but it should be worth to have a look at existing indexing schemes in library and information science:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://eprints.rclis.org/cms/jita/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;JITA Classification Schema of Library and Information Science&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://books.infotoday.com/asist/TheInfoSciLib3.shtml&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;ASIS&amp;amp;T Thesaurus of Information Science, Technology, and Librarianship&lt;/a&gt; (2005)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Thesaurus of Library and Information Science Terms (ISBN 8170003784)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;LISA Subject Headings&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;...&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The fact that most of these schemes are not publically available tells us something about the role of library and information science in the digital age. :-(&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So the best scheme is probably Wikipedia/DBPedia. A tag is choosen well, if there is a Wikipedia article about its subject. In addition we could include &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.abc-clio.com/ODLIS/odlis_A.aspx&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;terms from ODLIS&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="109" LastActivityDate="2012-05-22T22:14:19.720" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="9" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="6" CreationDate="2012-05-22T22:23:04.593" Score="8" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Libraries are not about books but about organized collections of documents. Book store questions may be on topic same as file management questions. For instance you could ask about how to manage your private collection of images. How about questions abnout Picasa, Flickr, Youtube etc.? These are all digital libraries as well. I am fine with book store questions but it's not the &quot;book&quot; which makes these questions on-topic, but the collection of books.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="109" LastActivityDate="2012-05-22T22:23:04.593" />
  <row Id="10" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="6" CreationDate="2012-05-23T01:04:01.787" Score="4" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Book stores have a completely different motive than libraries and they exist in a seperate ecosystem too. There is some overlap but bookstores in general would probably be better served by going to a more general &quot;retail store&quot; type forum. Libraries have their own niche apart from book stores and thus I would say no such queries are not on topic. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="125" LastActivityDate="2012-05-23T01:04:01.787" />
  <row Id="11" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-05-23T01:16:19.073" Score="4" ViewCount="144" Body="&lt;p&gt;Obviously the American Library Association is a big organization and their involvement could be a massive boon to our community. Alternatively it could end up being a boondoggle and waste of time. I'm sure others have more experience dealing with the ALA and I'd wager we probably have some ALA members or staff on the site already. So, what do we do about the ALA and other such professional organizations? &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="125" LastActivityDate="2012-05-30T05:44:08.557" Title="How and When do we get the ALA involved in this site and how involved do we let them get?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;site-promotion&gt;&lt;us&gt;&lt;ala&gt;" AnswerCount="4" CommentCount="5" />
  <row Id="12" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="2" CreationDate="2012-05-23T02:11:13.753" Score="1" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I am not an expert in the subject matter, but I would suggest asking those questions in a way that &lt;em&gt;elicits&lt;/em&gt; the factors that determine different types of libraries' different choices. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So rather than&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;How should any library handle this issue/problem?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;the question could be asked as/edited to&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;How do a library's audience, community and speciality affect how it can best handle [issue/problem]?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can then imagine an answer along the lines of:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Audience matters a lot. I used to work in a university library where we used [solution A]. It worked for us because the audience [did X, Y and Z]. But when I moved to a public library that also considered adopting [solution A], we found it unworkable because our most frequent users were [educational background/age group] and they found A too hard to use. So we instead used [solution B], which was not only easier for users but accommodated our  collection of [gizmos]. I am also aware of a paper from [conference, with link] that suggests that libraries with [kind of audience] have generally had better experiences with adoption of [solutions] with features [P, Q and R].&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;p&gt;So when considering how to solve [problem], I would consider your main user groups and possibly do some trials of [solutions A and B] with a few volunteer users.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="139" LastActivityDate="2012-05-23T02:11:13.753" />
  <row Id="13" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-05-23T02:32:08.773" Score="10" ViewCount="110" Body="&lt;p&gt;I was lead to believe that &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Information_science&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;information science&lt;/a&gt; was ontopic, but it appears that most of the questions have to do with libraries. For example, would topics related to eDiscovery be offtopic even though they fall within the domain of information science? If so, what sub-domains of information science are ontopic, and how does one test to confirm the topics presented fit within those terms?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="88" LastEditorUserId="144" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-05-23T17:16:46.537" LastActivityDate="2012-05-31T03:10:29.233" Title="Is information science as a domain ontopic?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;scope&gt;" AnswerCount="3" />
  <row Id="14" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-05-23T02:55:41.590" Score="13" ViewCount="101" Body="&lt;p&gt;I went through library school without a strong exposure to the archival profession and its rich history and scholarship. I'm trying to make up for lost time now, but am wondering if questions involving archives are welcome here. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Because of the increasing relevance of archival theory/practice to the preservation of born digital materials I would like to see archives included. But I was wondering what other people think?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;...and then there are museums :-D&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="51" LastActivityDate="2012-05-23T19:44:33.720" Title="Are questions about archives on topic, and should they be solicited somehow?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;scope&gt;&lt;archives&gt;" AnswerCount="3" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="15" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="6" CreationDate="2012-05-23T03:16:36.097" Score="0" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I'd say yes, in fact, bookstore were some of the best &quot;libraries&quot; for some collections (for example, tech/computer books), but the fact is that they're rapidly going away, and likely will completely go away within the next 3-10 years.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="88" LastActivityDate="2012-05-23T03:16:36.097" />
  <row Id="16" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="13" CreationDate="2012-05-23T11:36:53.363" Score="18" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;It's up to the community that forms. Certainly there was &lt;a href=&quot;http://discuss.area51.stackexchange.com/q/4109/41190&quot;&gt;discussion during the proposal phase that suggested that it was on-topic&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I would suggest that it should be on-topic. That said, since there are more librarians in the world than there are information science academics, I suspect that library-oriented content will dominate.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="139" LastActivityDate="2012-05-23T11:36:53.363" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="17" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="11" CreationDate="2012-05-23T14:54:06.017" Score="2" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Well, if nothing else, it should most likely wait a while - we want to get our site established and running, decide the scope, what is on/off topic, etc. before we rush out and get big groups like ALA interested  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="22" LastActivityDate="2012-05-23T14:54:06.017" />
  <row Id="19" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="14" CreationDate="2012-05-23T16:54:34.023" Score="5" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I do think archives should be included because archivists go through a Library &amp;amp; Information Science degree program. I would say no to museums and galleries because they are a different degree program, so the education and philosophies might be different. Archivists fall under the umbrella term of the &quot;librarian&quot; profession due to the similar education while museum and galleries are a separate profession, in my opinion.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="97" LastActivityDate="2012-05-23T16:54:34.023" />
  <row Id="20" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="14" CreationDate="2012-05-23T18:58:07.770" Score="-3" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I would say that questions on archives should not be considered on topic. Archives is a separate profession from librarianship (evidenced by the existence of separate professional organizations, for example) that, while related to librarianship (and museum studies, as another information setting), also has ties to history and is more closely aligned to records management. Archives and libraries have different theoretical frameworks that underlie the organization and description of materials (archival arrangement and description vs. cataloging, for example). Although some archival programs are part of library degree programs, this is far from universal, as many schools offer archival studies through their history department and, within North America, the University of British Columbia, Georgia State and San Jose State offer a Master of Archival Studies or Master of Archives and Records Administration degree.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Questions regarding the preservation of born-digital materials that are not specific to a particular information environment might be better suited to the proposed Digital Preservation stack.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="27" LastActivityDate="2012-05-23T18:58:07.770" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="21" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="24" CreationDate="2012-05-23T19:39:00.760" Score="4" ViewCount="62" Body="&lt;p&gt;For example: &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Into what age groups is it most effective to divide storytimes?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;How might one best use Facebook as a tool with one's teen councilors, volunteers or patrons? (And I have plenty of subdividing questions, such as Do you allow teens to moderate any aspect of your Facebook presence; and, Do you address the fact that Facebook requires users to be 13 or older?)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="66" LastEditorUserId="38" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-05-23T20:46:58.913" LastActivityDate="2012-05-23T20:47:55.977" Title="Are youth services questions on topic?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;scope&gt;&lt;youth-services&gt;&lt;public-libraries&gt;" AnswerCount="2" />
  <row Id="22" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="14" CreationDate="2012-05-23T19:44:33.720" Score="7" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;As an archivist who's title is librarian (that is I do both archival and library work) I think that the archival questions are certainly on topic. While the work &lt;em&gt;can&lt;/em&gt; be very separate from library work, in my day to day job it is one in the same. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For example, my work envolves cataloging and metadata tasks for both archival materials and electronic journal articles and I need to worry about digital and physical preservation of our collections (and yes, I am waiting w/ bated breath for the Digital Preservation stack to get into beta). &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Often the questions faced by archivists are faced by librarians as well: how to create a collection development plan or how to catalog a type of material. Yes, they are answered using different sets of background knowledge, but they all stem from the same premise of caring for and providing access to information no matter its form. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="40" LastActivityDate="2012-05-23T19:44:33.720" />
  <row Id="23" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="4" CreationDate="2012-05-23T20:38:40.983" Score="3" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I'm not sure if you're suggesting restricting the list of available tags or just coming up with a list of possible tags to use in questions, so I'll try to hit both points.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ignoring for the moment that there is no way to pre-create tags or to enforce that only existing tags are used, you might find it best to let tags grow naturally. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It'd be difficult to predict which questions will be asked or how they're best discovered through tagging. Over time, you should end up with a decent set of tags that accurately reflects the topics of the various questions you have.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now, of course, there's room for interpretation here and sometimes there will be two or more tags referring to the same thing. Then you can pick the canonical version (by asking here on meta, if needed) and set up &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.stackoverflow.com/questions/70710/what-are-tag-synonyms-how-do-they-work&quot;&gt;tag synonyms&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Last but not least, as you (as a community) work on your tags, keep an eye out for &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.stackoverflow.com/2010/08/the-death-of-meta-tags/&quot;&gt;meta tags&lt;/a&gt; and do your best to avoid them.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="26" LastActivityDate="2012-05-23T20:38:40.983" />
  <row Id="24" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="21" CreationDate="2012-05-23T20:40:32.777" Score="11" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I would think that, being a legitimate concern for libraries, that questions like this would be on topic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="22" LastActivityDate="2012-05-23T20:40:32.777" />
  <row Id="25" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="21" CreationDate="2012-05-23T20:47:55.977" Score="8" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I hope so! I'm a Youth Librarian!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Youth Librarianship is part of &quot;Library and Information Science&quot; so topics regarding it should be considered on topic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="97" LastActivityDate="2012-05-23T20:47:55.977" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="26" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="13" CreationDate="2012-05-24T02:17:41.520" Score="0" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Someone else may want to post an answer arguing the opposite, so that&#xA;  users can decide.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Sure why not.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I originally thought of information science as data classification which seems related to libraries.  I then looked on wikipedia (librarians please don't cringe) and found &quot;However, it is actually a broad, interdisciplinary field, incorporating not only aspects of computer science, but often diverse fields such as archival science, cognitive science, commerce, communications, law, library science, museology, management, mathematics, philosophy, public policy, and the social sciences.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Boy, that's broad.  So most of the content here is about libraries, some is about information science related to libraries.  And some is about academic information science as not related to libraries?  That feels weird.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As I write the counter opinion, I can't really argue this.  As the site grows people will follow the relevant tags and I don't imagine the info science will overshadow the library &quot;core.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Note: I'm not a librarian and not planning to stay with the site in the long run so nothing vested in the outcome either way (I'm a computer programmer but I'd like to see this community succeed.  Turns out librarians know more about the stack exchange way than many techies do!)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="137" LastActivityDate="2012-05-24T02:17:41.520" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="27" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="28" CreationDate="2012-05-24T03:47:09.253" Score="2" ViewCount="51" Body="&lt;p&gt;Since I can only vote for 1 as answer, is commenting on all good answers with thanks considered filling the site with chatter?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="184" LastEditorUserId="96" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-05-24T09:49:17.033" LastActivityDate="2012-05-24T19:15:12.957" Title="&quot;Best practice&quot; response to multiple good answers?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;etiquette&gt;&lt;comments&gt;" AnswerCount="1" />
  <row Id="28" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="27" CreationDate="2012-05-24T09:48:51.950" Score="8" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;You can vote 30 times per UTC day, plus 10 more times on questions&#xA;  only.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/privileges/vote-up&quot;&gt;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/privileges/vote-up&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I'd recommend waiting a day to come back to the answers you'd like to vote. You can also cancel votes by clicking on the upvote or downvote button again.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Remember, marking a question as the accepted answer is not the same as voting on answers, you can only mark one answer as accepted and this can be cancelled or changed any time unlike voting which can get 'locked in' after a certain amount of time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Unless you have something valuable you can contribute to the answer it's best not to comment. But it's acceptable to thank somebody in a comment &lt;em&gt;in addition to&lt;/em&gt; making a point (even if that's nothing more than explaining &lt;em&gt;how&lt;/em&gt; you found the answer useful).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="96" LastEditorUserId="144" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-05-24T19:15:12.957" LastActivityDate="2012-05-24T19:15:12.957" />
  <row Id="29" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="30" CreationDate="2012-05-24T10:17:26.033" Score="6" ViewCount="68" Body="&lt;p&gt;Aren't most questions already asking 'What is the best way to do X?'&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What does this tag achieve?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="96" LastActivityDate="2012-05-24T19:22:50.090" Title="Do we really need the 'best-practices' tag?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;tags&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="0" FavoriteCount="1" />
  <row Id="30" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="29" CreationDate="2012-05-24T14:41:47.527" Score="13" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;No, those types of tags should be avoided. Think of it this way &amp;mdash;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It's not likely the question is actually &lt;em&gt;about&lt;/em&gt; the subject of &quot;best practices.&quot; Tags are supposed to tell you what the question is about (the subject of the question). Tags are &lt;strong&gt;not&lt;/strong&gt; supposed to be used to describe &lt;em&gt;why&lt;/em&gt; the question was asked, or similar types of meta-categorization.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So tags like [beginner] and [best-practices] and [subjective] are to be avoided.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.stackoverflow.com/2010/08/the-death-of-meta-tags/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Death of Meta Tags&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="81" LastEditorUserId="81" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-05-24T19:22:50.090" LastActivityDate="2012-05-24T19:22:50.090" />
  <row Id="31" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="32" CreationDate="2012-05-24T19:55:16.963" Score="2" ViewCount="76" Body="&lt;p&gt;There have been a few questions from people asking for help finding library resources -- the type of question a &lt;em&gt;library user&lt;/em&gt; would pose at the reference desk, rather than a question that someone in the profession would ask. Are these questions on topic? &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="31" LastActivityDate="2012-05-30T19:50:02.950" Title="Are reference questions on topic?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;scope&gt;" AnswerCount="2" />
  <row Id="32" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="31" CreationDate="2012-05-24T19:55:17.430" Score="9" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I believe those questions are better directed to someplace like the Internet Public Library, or the SE could rapidly be overwhelmed with this sort of question. (And while our expertise helps to answer the questions, they aren't &lt;em&gt;about&lt;/em&gt; the expertise, if that makes sense.) The exception might be a reference librarian asking for help with a question s/he is fielding from a user.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="31" LastActivityDate="2012-05-24T19:55:17.430" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="33" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="11" CreationDate="2012-05-25T02:16:22.340" Score="4" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;i say spread it to all of our networks (loudly! and talk about how useful this forum is!) but the beauty of stackexchange is that we can do this - ask questions, solve problems, start revolutions - without any association involvement. &#xA;refreshing, no? (and i love me some SLA, so don't think i'm anti-association or anything.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="134" LastActivityDate="2012-05-25T02:16:22.340" />
  <row Id="34" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="11" CreationDate="2012-05-26T13:26:15.723" Score="6" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;My question would be &quot;ALA corporate&quot; (e.g. the staff at 50 E. Huron in Chicago), &quot;ALA organization&quot; (e.g. the folks the membership elect to do things), or &quot;ALA members&quot; (e.g. dues-paying folks)?  I think of Stack Exchange sites as communities onto their own, so direct involvement by the first and second could cause friction if their goal is to regularize and integrate with other ALA activities.  The third are most welcome to join and shape this community.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;-- From a 20-year dues-paying member of ALA&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="215" LastActivityDate="2012-05-26T13:26:15.723" />
  <row Id="35" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="6" CreationDate="2012-05-28T05:39:37.520" Score="1" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;All of the sample topics posed could equally come out of the public library setting: from the discussion of most &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.libraryjournal.com/article/CA6698264.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;user-friendly classification&lt;/a&gt;, to the perennial need for book/item displays. My library looks to bookstores for event &amp;amp; marketing ideas.&#xA;As Jacob pointed out, both places are trying to organize and provide access to content. &#xA;Aside from questions about how to liquidate 50 boxes of unsold holiday merchandise, I can't think of an inappropriate question. (Even then, I would say take it to your local library and they will use it in craft-time!)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="184" LastActivityDate="2012-05-28T05:39:37.520" />
  <row Id="36" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="11" CreationDate="2012-05-30T05:44:08.557" Score="5" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Coming from an overseas point of view, ALA can be involved, but if so, we should also extend the invitation to ALIA, CILIP and others.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I would prefer that responses came from individuals rather than entities, but it would be good to use the resources of our national organisations to keep the list of participants varied and the answers informative!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="249" LastActivityDate="2012-05-30T05:44:08.557" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="37" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-05-30T10:24:51.227" Score="3" ViewCount="53" Body="&lt;p&gt;This is number 5 of &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.stackoverflow.com/2010/07/the-7-essential-meta-questions-of-every-beta/&quot;&gt;the 7 Essential Meta Questions of Every Beta&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;. The current design and logo is ... well, there is no design. So how about logo, colors, borders and all this little nice stuff that makes a site pleasant and distinct to other sites. I found browsing around &lt;a href=&quot;http://stackexchange.com/sites&quot;&gt;existing stackexchange site&lt;/a&gt; very inspiring.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My personal opinion: the design &lt;em&gt;should not only mirror the &quot;book&quot; metaphor!&lt;/em&gt; Libraries are not about books but about documents, which can be articles, images, films, files, audio etc. And libraries are about the use and exchange of documents. How about a gust of papers, videos, cds, bits, reels, tweets, books etc. falling from the sky and a meadow with chairs, sofas, children, researchers etc. at the bottom?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="109" LastActivityDate="2012-06-03T01:18:42.557" Title="What should our logo and site design look like?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;design&gt;" AnswerCount="3" />
  <row Id="38" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="37" CreationDate="2012-05-30T14:53:56.360" Score="1" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I agree that the logo and site design should be worked on.  Your suggestion is interesting; I like that it includes the data &amp;amp; media as well as people.  Were you thinking about that for the header?  Would it be too busy/too small for something that size (considering the top/bottom orientation of falling material &amp;amp; people)?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="101" LastActivityDate="2012-05-30T14:53:56.360" />
  <row Id="39" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="42" CreationDate="2012-05-30T19:15:37.527" Score="3" ViewCount="83" Body="&lt;p&gt;Stack Exchange is meant to be a question and answer site. Questions that are asked should have a definite answer and should avoid being too discussion based. There was one posted recently asking for &quot;unique adult programs&quot;. Are questions asking for programming ideas be on topic?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="97" LastEditorUserId="26" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-05-30T19:36:47.380" LastActivityDate="2012-05-30T19:52:50.637" Title="Are questions about programming ideas on topic?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;scope&gt;" AnswerCount="2" />
  <row Id="40" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="39" CreationDate="2012-05-30T19:46:44.817" Score="0" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I'm not certain that the event programming ideas question is valid from a Stack Exchange perspective, since SE comes out of the computer programming world where 1 question really doesn't have more than 5 right answers. That said, I've come to SE from Unshelved Answers where this question would have been perfectly appropriate because it is soliciting information from engaged professionals that will allow the questioner to do a better job/be a better professional.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="184" LastActivityDate="2012-05-30T19:46:44.817" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="41" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="31" CreationDate="2012-05-30T19:50:02.950" Score="1" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I have to split the question into two parts:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;(1) Are reference questions asking for &lt;em&gt;facts&lt;/em&gt; on-topic? No. They're on whatever topic they're asking about, and if that's not libraries or information science, they're off-topic for this community.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;(2) Are reference questions asking &lt;em&gt;where to find facts&lt;/em&gt; on-topic? Yes. If it's a member of the public asking about library resources, that's a libraries question; if it's a reference librarian asking for the name of a good resource, that's a professional expertise question within libraries.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="345" LastActivityDate="2012-05-30T19:50:02.950" />
  <row Id="42" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="39" CreationDate="2012-05-30T19:52:50.637" Score="5" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;There is more of a problem here with this particular question than it just being about library programming. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First and foremost, StackExchange is not a forum - question posts are expected to be solving some sort of problem. This particular question, such as it is, isn't really a question at all - there is nothing to be solved. The only answers that this question is going to receive are lists of what other libraries did, and everyone is going to have a different idea on what makes their programming choices &quot;unique&quot;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There is no real effort in solving a problem, here - because there is no problem here to solve. There is also no way to determine which answer is the most correct.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;From the &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/faq#dontask&quot;&gt;site FAQ&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;To prevent your question from being flagged and possibly removed,&#xA;  avoid  asking subjective questions where... every answer is equally valid: “What’s your favorite &lt;strong&gt;__&lt;/strong&gt;?”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is pretty much what this question is doing, but replacing &quot;favourite&quot; with &quot;unique&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Also, &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.stackoverflow.com/2011/01/real-questions-have-answers/&quot;&gt;this SE blog post&lt;/a&gt; also points out another useful tip that can be applied:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Real questions have answers, not items or ideas or opinions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Since this question is only ever going to get ideas and opinions, and not answers, it is not a very good fit for the site. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is not to say that any question about library programming is automatically off-topic here, but it does mean that there needs to be a concrete focus on making sure that we ask questions that are indeed actual questions that have concrete answers. Stack Exchange is not a forum - it is intended to help you solve problems that you face.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I realize that a lot of the content on this site will be of the more subjective sorts of questions than, say, Stack Overflow, but that does not mean that it is a place where anything goes. If a question about library programming can be asked in such a way that it becomes more of a Good Subjective question than a Bad Subjective question (see this &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.stackoverflow.com/2010/09/good-subjective-bad-subjective/&quot;&gt;blog post&lt;/a&gt; for more information), then I don't see why they couldn't be considered on topic here. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="22" LastActivityDate="2012-05-30T19:52:50.637" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="43" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-05-30T20:12:21.377" Score="6" ViewCount="343" Body="&lt;p&gt;One of the essential questions we are supposed to ask ourselves as a beta site is who the mods should be. When a SE site first hits beta, a few &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.stackoverflow.com/2010/07/moderator-pro-tempore/&quot;&gt;pro-tem mods&lt;/a&gt; are selected. As the linked post states, &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;This is a temporary, short-term appointment. Moderators Pro Tem focus&#xA;  and expedite the essential needs of each new site. By the end of Beta,&#xA;  the community will be better suited to hold their own elections.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So, for now, we should take a look at who is interested in doing such a thing. Some basic rules to keep in mind:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;A person interested in being a mod posts an answer featuring username&#xA;and the link to the profile, plus an optional why-me text.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;If you think someone might make an awesome mod here, nominate them and then poke them in &lt;a href=&quot;http://chat.stackexchange.com/rooms/3517/libraries-and-information-science&quot;&gt;chat&lt;/a&gt; and let them know of the potential opportunity! If you're nominated and aren't interested, please post a comment or edit the nomination to decline.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Users express their support/negation by voting, and support words/doubts as comments.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The SE team uses this information as a guideline of who to choose as moderators.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="22" LastEditorUserId="144" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-05-30T23:22:29.237" LastActivityDate="2012-06-12T18:13:09.727" CommunityOwnedDate="2012-05-30T23:22:38.833" Title="Who should our moderators be?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;moderation&gt;" AnswerCount="4" CommentCount="9" FavoriteCount="0" />
  <row Id="44" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="37" CreationDate="2012-05-30T20:18:21.257" Score="1" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Maybe something a bit simpler -- like the same item in several formats: a period script of Macbeth, Macbeth in a book, Macbeth on a DVD -- representing libraries as keepers of the past and providers of the material in changing formats. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="195" LastActivityDate="2012-05-30T20:18:21.257" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="45" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-05-30T20:18:30.857" Score="8" ViewCount="126" Body="&lt;p&gt;So, after a long time chilling in Area51, we have made it to public beta. This is a pretty awesome thing - and we seem to be rolling pretty well with it. Lots of good questions and answers happening on a variety of library topics, which is cool to see!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Anyone committed to the beta is aware of the site, but now we are open to anyone! How can we get the word out to the world at large that LIS.SE exists and is awesome? There are a large variety of libraries and library groups out there that I am sure would love to be a part of this awesomeness.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;How can we get the word out? Similar to &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/11/how-and-when-do-we-get-the-ala-involved-in-this-site-and-how-involved-do-we-let&quot;&gt;this question&lt;/a&gt; - how do we let people know we are here? How can we spread the word far and wide (and not just necessarily online, either!)?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="22" LastEditorUserId="109" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-06-27T12:24:22.243" LastActivityDate="2012-06-27T12:24:22.243" Title="How do we spread the word about our awesome site?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;site-promotion&gt;" AnswerCount="5" />
  <row Id="46" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="45" CreationDate="2012-05-30T22:56:13.933" Score="4" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I've been tweeting it, and my tweets have gotten a fair few RTs, so that's something... but too much tweeting the same thing becomes tweetspam.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One thing &lt;a href=&quot;http://digitalhumanities.org/answers/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;DH Answers&lt;/a&gt; does that we might emulate is auto-posting new questions to a dedicated Twitter account. For those of us who follow Twitter, that's easier to monitor than having the LibStEx site open, or remembering to check it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I plan to show LibStEx to my lib-tech students; with luck that will bring in more folks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="60" LastActivityDate="2012-05-30T22:56:13.933" CommentCount="7" />
  <row Id="47" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="45" CreationDate="2012-05-30T23:32:34.530" Score="1" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Share the site on library listservs? &lt;br/&gt; Blog about it? &lt;br/&gt; E-mail all of our librarian friends? &lt;br/&gt; Stand on the street corner dressed as the Statue of Liberty holding a sign? OK, maybe the sign is too much ... &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="195" LastActivityDate="2012-05-30T23:32:34.530" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="48" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="45" CreationDate="2012-05-31T00:09:53.360" Score="2" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;A note in your local professional newsletter/bulletin, an e-mail to your co-workers (if applicable), a post on relevant mailing lists, plus of course all of the relevant personal social media (Twitter, Facebook, Tumblr, Google+, LinkedIn, &amp;amp;c.). . . . How do you announce anything?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I myself have submitted something to the &lt;em&gt;LibraryJournal&lt;/em&gt; Tumblr, which is read by a lot of library-loving, technology-literate people; here's hoping they publish it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="345" LastActivityDate="2012-05-31T00:09:53.360" />
  <row Id="49" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="13" CreationDate="2012-05-31T03:10:29.233" Score="2" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I would agree that information science should be considered on topic for many of the reasons that participants in this thread &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.libraries.stackexchange.com/q/14/360&quot;&gt;Are questions about archives on topic, and should they be solicited somehow?&lt;/a&gt; were arguing that questions about archives should be considered on topic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As libraries increasingly engage in building digital collections and in new services related to data curation and digital humanities, the concerns and perspectives of information science will be important and relevant.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Data representation, knowledge organization, user communities, information behavior, systems analysis ... all these are important information science topics that I would hope an LIS Stack Exchange would engage with.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="360" LastActivityDate="2012-05-31T03:10:29.233" />
  <row Id="50" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="134" CreationDate="2012-05-31T16:52:44.823" Score="11" ViewCount="209" Body="&lt;p&gt;I keep wanting to post digital preservation questions here; I've seen that some DP related questions have already surfaced in the Q&amp;amp;A. For those that are not aware, there is another stack exchange proposal for &quot;Digital Preservation&quot; in the works. I'm a bit confused where the line is between questions appropriate to Digital Preservation and those appropriate to Libraries. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A quick look at the name tags shows there are quite a few DP folks lurking/participating already--so maybe there is a clear distinction that I'm just missing but our guru's will point out.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Just curious, is there a way for moderators to move questions from one site to another?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="90" LastActivityDate="2013-02-25T13:26:21.203" Title="Where is the line between the Digital Preservation and Libraries stack exchange sites?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;moderation&gt;" AnswerCount="6" CommentCount="1" FavoriteCount="2" />
  <row Id="51" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="50" CreationDate="2012-05-31T16:56:59.060" Score="13" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I think the DP proposal should be withdrawn and we should just talk about those issues here.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="51" LastActivityDate="2012-05-31T16:56:59.060" CommentCount="6" />
  <row Id="52" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="50" CreationDate="2012-05-31T18:21:41.093" Score="4" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Digital Preservation seems like it would fit as a subset of questions here - there seems to be a lot of overlap. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As for merging/migrating questions - this is a possibility - mods do have the ability to migrate questions from site to site (for example, when the Literature beta site closed, a bunch of the questions from there got moved to SciFi.SE). People with enough rep to vote to close also have the ability to suggest some migrations, but that is pretty limited. You can also flag questions and suggest they be migrated. However, I don't know how that would work for a beta proposal - I have no idea if it is something that should happen, let alone if it is even possible. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="22" LastActivityDate="2012-05-31T18:21:41.093" />
  <row Id="53" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="55" CreationDate="2012-05-31T18:50:58.147" Score="6" ViewCount="61" Body="&lt;p&gt;Specifically inspired by &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/264/how-to-keep-high-security-standards-while-allowing-self-checkout/447#447&quot;&gt;this answer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The wording of the answer, combined with the user listing the same URL as their website on their profile, makes this seem pretty obviously like self-promotion.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The FAQ sayeth:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Be careful, because the community frowns on overt self-promotion and tends to vote it down and flag it as spam. Post good, relevant answers, and if some (but not all) happen to be about your product or website, so be it. However, you must disclose your affiliation in your answers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So, what's the way to deal with these kinds of questions? Comment, edit, or both? Or is a one-off promotional post on an appropriate question &quot;harmless?&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="198" LastEditorUserId="144" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-05-31T20:35:13.583" LastActivityDate="2012-05-31T20:35:13.583" Title="What's the etiquette for dealing with promotional answers?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;flagging&gt;&lt;spam&gt;" AnswerCount="2" />
  <row Id="54" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="53" CreationDate="2012-05-31T19:14:11.890" Score="7" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Not &quot;harmless&quot;, that's for sure. If we allow this to continue, it won't be long before there are companies that sell to libraries flooding answers strictly to advertise their brands.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Comment that self-promotion without a statement about being affiliated with the company is not appropriate for the site. Just like the FAQ says, &quot;you must disclose your affiliation in your answers.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="97" LastActivityDate="2012-05-31T19:14:11.890" />
  <row Id="55" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="53" CreationDate="2012-05-31T19:15:56.070" Score="10" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;In that particular instance, based on both the answer &amp;amp; profile, that it is spam and should be flagged as such for a moderator to take care of.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As for promotion in general, I think it depends on the case.  Mentioning a product you've used and have experience with and is relevant to answering the question is within the bounds of acceptable promotion.  As you and KatieR quoted, promoting your own creation/business/etc without acknowledging your association is against the rules.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="101" LastActivityDate="2012-05-31T19:15:56.070" />
  <row Id="56" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="50" CreationDate="2012-06-01T15:16:44.863" Score="8" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;The difficulty with shifting digital preservation here comes from the proposal stage--there was some discussion about the lines of library/information science and a lot of people seemed to want the site to focus exclusively on libraries. The archives and museum communities also have a huge stake (larger, I would argue) in digital preservation, but often not so much a stake in libraries.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That said, I think DP is going to have a tough time getting the required high rep users, and if there's consensus that &quot;information science&quot; includes &quot;cultural heritage&quot; more broadly, I think it makes a lot of sense to include DP questions on the LIS SE.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="31" LastActivityDate="2012-06-01T15:16:44.863" />
  <row Id="57" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-06-01T17:19:48.580" Score="7" ViewCount="118" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/profession&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'profession'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;profession&lt;/a&gt; seems like it's a bad tag. I can't see how it would be useful or beneficial in classifying a question. Should it be killed before it gains traction and ends up on every question asked about the profession of being a librarian?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="104" LastEditorUserId="104" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-06-09T13:35:52.040" LastActivityDate="2012-06-09T13:35:52.040" Title="Should [profession] be killed before it snowballs?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;tags&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="14" FavoriteCount="1" />
  <row Id="58" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="43" CreationDate="2012-06-01T19:14:59.670" Score="10" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I will happily throw my hat into the ring. (If I had an actual hat.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I'm &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/users/22/ashley-nunn&quot;&gt;Ashley Nunn&lt;/a&gt; - I have been using the network for a while now - I am mostly active on Gaming, where I am a 10k user who loves to help out with the various tools and responsibilities and such. I believe in at least trying to leave comments along the way to help people learn how the SE network works. :D &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I don't have a huge pile of library experience, per se - I work in Inter-Library Loans at the University of Waterloo while I work on getting my undergrad degree in English (if I have my way, it will be a Rhetoric and Professional Writing degree, with specializations in Digital Media and Global Literature), and eventually I want to go to U of Toronto to get my Masters of Information in Library Science and Archives and Records Management. Been working in ILL for about a year now. It's pretty much the most awesome thing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So yeah. That's me. :D&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="22" LastActivityDate="2012-06-01T19:14:59.670" CommunityOwnedDate="2012-06-01T19:14:59.670" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="59" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="57" CreationDate="2012-06-02T03:03:28.930" Score="2" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I added that tag because I thought there should be a tag for questions about the profession versus tags for library operations or equipment or policies. I'm happy to have the discussion here in meta, though. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="215" LastActivityDate="2012-06-02T03:03:28.930" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="60" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="61" CreationDate="2012-06-02T23:32:39.863" Score="1" ViewCount="44" Body="&lt;p&gt;So far we have the following tags:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/university-libraries&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'university-libraries'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;university-libraries&lt;/a&gt; (14 questions)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The following tag was introduced after the start of this discussion:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/academic-libraries&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'academic-libraries'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;academic-libraries&lt;/a&gt; (2 questions)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The following existed but were removed after tag edits:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/academic&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'academic'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;academic&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/academia&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'academia'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;academia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We have never had the following tags:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/college-libraries&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'college-libraries'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;college-libraries&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/research-libraries&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'research-libraries'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;research-libraries&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&quot;College libraries&quot; is usually taken to include university libraries, but many colleges aren't universities, so the reverse isn't true. Academic libraries are both college and university libraries. Research libraries are most academic libraries a few major public libraries (e.g., NYPL).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Nobody's using the tag &quot;academic.&quot; The distinction between academia and academic libraries is probably very small in this site's context. The use of &quot;public-libraries&quot; and &quot;university-libraries&quot; indicates that the &quot;-libraries&quot; ending is standard here.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Real-life organizations include such groups as the Association of College and Research Libraries and the Association of Research Libraries. &quot;College libraries&quot; and &quot;research libraries&quot; are therefore recognized terms in the broader professional community.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This looks like it may need some cleanup before it gets out of control, possibly by designating one or two central tags and several synonyms. Suggestions?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="345" LastEditorUserId="26" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-06-27T21:24:41.110" LastActivityDate="2012-06-27T21:24:41.110" Title="How should we clean up the tags university-libraries, academia, and academic?" Tags="&lt;feature-request&gt;&lt;status-completed&gt;&lt;tags&gt;&lt;tag-synonyms&gt;&lt;retagging&gt;" AnswerCount="1" FavoriteCount="1" />
  <row Id="61" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="60" CreationDate="2012-06-02T23:32:40.443" Score="4" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;My suggestion here is to make the following tag a main tag:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/academic-libraries&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'academic-libraries'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;academic-libraries&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Implement as a synonym of the new main tag:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/university-libraries&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'university-libraries'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;university-libraries&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While synonyms cannot be created for presently non-existing tags, the following are eligible for future synonyming if the occasion arises:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/college-libraries&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'college-libraries'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;college-libraries&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/academia&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'academia'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;academia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/academic&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'academic'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;academic&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Finally, &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/research-libraries&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'research-libraries'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;research-libraries&lt;/a&gt; should be a separate tag. The tag wiki should be used to disambiguate it from the above.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="345" LastEditorUserId="345" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-06-08T05:25:14.467" LastActivityDate="2012-06-08T05:25:14.467" CommunityOwnedDate="2012-06-02T23:32:40.443" CommentCount="7" />
  <row Id="62" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="57" CreationDate="2012-06-02T23:34:55.197" Score="1" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;That's a valid concern, but I think in this case it depends on how it's defined. For example, I saw a question about Cutter numbers the other day, and while librarians do use them professionally, I don't see how the &lt;em&gt;question&lt;/em&gt; is in any way about the profession of being a librarian or information scientist; it's about cataloging, not the profession. You see the difference? I'll see about making a tag wiki entry to clarify this and promote proper usage. If it turns out to be a problem, we can discuss removing it at that time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="345" LastActivityDate="2012-06-02T23:34:55.197" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="63" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="37" CreationDate="2012-06-03T01:18:42.557" Score="0" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I think we should also reflect the values of the profession in how we release our logo. We should strongly consider either A) using a logo that is already available under a Creative Commons or similar license, or B) releasing any logo that is created under a similar license.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ideas:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://thenounproject.com/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;The Noun Project&lt;/a&gt; provides great icons under CC licenses. Maybe something combining a &lt;a href=&quot;http://thenounproject.com/noun/book/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;book&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://thenounproject.com/noun/library/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;library&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://thenounproject.com/noun/museum/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;museum&lt;/a&gt;, &amp;amp; &lt;a href=&quot;http://thenounproject.com/noun/computer/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;computer&lt;/a&gt;?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;There's already a lot of great &quot;Ask a Librarian&quot; logos out there, for instance on Flickr. Could we reuse one or ask the artist to create a new one?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="136" LastActivityDate="2012-06-03T01:18:42.557" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="64" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="92" CreationDate="2012-06-03T03:55:29.677" Score="4" ViewCount="24" Body="&lt;p&gt;Most of our tags use the plural for things like institutions. (E.g., &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/public-libraries&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'public-libraries'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;public-libraries&lt;/a&gt;.) Should &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/archive&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'archive'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;archive&lt;/a&gt; be renamed &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/archives&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'archives'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;archives&lt;/a&gt; to maintain consistency and avoid confusion? If so, should it be made a synonym of &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/archives&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'archives'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;archives&lt;/a&gt;?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="345" LastEditorUserId="26" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-06-07T19:59:43.727" LastActivityDate="2012-06-07T21:13:30.970" Title="Should the [archive] tag be changed and synonym'd to [archives]?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;status-completed&gt;&lt;tags&gt;&lt;tag-synonyms&gt;&lt;retagging&gt;" AnswerCount="3" CommentCount="0" FavoriteCount="0" />
  <row Id="65" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="66" CreationDate="2012-06-03T04:09:41.220" Score="1" ViewCount="17" Body="&lt;p&gt;As of this writing, &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/public-libraries&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'public-libraries'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;public-libraries&lt;/a&gt; has 12 questions and &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/public-library&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'public-library'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;public-library&lt;/a&gt; has 2. Obviously these are intended to be the same category, and plurals appear to be the order of the day, so I've submitted retagging edits for the two &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/public-library&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'public-library'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;public-library&lt;/a&gt; questions. However, this may not be sufficient to indicate a need for a synonym.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="345" LastEditorUserId="345" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-06-08T04:52:05.787" LastActivityDate="2012-06-08T04:52:05.787" Title="Should [public-library] and similar be made synonyms of their plurals (e.g., [public-libraries])?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;tags&gt;&lt;tag-synonyms&gt;" AnswerCount="1" FavoriteCount="0" />
  <row Id="66" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="65" CreationDate="2012-06-03T04:09:41.673" Score="2" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I believe that this does indicate a need for a synonym, as clearly we are experiencing splintering in the tag structure and single-to-plural conversion is intuitive and noncontroversial.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="345" LastActivityDate="2012-06-03T04:09:41.673" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="67" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="91" CreationDate="2012-06-03T04:26:57.533" Score="2" ViewCount="29" Body="&lt;p&gt;As of this writing, &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/interlibrary&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'interlibrary'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;interlibrary&lt;/a&gt; has 2 questions (one tagged both &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/interlibrary&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'interlibrary'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;interlibrary&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/loan&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'loan'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;loan&lt;/a&gt;) and &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/interlibrary-loan&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'interlibrary-loan'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;interlibrary-loan&lt;/a&gt; has 2. Obviously these are intended to be the same category, so I've submitted retagging edits for the two [interlibrary] questions. However, this may not be sufficient to indicate a need for a synonym, and people may wish to disagree with my preference for [interlibrary-loan] over [interlibrary].&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="345" LastEditorUserId="26" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-06-07T19:56:18.863" LastActivityDate="2012-06-07T19:59:06.067" Title="Should [interlibrary] be made a synonym of [interlibrary-loan]?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;status-deferred&gt;&lt;tag-synonyms&gt;" AnswerCount="2" FavoriteCount="0" />
  <row Id="68" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="67" CreationDate="2012-06-03T04:26:57.937" Score="2" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I believe that this does indicate a need for a synonym, as clearly we are experiencing splintering in the tag structure and the full name of interlibrary loan is more understandable to people who don't deal with the subject regularly (and therefore might have questions about it) and will show up when people do searches for the full phrase. Furthermore, one of the prior [interlibrary] questions appears to have been by someone who simply didn't understand how to make multi-word tags, as it was tagged [interlibrary][loan].&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="345" LastActivityDate="2012-06-03T04:26:57.937" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="69" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="64" CreationDate="2012-06-03T04:32:49.960" Score="3" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I believe that, yes, this needs to happen; although there is no current splintering in the tag base, the SE system restricts creating [archives] when [archive] exists. (In the cases of libraries/library, it apparently is unaware of the nonstandard plural, allowing both tags to exist.) However, pluralization in our institutional classification tags is standard here. Furthermore, as there is already usage of the [archive] tag, a synonym will help the community adjust.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="345" LastActivityDate="2012-06-03T04:32:49.960" />
  <row Id="70" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="71" CreationDate="2012-06-03T07:51:12.540" Score="2" ViewCount="40" Body="&lt;p&gt;Currently, the &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/private-collection&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'private-collection'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;private-collection&lt;/a&gt; tag has exactly 1 usage, in the meaning of &quot;home library,&quot; and is on the only question currently tagged &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/home-libraries&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'home-libraries'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;home-libraries&lt;/a&gt;. At the moment, these are clearly intended to mean the same thing, and both are in usage, so one or the other is a candidate for being made into a synonym. The &quot;-libraries&quot; option would match other items in a standard taxonomy of library types that we're essentially implementing here, but &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/private-collection&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'private-collection'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;private-collection&lt;/a&gt; might be slightly less ambiguous.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="345" LastEditorUserId="345" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-06-08T04:59:20.847" LastActivityDate="2012-06-08T05:00:03.030" Title="Should [private-collection] be made a synonym of [home-libraries|home-library]? (Or vice-versa or . . . ?)" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;tags&gt;&lt;tag-synonyms&gt;" AnswerCount="2" FavoriteCount="0" />
  <row Id="71" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="70" CreationDate="2012-06-03T07:51:12.947" Score="2" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;The slight ambiguity of &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/home-libraries&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'home-libraries'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;home-libraries&lt;/a&gt;—private collections in the home vs. &quot;your local (i.e., home) library&quot;—can be easily overcome both by reference to the growing taxonomy (public-libraries, school-libraries, &amp;amp;c.) and more importantly by reference to the tag wiki (which I'm working on).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For this reason, and for those given in the question itself, I think that &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/private-collection&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'private-collection'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;private-collection&lt;/a&gt; should be synonym'd to &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/home-libraries&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'home-libraries'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;home-libraries&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="345" LastEditorUserId="345" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-06-08T05:00:03.030" LastActivityDate="2012-06-08T05:00:03.030" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="72" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="73" CreationDate="2012-06-03T09:56:58.100" Score="1" ViewCount="47" Body="&lt;p&gt;There was recently posted a question to the topic of civil disobedience. Was this question removed by the person who asked the question or by the moderators here?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="389" LastActivityDate="2012-06-03T17:46:10.820" Title="Where's the question about civil disobedience?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" AnswerCount="1" />
  <row Id="73" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="72" CreationDate="2012-06-03T17:04:41.103" Score="3" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;The community deemed it non-constructive (within the purpose of the site) due to having no clear, factually correct answer and downvoted it; at that point, removal by the person who asked the question was merely an acknowledgement of the error in advance of moderation, but one or the other was almost certainly going to happen.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When I follow a link to the question (from my flag history), I get the following message:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;This question was voluntarily removed by its author.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="345" LastEditorUserId="345" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-06-03T17:46:10.820" LastActivityDate="2012-06-03T17:46:10.820" CommunityOwnedDate="2012-06-03T17:04:41.103" />
  <row Id="74" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="43" CreationDate="2012-06-03T17:39:58.143" Score="0" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I'm &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.libraries.stackexchange.com/users/345/m-alan-thomas-ii&quot;&gt;M. Alan Thomas II&lt;/a&gt;. I was active on Unshelved Answers, I was active during the definition phase of this proposal, I even popped in occasionally during the (test of our) commitment phase, and now I'm active here. I've spent a little time hanging out on other SE sites in the interim, but this is pretty much the only one I've got an attachment to.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I'm a &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wikipedia%3aWikiGnome&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;WikiGnome&lt;/a&gt;-type user. I'm more active on Meta than Main. My impulse is to comment and vote more than ask and answer questions. I've raised helpful flags. I've submitted a variety of retagging suggestions on individual posts, I've written tag wiki entries, and I'm the only person using the [&lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/tag-synonyms&quot;&gt;tag-synonyms&lt;/a&gt;] tag here so far. Of course, with my reputation, all of that still requires authorization from others. (Even my questions on Meta so far are really just there to see if people agree that the moderators should do something.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So. I'm never going to get rich, reputation-wise, writing brilliant questions or answers, but I'd like to help behind the scenes as this place works its way through Beta and beyond. Maybe someday, if everything is humming along smoothly and there are good candidates to take my place, I'll quietly bow out and go back to just pottering around, but right now I feel that someone has to work on all of those bits that everyone uses but no-one thinks about.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Obligatory &quot;professional qualifications and associations&quot; block: M.S.–L.I.S. from Ilinois, ALA, IFRT, LIRT, GameRT, OIF supporter, FTRF. Trained as an information scientist for academia, working as a reference librarian in a public library; go figure.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I believe that at least one of our three mods should be a professional, expert member of the LIS community, with or without SE experience, rather than someone who wouldn't be qualified to ask or answer questions here but does have experience on other SE sites. Not only do we need at least one subject-matter expert to handle those moments when one is called for, but if the community is to determine for itself exactly how it is going to work—and other SE sites such as Programmers.SE and RPG.SE have made choices contrary to the global SE norms—then it shouldn't be moderated entirely by people whose purpose is to ensure that that doesn't happen.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="345" LastEditorUserId="345" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-06-12T18:13:09.727" LastActivityDate="2012-06-12T18:13:09.727" CommunityOwnedDate="2012-06-03T17:39:58.143" CommentCount="14" />
  <row Id="75" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="77" CreationDate="2012-06-05T01:50:56.277" Score="0" ViewCount="68" Body="&lt;p&gt;I'll post the ones I suspect are going to get up-votes below; anything clearly on-topic I'm just porting straight into Main.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Remember: An up-vote stands for &quot;off-topic for this site&quot; or &quot;non-constructive.&quot; (You may wish to indicate which in the comments.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="345" LastEditorUserId="345" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-06-05T02:15:01.240" LastActivityDate="2012-06-05T05:10:40.137" Title="Which questions from the definition phase of this proposal that were highly-rated as on-topic are now considered off-topic/non-constructive?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;scope&gt;" AnswerCount="5" CommentCount="4" FavoriteCount="0" />
  <row Id="76" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="75" CreationDate="2012-06-05T01:52:00.707" Score="3" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;What [teen,pre-teen,adult] programs do you run at your library? (and are they well attended?)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Number 2 question with 23 votes. Survey, no correct answer.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="345" LastActivityDate="2012-06-05T01:52:00.707" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="77" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="75" CreationDate="2012-06-05T01:56:25.613" Score="0" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Can you name a book that portrays step-families in a positive light rather than the typical &quot;wicked stepmother&quot; and/or &quot;abusive stepfather&quot; tropes?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Number 3 question with 22 votes. Slightly subjective. This falls into the &quot;no single correct answer, but it asks a question of the professional community that can produce a useful answer list for future reference via community wiki and other methods.&quot; Might need re-wording, of course.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;N.B.:&lt;/strong&gt; A question about this type of question has been posted at &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/81/are-list-answerable-questions-constructive/&quot;&gt;Are list-answerable questions constructive?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="345" LastEditorUserId="345" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-06-05T05:10:40.137" LastActivityDate="2012-06-05T05:10:40.137" CommentCount="7" />
  <row Id="78" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="75" CreationDate="2012-06-05T02:06:27.770" Score="0" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;How do you deal with parents leaving their children in the libraries as alternate free daycare?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Number 6 question (tied) with 16 votes. No known answer. (Seriously.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="345" LastActivityDate="2012-06-05T02:06:27.770" CommentCount="4" />
  <row Id="79" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="75" CreationDate="2012-06-05T02:07:47.457" Score="0" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Do you have a policy for using library facilities after hours? If so, what works or doesn't work, and/or what would you change about your policy?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Number 6 question (tied) with 16 votes. Survey, no correct answer.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="345" LastActivityDate="2012-06-05T02:07:47.457" CommentCount="5" />
  <row Id="80" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="75" CreationDate="2012-06-05T02:09:20.823" Score="0" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Aggressive patrons: how do you deal with them?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Number 8 question with 14 votes. Survey. Possibly salvageable if re-worded.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="345" LastActivityDate="2012-06-05T02:09:20.823" CommentCount="4" />
  <row Id="81" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="84" CreationDate="2012-06-05T02:32:24.597" Score="1" ViewCount="260" Body="&lt;p&gt;Here's my example:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Can you name a book that portrays step-families in a positive light rather than the typical &quot;wicked stepmother&quot; and/or &quot;abusive stepfather&quot; tropes?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;During the Definition phase for this proposal, this was the #3 question with 22 votes. (#2 had one more vote; #1 was only two ahead of that.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Yes, it's slightly subjective and might need re-wording. Ignoring that for a moment, I feel like we have a lot of questions like that around here. I've certainly asked some, although I push concrete, at least semi-objective points to be addressed in the answers so that there's some way of judging them as &quot;good&quot; and &quot;correct.&quot; In this case, the standard would be whether each book addresses the point in question in the manner indicated.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So, is this on-topic and constructive or not? I'll post two arguments below.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="345" LastEditorUserId="345" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-06-05T23:13:57.380" LastActivityDate="2012-06-05T23:13:57.380" Title="Can list-answerable questions (e.g., reader's advisory) be constructive?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;scope&gt;" AnswerCount="3" CommentCount="3" FavoriteCount="1" />
  <row Id="82" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="81" CreationDate="2012-06-05T02:32:24.953" Score="1" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Not all list-answerable questions are good, but not all of them are bad, either. See the list of what might allow for a good such question at &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.stackoverflow.com/2010/09/good-subjective-bad-subjective/&quot;&gt;Good Subjective, Bad Subjective&lt;/a&gt; and the list of what might make for a bad such question at &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.stackoverflow.com/2011/01/real-questions-have-answers/&quot;&gt;Real Questions Have Answers&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The above example asks a question of the professional community that is best answered by the professional community and that can produce a useful answer list for future reference. (Community wiki might be helpful here; there's a reason it automatically triggers on any question with 30 answers.) It was also overwhelmingly accepted as appropriate during the Definition phase of the proposal.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this case, reader's advisory is a professional skill with acknowledged experts and a core library function that frequently requires conferring with other experts, whether directly (as when asking the question) or indirectly (by consultation of expert answers in the future). Furthermore, unlike general reference questions (where the answer is simply sourced from existing references), there may be questions for which there are no existing published answers and an answer needs to be sourced from the expert community.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This type of question may, but will not necessarily, produce bad answers. Experts trained in the relevant area—here, reader's advisory—are capable of producing good, substantive, real answers to such questions. Poor answers may need prodding in the comments, incorporation into better answers, or flags for moderator attention, but questions like those referred to above should only be closed &lt;em&gt;a posteriori&lt;/em&gt;, not &lt;em&gt;a priori&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;given that the examples refer to questions requiring expert knowledge and/or objective points that need to be addressed by the answers, creating a reasonable possibility of producing a useful, long-term reference&lt;/strong&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="345" LastEditorUserId="345" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-06-05T23:05:12.960" LastActivityDate="2012-06-05T23:05:12.960" CommunityOwnedDate="2012-06-05T23:05:12.960" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="83" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="81" CreationDate="2012-06-05T02:33:13.057" Score="1" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;No, it's technically not about libraries (although it's very much a library question), the answer will necessarily be non-complete, and, being a list, there will in some sense not be a single answer.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="345" LastActivityDate="2012-06-05T02:33:13.057" CommunityOwnedDate="2012-06-05T02:33:13.057" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="84" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="81" CreationDate="2012-06-05T17:48:51.963" Score="6" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;No, this type of question is not appropriate at all. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is an expert-to-expert forum &amp;mdash; librarians and library professionals &amp;mdash; and not for end users. It's an academic and &quot;science of...&quot; site not targeted at those who &lt;em&gt;use&lt;/em&gt; libraries.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But &lt;strong&gt;in case I misunderstood&lt;/strong&gt; the purpose of your &quot;example,&quot; let me answer on another level &amp;mdash;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These &quot;big list&quot; questions aren't really a good fit for this type of Q&amp;amp;A. Inevitably, all semblance of &quot;expertise&quot; get thrown away as it becomes difficult to begrudge any of the participants their one-line answers because the question itself is so ridiculously open-ended that any answer is just as &quot;right&quot; as any other. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You should only &lt;strong&gt;ask practical, answerable questions based on actual problems that you face.&lt;/strong&gt; That's a pretty big ask &amp;mdash; We specifically forgo these types of &quot;generalized populous questions&quot; because chatty, open-ended questions diminish the usefulness of this site. It's a tough sell, but it's that practical, low-noise approach to Q&amp;amp;A that drives &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;experts&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; to these sites.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Don't throw that away so early in your development.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Closed as &quot;not constructive&quot;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;  This question is not a good fit to our Q&amp;amp;A format. We expect answers to generally involve facts, references, or specific expertise; this question will likely solicit opinion, debate, arguments, polling, or extended discussion.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Literature SE became a book-recommendation engine and is now among the &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.stackoverflow.com/2012/04/when-a-site-grows-quiet/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;sites that are no longer with us.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Yes, these questions may receive a lot of answers and become part of voting engine&amp;hellip; but the relative popularity of these &quot;poll&quot; questions is a &lt;strong&gt;fallacy.&lt;/strong&gt; It doesn't drive quality. What you are teaching your users is &quot;Why should I ask hard, intriguing questions when the &lt;em&gt;&quot;What's your favorite book?&quot;&lt;/em&gt; -mongers get all the 'reputation'?&quot; Don't do it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.stackoverflow.com/2011/01/real-questions-have-answers/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Real Questions Have Answers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="81" LastActivityDate="2012-06-05T17:48:51.963" CommentCount="12" />
  <row Id="85" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="70" CreationDate="2012-06-06T19:58:34.460" Score="0" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Perhaps only because I deal in antique data now, I think that &quot;private collection&quot; is a very different thing than &lt;em&gt;any&lt;/em&gt; kind of library, including home library.  However, this usage would be rather rare here.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="178" LastActivityDate="2012-06-06T19:58:34.460" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="86" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="95" CreationDate="2012-06-07T07:12:58.167" Score="0" ViewCount="19" Body="&lt;p&gt;So far we've got &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/professional-development&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'professional-development'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;professional-development&lt;/a&gt; x4 and &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/staff-development&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'staff-development'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;staff-development&lt;/a&gt;. We don't have anything using the term &quot;training.&quot; I'm not sure how we want to deal with this.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Are professionals and staff different people? Within the context of a library, I think we understand that this could mean librarians vs. non-librarian staff, although it doesn't have to. But are the &quot;development&quot; terms really so different?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Is &quot;staff development&quot; different from &quot;staff training&quot;?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Is there some librarians-and-staff &quot;training&quot; separate from &quot;staff training&quot; that we want to consider?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="345" LastEditorUserId="345" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-06-08T04:51:24.197" LastActivityDate="2012-06-08T04:51:24.197" Title="How should we deal with [professional-development], [staff-development], and similar training terms?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;tags&gt;&lt;tag-synonyms&gt;" AnswerCount="1" FavoriteCount="0" />
  <row Id="87" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-06-07T11:01:28.697" Score="6" ViewCount="62" Body="&lt;p&gt;Are the users of this site involved in the information industry, or will we be answering questions from those interested in organising their own collections but don't neccessarily know about library tools, terminology, etc?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Currently I think we have people from both aspects; which will affect what tags are used.&#xA;E.g. Professional development or Staff development might be used to differentiate from Training (for those who aren't in the Lib/Info Sci industry), or we could just use Training to encompass everyone.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="249" LastEditorUserId="345" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-06-07T18:50:16.840" LastActivityDate="2012-06-07T19:39:04.953" Title="Who are we directing the site towards?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;tags&gt;&lt;scope&gt;" AnswerCount="3" CommentCount="4" FavoriteCount="2" />
  <row Id="88" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="87" CreationDate="2012-06-07T11:52:06.183" Score="0" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;The FAQ says that this site is for &quot;librarians and library professionsals&quot;. I think we should discourage people from asking about organizing their own collections. Additionally, I think we should discourage people who aren't library professionsals and don't know basic library terminology. It will just bring down the quality of the site and bore the experts/professionsals. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I say this with evey fiber of my public librarianship screaming at me that it's not right to work to make it accessible to all. But I don't want to spend hours explaining every tiny detail (down to what call numbers are) of librarianship that people pick up from either education or working in a library. I appreciate their interest in the field but would say do some googling or volunteering first and then come back with some thoughtful questions. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="97" LastActivityDate="2012-06-07T11:52:06.183" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="89" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="87" CreationDate="2012-06-07T19:28:51.877" Score="2" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;This site is aimed at an &lt;em&gt;expert community&lt;/em&gt;. Those experts may or may not have degrees—my coworker who has published a best-selling ALA publication and is invited to give talks on it is nevertheless not a librarian because she doesn't have an MLIS—and they may be degreed professionals in other fields who answer questions where our interests overlap. (For example, a First Amendment lawyer who provides expert-level legal information on censorship questions.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As for which community that &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt;—i.e., what's on-topic—we have agreed that it is the &quot;Libraries and Information Science&quot; community. We deliberately changed it from library science to libraries because we wanted to expand beyond the science of it to all exerts in any aspect of libraries. We likewise rejected the idea of restricting it to merely library management. More importantly to me, we acknowledged that the information science community vastly overlaps with the library science community to the point at which it was best to include them on our proposal, so information scientists who are &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; librarians and are &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; asking &quot;library questions&quot; are also welcome.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is not a site for non-experts asking for explanations of basic concepts. However, this is a site for subject-matter experts who are not experts at teaching or explaining things asking other subject-matter experts how to teach or explain their subject of mutual interest. If a non-expert gets here from Google and finds the answer useful, that's nice, but they don't have to be involved in either asking or attempting to answer any such question. We shouldn't be deliberately obfuscating our questions or answers or, even worse, not asking the questions we need answered just to prevent outsiders from reading them.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By the same token, this is not a site for explaining to people who just bought their first book how to put it on a shelf. On the other hand, I personally know people with home libraries—frequently professional libraries—with thousands of items and a surprisingly high circulation rate. At some point the line between those people and people running a small public library has gotten blurred in certain respects, which is why you'll find questions tagged both [home-libraries] and [small-libraries]. We shouldn't be answering &quot;newbie&quot; questions, as stated above, but the fact that they're working with a non-public, non-school, non-college, non-university, non-corporate, non-subscription library does not mean that they aren't working with a library at all and can't have expert questions . . . especially when they're librarians who happen to have a massive personal library.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="345" LastActivityDate="2012-06-07T19:28:51.877" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="90" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="87" CreationDate="2012-06-07T19:39:04.953" Score="2" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Speaking as a moderator and user of another StackExchange site focused on &lt;em&gt;professionals&lt;/em&gt;, I can say that directing a site towards those professionals can work and work well. Public forums on professional topics tend to get drowned in interested amateurs, which means that such forums end up with big walls around them or outright hostile cultures. Building a culture of accessibility to professionals and keeping the signal to noise ratio within acceptable limits goes a very long way towards the creation of a thriving community.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;ServerFault has drawn a very clear line in the FAQ and elsewhere that &lt;em&gt;in the home&lt;/em&gt; is explicitly off topic with rare exceptions. Such a policy would also work here, I believe. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As a caveat to that, we've had several users with rather complex home installations (a lot of sysadmins have home labs more complex than some small office networks) ask very intelligent questions and it was only late into the process that it was revealed that this was a home lab not a workplace thing. It all depends on how the questions are asked, and whether or not they pass the smell test of expert/professional. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It does take vigilance though. A willingness to close/hammer questions that clearly don't fit the scope of the site (something sysadmins have, er, no problem with) needs to be developed as well. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="462" LastActivityDate="2012-06-07T19:39:04.953" CommentCount="6" />
  <row Id="91" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="67" CreationDate="2012-06-07T19:59:06.067" Score="3" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Since the questions have been retagged, &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/interlibrary&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'interlibrary'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;interlibrary&lt;/a&gt; doesn't exist anymore. If someone goes to type it in when posting a question, &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/interlibrary-loan&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'interlibrary-loan'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;interlibrary-loan&lt;/a&gt; will come up as a suggestion, so I think the odds of it reoccurring are relatively small.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In order for me to create a synonym, I'd have to recreate the tag, which seems a little silly at this point. :)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If it does come up again, we'll revisit setting up a synonym.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="26" LastActivityDate="2012-06-07T19:59:06.067" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="92" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="64" CreationDate="2012-06-07T20:03:08.900" Score="1" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I merged &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/archive&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'archive'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;archive&lt;/a&gt; into &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/archives&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'archives'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;archives&lt;/a&gt; and set up a synonym, so future attempts to use &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/archive&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'archive'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;archive&lt;/a&gt; will be automatically converted to the plural form.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="26" LastActivityDate="2012-06-07T20:03:08.900" />
  <row Id="93" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="50" CreationDate="2012-06-07T20:41:03.533" Score="4" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;There is overlap in the Venn diagram between libraries and digital preservation but there are a lot of people working in digital preservation who are not involved with libraries at all. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Science data managers&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Professional photographers (&lt;a href=&quot;http://photo.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/digital-preservation&quot;&gt;there are digital preservation questions on the Photo SE&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Folks in various entertainment media industries (music, film) &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Museum professionals (&lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/14/are-questions-about-archives-on-topic-and-should-they-be-solicited-somehow&quot;&gt;which it sounds like people don't think fits here&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Computer scientists and engineers working on storage media.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Folks working on digital media for news organizations&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Anyone involved in Digital Asset Management&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is to say that there are a lot of people who work on digital preservation that do not think what they do has anything to do with libraries. While &quot;information science&quot; was appended to the libraries SE title, in practice, the title seems to suggest that this space is about things that happen in libraries and things that people with MILS degrees do. (In the broadest sense it would seem like &quot;information science&quot; could be a catch all category for a lot of different stack exchange sites.) &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="65" LastActivityDate="2012-06-07T20:41:03.533" CommentCount="4" />
  <row Id="94" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="64" CreationDate="2012-06-07T21:13:30.970" Score="1" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;'Archive' is a potentially problematic term as it might be a few things:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;a noun, referring to a place where things are stored&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;a noun, referring to the organization that stores things&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;a verb, referring to the process of storing things&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I'd personally be inclined to add both 'archives' and 'archiving', as there are aspects of archiving that happen in locations other than formal archives ... but we'd have to see how it gets used first.  Looking at those that are currently flagged as 'archives', &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/209/&quot;&gt;only one&lt;/a&gt; stands out as it's &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; not about the topic of archives.  Those looking for an archive of a specific type of content may not be either.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="62" LastActivityDate="2012-06-07T21:13:30.970" />
  <row Id="95" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="86" CreationDate="2012-06-08T00:01:23.737" Score="1" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I like the use of 'professional development' since it is related to obtaining new skills regardless of current circumstances such as retirement or being employed in another field.  It can encompass development at either group (staff) or individual level and should relate to &quot;acquiring of skills in the information industry&quot;.  (Or whatever broader term we can agree our various occupations fit under.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="249" LastActivityDate="2012-06-08T00:01:23.737" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="96" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="100" CreationDate="2012-06-08T04:49:37.240" Score="2" ViewCount="24" Body="&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/research&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'research'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;research&lt;/a&gt; tag appears to have several different question topics its being used for, and I can't think of an obvious definition that would allow us to declare some usage right and some wrong. So: ignore / retag / delete?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="345" LastActivityDate="2012-06-08T19:48:31.107" Title="[research]: What should be done?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;tags&gt;&lt;tag-synonyms&gt;&lt;retagging&gt;" AnswerCount="1" FavoriteCount="0" />
  <row Id="97" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-06-08T12:08:20.657" Score="6" ViewCount="80" Body="&lt;p&gt;It has been asked about &#xA;&lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/87/who-are-we-directing-the-site-towards/90&quot;&gt;Who are we directing the site towards?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In that discussion came the topic of ways to set the scope in the FAQ to discourage the interested amateurs we're (potentially) not interested in serving.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But first, some background. I'm a moderator and high rep user of ServerFault, one of StackExchange's other for-professional sites. We have quite a bit of experience in building a community for people-who-get-paid-for-this. We have learned that one of the better ways to handle this is to have a well-phrased 'NOT about' section in the &lt;a href=&quot;http://serverfault.com/faq&quot;&gt;FAQ&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If LIS wants to be a site aimed at professionals or subject-matter experts, I believe we should find some language to go into the FAQ.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The ServerFault NOT About section reads:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;and it is &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; about…&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Anything in a home setting&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Product, service, or learning material recommendations&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Career, salary, personnel, employment, or formal education&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Licensing, legal advice, and circumvention of security or policy&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Unauthorized hacking, password cracking, or system misuse&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The first bullet-point is the work-horse. We've found that by scoping ServerFault as &lt;em&gt;in the workplace&lt;/em&gt; we effectively exclude a lot of the interested amateurs. This is why it is bolded and the first point.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The second bullet-point is intended to do two things. First, discourage a certain kind of subjective question that can't be answered, and Second, discourage a type of question that attracts a lot of spam.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The third bullet-point is there because there is very little formalized education in the Systems Administration space, and what there is tends to be offered by vendors and is highly domain-specific. Indeed, it is &lt;em&gt;Too Localized&lt;/em&gt;. I don't expect this to be a problem for LIS, as there are degree programs for it. However, career advice may still be too-subjective.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The other two points are specific to our subject matter and are the kind of too-localized or outright dangerous question we want to discourage. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What kind of verbiage could we put into the LIS FAQ to discourage interested amateurs? &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.libraries.stackexchange.com/a/90/462&quot;&gt;From the discussion we had&lt;/a&gt;, it sounds like &lt;em&gt;in the home&lt;/em&gt; is not a viable limiter for LIS, so we need to come up with something.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We also need to figure out what, if anything, we plan on doing with career-advice type questions. These typically come from people just breaking into the field, and people looking to change career &lt;em&gt;paths&lt;/em&gt;. Of the two, the former are far more common and in ServerFault's case is predominantly students fresh out of college looking for the &lt;em&gt;best&lt;/em&gt; path to take to the career of their dreams; the rest are usually entry-level positions looking to advance. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="462" LastActivityDate="2012-06-10T14:29:00.097" Title="Setting the scope for the site: Professional/Expert" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;scope&gt;" AnswerCount="3" CommentCount="2" FavoriteCount="2" />
  <row Id="98" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="97" CreationDate="2012-06-08T13:34:53.277" Score="3" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Discussing education in the LIS world is a hot button topic. I think it would be better off not discussed on this site. The reason I say this is because anytime someone says &quot;You NEED an MLIS to work in the field&quot;, five more people come back saying either 1. &quot;I don't have one and I am the director/head librarian/whatever&quot; or 2. &quot;I work for people who don't have their degree.&quot; (The second being my situation.) In many cases, experience is valued just as equally as education.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Choosing to get your MLIS should be a personal decision because it is possible to move up in the library world without one -- maybe a little bit harder and a little longer road -- but there are tons of examples out there of successful professionals without their MLIS. It is a lot of debt and there aren't a ton of full-time, professional level job prospects out there. This is especially true of those who are switching careers and don't have the freedom to move to where there are jobs. The ALA has been telling us for a decade now that there is a &quot;graying of the profession&quot; and a &quot;mass retirement&quot; is just on the horizon but this is simply not happening due to the way the economy is these days.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="97" LastActivityDate="2012-06-08T13:34:53.277" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="99" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="97" CreationDate="2012-06-08T19:35:23.313" Score="1" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Okay, I tried typing this part once, stopped partway through, and came to a realization:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Advice is not an answer.&lt;/strong&gt; That is, it's unlikely to be a &lt;em&gt;concrete, factual&lt;/em&gt; answer that is &lt;em&gt;identifiably correct&lt;/em&gt;, and anything that you think of as &quot;advice&quot; is probably directed at an individual's problem rather than a generalized problem and the question is therefore &lt;em&gt;too local&lt;/em&gt; to boot. If experts ask questions about such problems in general and answer those questions with factual information, that's okay, but this must be distinguished from non-experts begging for personal advice.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I feel like there should be a &quot;Thin Ice&quot; or &quot;Danger Zone&quot; or &quot;Caution/Warning Area&quot; or something that notes that&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;While all questions should be asked by experts and express generalizable, expert concerns, the following topics are less inherently expert concerns, are less likely to have a single identifiably-correct answer, and will therefore receive heightened scrutiny:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/home-libraries&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'home-libraries'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;home-libraries&lt;/a&gt;: Optimally, these are questions also generalizable to other &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/small-libraries&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'small-libraries'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;small-libraries&lt;/a&gt;, whether public or private. Questions that are non-expert or too idiosyncratic will be closed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/profession&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'profession'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;profession&lt;/a&gt;: This is a site for current experts, not future experts; anyone wanting advice on getting into the profession should speak to their local professionals for personalized advice. (&lt;em&gt;Advice is not an answer.&lt;/em&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="345" LastEditorUserId="345" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-06-08T19:52:22.387" LastActivityDate="2012-06-08T19:52:22.387" CommunityOwnedDate="2012-06-08T19:35:23.313" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="100" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="96" CreationDate="2012-06-08T19:48:31.107" Score="5" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I'd say there's at least two concepts there :&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;research-support&lt;/strong&gt; :  libraries supporting people doing research&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LIS-research&lt;/strong&gt; : doing research about libraries &amp;amp; LIS.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="62" LastActivityDate="2012-06-08T19:48:31.107" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="101" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-06-09T01:38:11.280" Score="3" ViewCount="50" Body="&lt;p&gt;There are currently three tags involving Youth:&#xA;- Youth services&#xA;- Young adult&#xA;- Young people.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Do we need all three?  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Youth services covers what library (or other information industry) services are provided to this demographic.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Young people could combine all age groups from 5-16 years of age, but I wonder if this is needed.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Young adult is the demographic.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Are questions going to be about the service aspect, or are this there a need to add in the demographic for each age group/range?  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="249" LastEditorUserId="249" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-06-11T04:09:40.477" LastActivityDate="2012-06-11T04:09:40.477" Title="Do we need [youth-services], [young-adult] and [young-people]?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;tags&gt;&lt;youth-services&gt;" AnswerCount="3" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="102" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="101" CreationDate="2012-06-09T01:38:11.607" Score="0" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I think we should make 'young people' a synonym for 'young adult' regardless.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="249" LastActivityDate="2012-06-09T01:38:11.607" CommentCount="4" />
  <row Id="103" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="101" CreationDate="2012-06-09T14:50:41.273" Score="2" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I dont think we need three different tags  Young adult tends to refer to a specific category of book and youth services would refer to services for that particular age group, I suppose, but young people seems to be a superfluous tag.  There is no real need for it to exist.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="22" LastActivityDate="2012-06-09T14:50:41.273" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="104" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="97" CreationDate="2012-06-10T14:29:00.097" Score="1" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Sure there is no strict line, but discouraging questions about home libraries looks like a good policy. If you manage a collection of documents for your own use, the result may also be a library, but the practice is not providing library services but &lt;strong&gt;personal knowledge management&lt;/strong&gt;. Note that some libraries provide courses in personal knowledge management for their patrons, questions about this services may be on-topic. But if there are no &lt;strong&gt;patrons&lt;/strong&gt; involved, a question is surely off-topic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="109" LastActivityDate="2012-06-10T14:29:00.097" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="105" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="101" CreationDate="2012-06-10T16:38:19.517" Score="1" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/young-people&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'young-people'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;young-people&lt;/a&gt; question was about something that falls into the YA range and is specifically a youth services operation. One of the two &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/young-adult&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'young-adult'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;young-adult&lt;/a&gt; questions appears to have nothing to do with young adults, which is odd, and the other could just as easily be filed under &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/youth-services&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'youth-services'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;youth-services&lt;/a&gt;. I haven't reviewed all of &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/youth-services&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'youth-services'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;youth-services&lt;/a&gt; yet, but it's clearly a large and appropriate tag.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I suggest:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;retagging the &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/young-people&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'young-people'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;young-people&lt;/a&gt; question, which will delete the tag from the database,&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;allowing &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/young-adult&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'young-adult'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;young-adult&lt;/a&gt; to exist along with other age group markers within the broad umbrella of &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/youth-services&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'youth-services'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;youth-services&lt;/a&gt;, and&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;using the tag wiki to explain usage.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="345" LastActivityDate="2012-06-10T16:38:19.517" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="106" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="43" CreationDate="2012-06-12T14:03:00.733" Score="5" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Since there seems to be a lack of desire for moderators, I would volunteer to be a temportary moderator while the site is getting off of the ground. While I have very litte personal experience with librarianship or library science, my fiancee (@KatieR), has been very active here. &lt;a href=&quot;http://serverfault.com/users/10472/mdmarra&quot;&gt;I am 25k+ on ServerFault&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://superuser.com/users/2855/mdmarra&quot;&gt;13k+ on SuperUser&lt;/a&gt; as well as having &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.stackoverflow.com/users/143112/mdmarra&quot;&gt;1.6k on mSO&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On ServerFault, I have &lt;a href=&quot;http://serverfault.com/users/10472/mdmarra?tab=badges&quot;&gt;lots of badges&lt;/a&gt;. Some of the ones that point to good community involvement include: &lt;a href=&quot;http://serverfault.com/badges/75/electorate&quot;&gt;Electorate&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://serverfault.com/badges/198/constituent?userid=10472&quot;&gt;Constituent&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://serverfault.com/badges/168/reviewer&quot;&gt;Reviewer&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://serverfault.com/badges/12/strunk-white&quot;&gt;Strunk &amp;amp; White&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;http://serverfault.com/badges/90/announcer&quot;&gt;Announcer&lt;/a&gt;. I was the first on the site to get Reviewer, which is given for using the 10k tools to review and act on a certain number of posts deemed in need of review by the system.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Even though I'm not a library professional, I have a firm understanding of how the Stack Exchange networks work. I do &lt;strong&gt;not&lt;/strong&gt; think that I would want to be a long-term moderator, but I would love to be a pro-tem mod during the formation of this community. I think that it could be very useful, but will also need a lot of pruning, because of the subjective nature of librarianship. This site will need good leadership during beta to keep it on-topic and relevant and I think that I can help with that!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="104" LastEditorUserId="104" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-06-12T14:32:50.603" LastActivityDate="2012-06-12T14:32:50.603" CommunityOwnedDate="2012-06-12T14:03:00.733" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="107" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="43" CreationDate="2012-06-12T16:03:20.073" Score="5" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;As we have a need for pro-tem moderators, I'll volunteer, but with a restriction that I can only do this short term -- I won't be able to devote much time to it once we hit mid-november or so, due to my busy winter/spring conference schedule.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So, qualifications :&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;I have experience in moderating Stack Exchange sites as &lt;a href=&quot;http://cooking.stackexchange.com/users/67/joe&quot;&gt;I was a pro-tem moderator&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&quot;http://cooking.stackexchange.com/&quot;&gt;Seasoned Advice (aka. Cooking.SE)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;I'm an active member of a library Friends group, overseeing our branch's book sale.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;I'm an active member of &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.asis.org/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;ASIS&amp;amp;T&lt;/a&gt;, having helped to organize the last two &lt;a href=&quot;http://rdap12.posterous.com/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;RDAP&lt;/a&gt; summits.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;I'm a member of ALA (LITA / ACRL / ALTAFF), but not active (never been to any of their meetings)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;I pseudo-lurk (failed lurking?) on the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.code4lib.org/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;code4lib&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://dewey.library.nd.edu/mailing-lists/ngc4lib/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;ngc4lib&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://pam.sla.org/manual/pamnet-information/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;PAMNET&lt;/a&gt; mailing lists&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As for library cred ... I was the one who added categorization to Fark.com.  (and then left after a falling out when Drew insisted on adding one then misusing it (weird == related to the paranormal; we already had strange) and then went and added a synonym (except for 'weird', all of the categories had a strong 'S' sound, but someone didn't like 'spiffy', so 'cool' was added, screwing up my color scheme).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I also had proposed to try to get the Cooking.SE group to work on a multilingual (multi-dialect?) thesaurus for cooking terms, but &lt;a href=&quot;http://cooking.stackexchange.com/questions/784/translating-cooking-terms-between-us-uk-au-ca-nz&quot;&gt;started a community wiki&lt;/a&gt; before the SE staff started blindly closing stuff that didn't fit into the StackExchange Q/A norm.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="62" LastActivityDate="2012-06-12T16:03:20.073" CommunityOwnedDate="2012-06-12T16:03:20.073" />
  <row Id="108" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="45" CreationDate="2012-06-14T08:05:33.177" Score="1" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Just briefly present LibStEx at meetings in your organization, among colleagues, at workshops and at conferences. Mouth-to-mouth is still underestimated among us, used to do digital-to-digital communication so much.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="109" LastActivityDate="2012-06-14T08:05:33.177" />
  <row Id="109" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="45" CreationDate="2012-06-15T03:44:30.773" Score="2" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Few things you can do (some stuff taken from my post &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.chemistry.stackexchange.com/questions/147/what-can-i-do-for-this-site&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;):&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Create a community promotion ad and post on a graduated site. Maybe on &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.english.stackexchange.com/questions/2223/community-promotion-ads-2012&quot;&gt;English&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.english.stackexchange.com/a/2296/17952&quot;&gt;They already have one for Lit.SE, but that may be removed since the site was closed&lt;/a&gt;). &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.mathematica.stackexchange.com/questions/160/what-would-be-a-good-community-promotion-ad&quot;&gt;Mathematica.SE&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.chemistry.stackexchange.com/a/140/22&quot;&gt;chem.SE&lt;/a&gt; have done so on Physics.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Create an A4(or whatever) poster for your users to print out and stick somewhere. &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.chemistry.stackexchange.com/a/134/22&quot;&gt;We did that on chem&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Write an awesome blog post, like &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.thickbook.com/2012/02/dear-stackexchange-will-you-be-my-valentine/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;this one by a TW mod&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Encourage colleagues/classmates/friends(who have a background in the site topic) to join. Tell them how awesome we are!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Try to get more experts engaged. Remember, the more experts you have, the better the site is (we don't want to degrade into Yahoo! Answers)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Retweet the upvoted questions posted by &lt;a href=&quot;http://twitter.com/#!/StackLibraries&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;@StackLibraries&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="258" LastActivityDate="2012-06-15T03:44:30.773" />
  <row Id="110" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-06-21T17:26:35.723" Score="1" ViewCount="49" Body="&lt;p&gt;It seems that we have a tag for &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/book-recommendations&quot;&gt;book-recommendations&lt;/a&gt;, the first use of which was more about building such a service, than actually asking for a recommendation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/802/books-on-human-condition-philosophy&quot;&gt;second use is asking for specific recommendations&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the definition phase of the site, the third highest ranked question was &lt;a href=&quot;http://area51.stackexchange.com/proposals/12432/libraries-information-science/13319#13319&quot;&gt;fairly similar&lt;/a&gt;, as it's looking for books that match a given requirement, but may be more objective as it isn't asking if they're necessarily any good.  It doesn't meet that 'only one right answer' that the folks running Stack Exchange seem to have convinced themselves are the only good type of questions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Where should we draw the line on this class of questions?  If these questions aren't acceptable, are there ways to ask a question to get a useful answer that would be acceptable?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Update:&lt;/b&gt;  I would assume that it'd be okay to ask if there exist recommended reading lists for a given topic for an age group or skill level.  I'd say it's on topic, and I'm guessing others would do it you tagged it 'collection-development' instead of 'book-recommendations'.  It's not really that different of a topic, and it again runs the risk of having more than one correct answer ... but I personally think it would be the sort of thing that we'd want on here.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="62" LastEditorUserId="62" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-07-06T14:41:07.210" LastActivityDate="2012-07-06T14:41:07.210" Title="Policy on 'Book Recommendations'?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="4" />
  <row Id="111" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-06-21T17:32:05.917" Score="2" ViewCount="86" Body="&lt;p&gt;I have noticed that there are &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/793/what-do-academic-university-libraries-do-with-back-issues-of-journals&quot;&gt;a couple of&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/761/if-your-library-requires-patrons-to-have-a-library-card-to-use-the-computers-do&quot;&gt;questions appearing&lt;/a&gt; where people are essentially asking for lists of answers regarding what &quot;your library&quot; does in a particular situation. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These questions are somewhat problematic because there is no real answer to them - they are just going to be endless discussion style responses because there is no way to pick a true answer - you can't say that Library X does it better than Library Y, essentially, because of how the question has been asked. There is no way to select one answer as being the one true right answer, because they are all equally valid. They all respond to the question of &quot;what does your library do&quot;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These questions are more suited for the realm of discussion and forums, which &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.stackoverflow.com/questions/92107/is-stack-overflow-a-forum/92115#92115&quot;&gt;Stack Exchange is not&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I understand that we, as professionals in the Library and Information Science field, have a great interest in knowing how other groups do things, especially when formulating new policies in your own institution. Problem is, while sharing ideas and such is a great thing to do, it is not a really good fit for Stack Exchange.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What can we do to make these questions more on-topic, following the SE model? Can we do anything? Or should they just be closed?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="22" LastActivityDate="2012-07-23T17:09:25.300" Title="Is 'What does your library do?&quot; an appropriate sort of question here?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;scope&gt;" AnswerCount="3" CommentCount="1" FavoriteCount="1" />
  <row Id="112" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="111" CreationDate="2012-06-21T19:34:02.410" Score="0" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;So here's the fallacy of the 'only one right answer' type question.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There's always more than one way to do things.  The 'correct' answer that gets marked in Stack Exchange isn't necessarily the one that best answers the question (as a better answer might be given after another answer has been marked as correct)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So, what we're really asking is, 'does anyone else have a workable solution to this problem?' or 'what are my options for dealing with this situation?', and then choosing the one that you believe best fits your circumstances (which may or may not be reflected in the question asked).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I've had times when I've marked a question as correct, as it looked correct on the surface, but it was more pseudocode, and was missing the outer calling structure ... and when I actually got the necessary bits to run it I found my performance went from 10k operations per second to 1 per second.  Had I been more skilled in Postgres, I might not've marked the answer as correct, and left it open in hopes of more answers that might've solved the problem.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So, my answer : &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;These answers should not be closed&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The 'SE model' is based on incorrect assumptions that will never be met.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;It might be possible to reword the questions based on what I think is being implied (above) to make it 'more acceptable', but it still won't really fit.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;If people think the question is overly broad, they can post comments asking for relevant clarifications to narrow the question down.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;(and if the Stack Exchange people think I'm off base on the no correct answer thing, go and take a look at the most recent questions on Stack Overflow -- every 'how can I get this to work?' or 'how can I do (x)?' question fits, the only difference is with software, we can verify it's an acceptable answer with a quick compile &amp;amp; test)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="62" LastActivityDate="2012-06-21T19:34:02.410" CommentCount="5" />
  <row Id="113" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="111" CreationDate="2012-06-23T06:02:21.317" Score="0" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;There's a very fine line to be drawn between questions where that's an okay thing to include and questions where that's not. This is essentially the same line as the one between good, constructive, subjective questions and bad, non-constructive, subjective questions. For example, from &quot;&lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.stackoverflow.com/2011/01/real-questions-have-answers/&quot;&gt;Real Questions Have Answers&lt;/a&gt;&quot;:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Constructive subjective questions:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;ol&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;inspire answers that explain “why” and “how”.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;tend to have long, not short, answers.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;have a constructive, fair, and impartial tone.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;invite sharing experiences over opinions.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;insist that opinion be backed up with facts and references.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;are more than just mindless social fun.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So, if a subjective question is best answered with experience, with explanation of why and how that experience was superior, and with facts and references backing up its backs up its claims of superiority, then, yes, &quot;If you've had success with this, how did you do it?&quot; and related guiding questions can be a useful part of a good, constructive, subjective question.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, it's a bad, non-constructive, subjective question if the question does not ask for a how or a why or facts or references or just lack the right tone or it fits these other points from Real Questions Have Answers:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;To prevent your question from being flagged and possibly removed, avoid asking subjective questions where …&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;every answer is equally valid: “What’s your favorite &lt;strong&gt;__&lt;/strong&gt;?”&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;your answer is provided along with the question, and you expect more answers: “I use &lt;strong&gt;_&lt;em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; for &lt;strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;_&lt;/strong&gt;, what do you use?”&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I fully agree with you that there is a category of non-constructive poll questions that need to be reformed or closed/deleted. However, I wouldn't be too hasty here, not just because not all questions that use &quot;you&quot; or &quot;your&quot; are going to be such questions but because we're dealing with a discipline that has some highly subjective areas in it and &quot;How we done it good&quot; is actually considered a perfectly valid type of formal article because &lt;strong&gt;there is no other way of answering some questions in this discipline.&lt;/strong&gt; If SE wants to be a collection of expert answers to canonical questions, well, this is what those things look like sometimes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="345" LastActivityDate="2012-06-23T06:02:21.317" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="114" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="110" CreationDate="2012-06-24T11:28:27.747" Score="3" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;The tag 'book recommendations' definitely implies that a specific book or group of books meets an individual need, e.g. a book about divorced dad who own a goat.  They are questions that are probably unique enough for another site to be created, and would attract a lot of bibliophiles whose interest is in specific content.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;How books can be selected to meet a certain audience falls into the 'collection development' arena.  I think that the phrasing has to be right however, and it is the focus on the library users - rather than just a reference question for a single person - that will separate these two issues.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="249" LastActivityDate="2012-06-24T11:28:27.747" />
  <row Id="115" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="110" CreationDate="2012-06-25T09:06:15.053" Score="0" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Given prior discussion here (http://meta.libraries.stackexchange.com/a/84/345) and the fate of Literature.SE, I'm going to have to go on record as supporting the consensus (however much I disagree with it) that providing professional Reader's Advisory is off-limits and general book recommendations even more so. Per the question and Deborah Mould's answer, however, collection development questions are valid but subject to a different tag.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We do need a &quot;head&quot; question type to draw people in for our &quot;long tail,&quot; but this isn't it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="345" LastActivityDate="2012-06-25T09:06:15.053" />
  <row Id="116" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-06-25T09:30:06.170" Score="-4" ViewCount="67" Body="&lt;p&gt;These are questions seeking authoritative identifying information (title &amp;amp; author) for a specific item for which the questioner can only provide a description of some sort. They:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Have one and only one correct answer and can be closed if they do not produce sufficient information to determine it.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Are real questions with actual answers that librarians face on a daily basis.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Usually require a large body of experts to answer.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Will match book titles and authors to reasonable descriptions of them for future reference (e.g., when drawing people looking for the same book off Google).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Were very popular on Unshelved Answers and may serve as the &quot;head&quot; necessary to draw in an audience to a &quot;long tail&quot; site such as this one.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I should note that on Unshelved Answers, it was virtually always the case that the questioner had been searching for the answer for years, the community only once failed to find the correct answer within a week, and other users frequently commented that they had harbored the same question or otherwise found the Q&amp;amp;A useful.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A question of this sort received the requisite 5 up-votes during the definition phase of this site (http://area51.stackexchange.com/proposals/12432/libraries-information-science/13474#13474) and another only 4 (http://area51.stackexchange.com/proposals/12432/libraries-information-science/13321#13321), but both received comments noting how interested the users would be in seeing such questions here.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I think that this is a perfectly factual, non-list, popular question type with a non-zero future reference potential that would serve both the &quot;head&quot; and the &quot;long tail&quot; of a long-tail model site such as this one.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="345" LastActivityDate="2012-06-27T15:46:50.427" Title="Are &quot;Name That Book&quot; questions on-topic?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;scope&gt;" AnswerCount="3" FavoriteCount="1" />
  <row Id="117" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="116" CreationDate="2012-06-26T01:06:01.503" Score="1" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I'm torn on this for two reasons ...&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;If we're catering to the 'I've been looking for this book for years' type situation, I think it's a very valuable service for this community.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have a feeling that we're going to end up being the reference desk for lazy people who don't know how to do research.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So, I'd propose that if it were acceptable, that there be some sort of bar that's set ... maybe some template to fill out w/ what they know of the book (with the hope that as they're filling it out, it'd give them sufficient clues to find it on their own, leaving only the truly chalenging ones ... and help to weed out the people who are not only lazing in searching themselves, but also in filling out some form or whatever barrier to ask the question is set)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Perhaps first we need to make an FAQ-type page, going over basic search strategies &amp;amp; tricks for locate books (like using google image search to &lt;a href=&quot;http://searchresearch1.blogspot.com/2011/05/answer-how-can-you-find-book-by-its.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;find books by color&lt;/a&gt;)  If we're going to have to do a reference interview for each one of these, it's going to get very tiring, very quickly.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="62" LastActivityDate="2012-06-26T01:06:01.503" />
  <row Id="118" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="116" CreationDate="2012-06-26T15:42:56.523" Score="2" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;This Stack Exchange is for professionals to ask questions about the profession, not a reference desk. We even start allowing any kind of &quot;Name That Book&quot; question and it'll snowball. I say we stop it before it begins and not allow it at all.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="97" LastActivityDate="2012-06-26T15:42:56.523" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="119" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-06-27T02:33:18.177" Score="1" ViewCount="19" Body="&lt;p&gt;We've got a bit of a tag pileup happening around research data. Last I checked, we've got&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;research-data&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;data-management&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;data-curation&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;research-support&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Synonyms, tag deletions, preferred term?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="60" LastActivityDate="2012-06-27T10:35:11.990" Title="Research data tag pileup" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;tag-synonyms&gt;" AnswerCount="1" />
  <row Id="120" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="119" CreationDate="2012-06-27T10:35:11.990" Score="1" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;No synonyms. &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/research-data&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'research-data'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;research-data&lt;/a&gt; is better related to data as collected digital objects. &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/data-management&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'data-management'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;data-management&lt;/a&gt; is too general and should be avoided. &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/data-curation&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'data-curation'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;data-curation&lt;/a&gt; sounds more like long term archiving. &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/research-support&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'research-support'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;research-support&lt;/a&gt; is also broader than support of research via dealing with research data.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="109" LastActivityDate="2012-06-27T10:35:11.990" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="121" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-06-27T12:24:02.043" Score="3" ViewCount="43" Body="&lt;p&gt;Has libraries.stackexchange been actively promoted at the recent ALA conference or have we lost a good opportunity to &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/45/how-do-we-spread-the-word-about-our-awesome-site&quot;&gt;spread the word&lt;/a&gt; The &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ala.org/conferencesevents/upcoming&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;next ALA meeting&lt;/a&gt; is in January but sure there are other meetings as well. We don't have flyer or something like that, do we? There are &lt;a href=&quot;https://encrypted.google.com/search?q=libraries+stackexchange&amp;amp;tbm=blg&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;some blog articles&lt;/a&gt; but no announcements in journals and newsletters, are there?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="109" LastActivityDate="2012-09-14T18:37:57.677" Title="How has this site been promoted at ALA conference or other meetings?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;site-promotion&gt;" AnswerCount="2" />
  <row Id="122" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="116" CreationDate="2012-06-27T15:46:50.427" Score="2" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;There are various places on the internet where they specifically do ONLY things like this - The &quot;What Was That Book&quot; community on Livejournal, Whatisthatbook.com, etc. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I don't think that they are a good fit for Libraries Stack Exchange, because a) the OP is the only person who knows if the answer is right, so upvoting and downvoting isn't useful whatsoever, b) It is relatively unlikely that someone else is going to be looking for the same book based on the same bits of it that they remember, and c) it is not really anything based on the profession - these are questions that anyone has, and other than the fact that they are about books, they aren't really useful.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One of the many reasons that Literature Stack Exchange failed was that a lot of its questions were just &quot;What was that book&quot; sorts of questions, which made for a very poor site. Also, Gaming recently finished deciding that &quot;Identify this Game&quot; questions also did not bring much in terms of long-term benefit to the site. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I really don't want to see Libraries go the way of Literature. I want this site to grow and blossom and be ten kinds of awesome, and if we get stuck on questions like &quot;What was that book&quot;, I suspect we will drown in them before we get our feet underneath us. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="22" LastActivityDate="2012-06-27T15:46:50.427" CommentCount="6" />
  <row Id="123" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="121" CreationDate="2012-06-27T15:53:59.577" Score="2" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I suspect nothing has really been done yet because we are a relatively new and shiny site. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you want to get the word out (which is totally awesome!) feel free to do so! Write to the people who put announcements and stuff in journals and newsletters! Make Libraries.SE sound as awesome and useful as we all know it can be, and get the word out.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It is probably going to be a while before word gets out on its own, since we haven't been around that long. But if we all work to get the word out in our own ways (within our own communities, or wider, whatever you can do is awesome), then eventually, it will (hopefully) begin to snowball on its own.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We don't have a flyer or anything pre-made, but as long as you follow the guidelines &lt;a href=&quot;http://stackexchange.com/legal/trademark-guidance&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; in regards to trademarks and the like, there is no reason why you can't make your own. If you do, please share it on meta - that way others can share in helping make the flyers (and anything else you come up with) represent Libraries in the most awesome way possible.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="22" LastActivityDate="2012-06-27T15:53:59.577" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="124" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-06-29T18:50:45.713" Score="2" ViewCount="30" Body="&lt;p&gt;Just to frame this question a bit: I'm a software developer who recently started working in a university library and I have a lot of questions regarding the regular workflows in a library. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now I image a lot of this questions would be &lt;em&gt;(very) subjective&lt;/em&gt;, for example:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;What is your most used feature, when working with metadata in an ILS?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;What feature you miss most from your ILS, when working with metadata?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;What innovative library websites do you know, and what feature do you find well executed there?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Free bibliographic metadata sources (links, sites)?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;and so on. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Questions 1. and 2. would help me to get a picture of typical requirements, especially concerning metadata. I talk about that with my colleagues, but to hear more &lt;em&gt;opinions&lt;/em&gt; would be great.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Question 3. looks too broad to me, although I admit, I'd love to get answers from library professionals (as opposed to say visitors or software developers).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Question 4. could maybe the most on topic. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Would the questions above be suitable for this site?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="545" LastActivityDate="2012-06-30T12:43:07.647" Title="Are questions like &quot;What is your most used feature in an ILS&quot; on-topic?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" AnswerCount="1" />
  <row Id="125" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="124" CreationDate="2012-06-30T12:43:07.647" Score="1" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;The way first two are worded is way too subjective.  I would suggest talking directly to the librarians you are working with. You'll get a better idea of their specific needs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One way to worst could be &quot;In a university library setting, what is an effective method of seeking out metadata?&quot; or &quot;are there any known and proven methods of seeking out metadata using [insert ILS] here?&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Question four is simply a list question and those are also off topic in the SE world. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="97" LastActivityDate="2012-06-30T12:43:07.647" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="126" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-07-05T20:14:19.200" Score="0" ViewCount="22" Body="&lt;p&gt;A long time ago, there was a discussion on Cooking.SE about what were called '&lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.cooking.stackexchange.com/questions/434/please-zap-the-meta-tags-and-dependent-tags&quot;&gt;meta-tags&lt;/a&gt;'.  Basically, those tags which mean absolutely &lt;em&gt;nothing&lt;/em&gt; on their own.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The one I've noticed is actually on meta, not the main site:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/constructive&quot;&gt;constructive&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This one's especially egregious as if people think (especially in meta), that a question is constructive -- up vote it.  If you think it's not, down vote it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So, should we have a policy against 'meta-tags' in general, or just the subjective ones?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="62" LastEditorUserId="144" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-07-07T20:32:43.403" LastActivityDate="2012-07-07T20:32:43.403" Title="Should we have a policy on 'meta-tags' on Meta?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;tags&gt;" AnswerCount="3" />
  <row Id="127" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="126" CreationDate="2012-07-06T02:41:13.630" Score="1" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Hopefully everything that is discussed in Meta is constructive, so I don't think we need this tag at all.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="249" LastActivityDate="2012-07-06T02:41:13.630" />
  <row Id="128" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="126" CreationDate="2012-07-06T04:43:30.063" Score="1" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;From what I can see, it looks like the tag is being used to talk about what is constructive/acceptable on the site and what isn't. This strikes me as somewhat useless, as the whole point of Meta is for issues like that. I say we just edit the questions to remove the tags, and just let the tag die on its own. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="22" LastActivityDate="2012-07-06T04:43:30.063" />
  <row Id="129" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-07-07T19:38:48.393" Score="3" ViewCount="19" Body="&lt;p&gt;Some acronyms may be very popular, so there should be synonyms, for instance:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/loc&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'loc'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;loc&lt;/a&gt; = &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/library-of-congress&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'library-of-congress'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;library-of-congress&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/ddc&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'ddc'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;ddc&lt;/a&gt; = &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/dewey-decimal-classification&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'dewey-decimal-classification'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;dewey-decimal-classification&lt;/a&gt; = &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/dewey-decimal-system&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'dewey-decimal-system'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;dewey-decimal-system&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/lcc&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'lcc'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;lcc&lt;/a&gt; = &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/library-of-congress-classification&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'library-of-congress-classification'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;library-of-congress-classification&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/ils&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'ils'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;ils&lt;/a&gt; = &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/integrated-library-systems&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'integrated-library-systems'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;integrated-library-systems&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;etc.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="109" LastEditorUserId="109" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-07-13T07:28:11.263" LastActivityDate="2012-07-13T07:28:11.263" Title="tag-synonyms for popular acronyms" Tags="&lt;feature-request&gt;&lt;tag-synonyms&gt;" />
  <row Id="130" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="126" CreationDate="2012-07-07T20:28:59.573" Score="2" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;As Ashley notes, the tag was apparently used to discuss types of questions that might be seen as inappropriate (not constructive). &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I've replaced it with &lt;a href=&quot;/questions/tagged/scope&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'scope'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;scope&lt;/a&gt; on the questions where it appeared, as this term is better able to encompass the topics of discussion (which may decide certain questions are appropriate / inappropriate for reasons beyond simply constructive/not-constructive). I've also merged (and synonymized) &lt;a href=&quot;/questions/tagged/on-topic&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'on-topic'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;on-topic&lt;/a&gt; with &lt;a href=&quot;/questions/tagged/scope&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'scope'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;scope&lt;/a&gt;, for the same reason. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="144" LastActivityDate="2012-07-07T20:28:59.573" />
  <row Id="131" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-07-10T17:48:05.103" Score="2" ViewCount="37" Body="&lt;p&gt;Throughout the beta, we need members from the site whose focus is to engage the community, both in community-building issues and site management. That's why we select a few members from each community to act as temporary, provisional Moderators. You can read about the program here: &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.stackoverflow.com/2010/07/moderator-pro-tempore/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Moderators Pro Tempore&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A bit delayed since their instatement, but I am pleased to announce that these members have stepped up and generously volunteered their time to help us assure that each community's issues are properly addressed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/users/22&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/users/flair/22.png&quot; alt=&quot;Ashley Nunn&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/users/97&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/users/flair/97.png&quot; alt=&quot;KatieR&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/users/127&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/users/flair/127.png&quot; alt=&quot;jonsca&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We want to make this site a huge success, and these members are great examples of exactly the type of people we need to make this site succeed. Please welcome them for the hard work and time they contribute.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;Did I overlook anyone?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Almost certainly. There are members who are actively involved and very deserving of recognition. My failure to account for everyone this early on is in &lt;em&gt;no way&lt;/em&gt; a slight against them. Ideally, Moderators are elected by the community and that's why &lt;strong&gt;you'll have your elections after your site makes it through graduation.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Most of all, be respectful and understanding of the Moderators Pro Tem. Members of your community are volunteering their time and learning on the job. It's a learning experience for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="12" LastActivityDate="2012-07-10T17:48:05.103" Title="Moderator Pro Tem Announcement" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;moderation&gt;" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="132" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-07-12T08:30:11.500" Score="-2" ViewCount="26" Body="&lt;p&gt;I just found out that the tag &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/libraries&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'libraries'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;libraries&lt;/a&gt; is blacklisted; I suppose it's because this is the name of the site and &lt;em&gt;all&lt;/em&gt; questions seem to be relevant to libraries. However, this is not true: the site is about library and information science, which includes questions about archives and museums among other topics not related to libraries. For this reason I'd like to allow &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/libraries&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'libraries'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;libraries&lt;/a&gt; next to &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/museums&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'museums'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;museums&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/archives&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'archives'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;archives&lt;/a&gt; for questions about libraries as general institutions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="109" LastActivityDate="2012-07-12T09:00:09.670" Title="Should the tag [libraries] be allowed?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;tag-blacklist-request&gt;" AnswerCount="1" />
  <row Id="133" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="132" CreationDate="2012-07-12T09:00:09.670" Score="5" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Why not just use &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/museums&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'museums'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;museums&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/archives&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'archives'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;archives&lt;/a&gt; as necessary, since those are probably going to be the exception not the rule?  If say, less than 5% of our questions are for other institutions, then retagging the other 95% as &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/libraries&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'libraries'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;libraries&lt;/a&gt; sounds like it would be counterproductive.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As a whole, SE would like to avoid the so-called &quot;meta&quot; tags (in the sense of all encompassing, not in the sense of &quot;Meta.Libraries&quot;, e.g., something like &lt;code&gt;programming&lt;/code&gt; or &lt;code&gt;computing&lt;/code&gt; on SO, etc.), as they are largely implied by the sites that house them.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="127" LastActivityDate="2012-07-12T09:00:09.670" CommentCount="5" />
  <row Id="134" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="50" CreationDate="2012-07-13T06:30:43.340" Score="5" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I wanted to draw everyone's attention to a recent answer given in the Discuss area of Area 51 to the following &lt;a href=&quot;http://discuss.area51.stackexchange.com/questions/5821/merging-digital-preservation-libraries-information-science&quot;&gt;question&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Rather than focus the time to discuss a mechanical merger and figure out who is for or against, why not sate yourselves for now on what is already on-topic for Libraries? Feel the merge potential, rather than talk about it. You don't need the merger for approval to ask on the site. Might as well ask now rather than waiting for Digital Preservation to launch.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;p&gt;That'll be a much better judge of the appropriateness of whether the Digital Preservation community would be happy sitting in the same site. See how everyone fits with what intersection already exists, and consequently work out from there if people are happy with the current state, or if a separate site is best.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That is an answer from &lt;a href=&quot;http://discuss.area51.stackexchange.com/users/1288/grace-note&quot;&gt;Grace Note&lt;/a&gt; one of the Community Managers here on SE.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So, please, test the waters with your DP questions on Libraries.SE! Allow your efforts to define the site and its eventual FAQ.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;(any opposing viewpoints can of course weight in on our Meta here or in A51 itself)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="127" LastActivityDate="2012-07-13T06:30:43.340" CommunityOwnedDate="2012-07-13T06:30:43.340" />
  <row Id="135" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-07-18T16:27:58.823" Score="3" ViewCount="109" Body="&lt;p&gt;Okay, so we have brainstormed somewhat on things we can do to get the word out about our site &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/45/how-do-we-spread-the-word-about-our-awesome-site&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, which is super awesome - it seems like people have a lot of good ideas. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now, let's try to act on some of those! &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are a few graduated sites on the network that are tangentially related to Libraries - English, for one - that we could put a community ad on. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If anyone here has an idea for a design we could use, post them here! Upvote ones you like and think would represent us well. :D &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="22" LastActivityDate="2012-07-31T10:37:59.550" Title="Let's get the word out!" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;site-promotion&gt;" AnswerCount="3" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="136" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="135" CreationDate="2012-07-20T16:01:57.437" Score="2" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;To get an idea for a design, I'd welcome some more brainstorming. Use or avoid the traditional image of searching in a card catalog? A reading room? Something &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.flickr.com/photos/timothygreigdotcom/2320316894/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;abstract&lt;/a&gt; (For instance I like images of mindmaps, classifications etc.)? &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.flickr.com/photos/library_mistress/tags/crash/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Crashed sleves&lt;/a&gt; and a funny tagline?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.stack.imgur.com/q3i58.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;http://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Student_using_the_card_catalogue_in_the_library,_1981.jpg&quot;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.stack.imgur.com/YRhnY.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/File:Homestead_Library_reading_room.jpg&quot;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.stack.imgur.com/n7mPQ.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;http://www.flickr.com/photos/library_mistress/1248479255&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The concept of information is very difficult to depict. Maybe the image from Shannon/Weaver or something from Otlet's Traité de Documentation (looks like the semantic web, doesn't it?). A citation graph might be worth to depict. Internet Archive and arXiv.org are known digital libraries/archives we could visually refer to, to also include the digital nature. Anyway, I just collected some images that came to my mind, please extend!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.stack.imgur.com/IXPyv.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Traité de Documentation&quot;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.stack.imgur.com/O60u5.png&quot; alt=&quot;enter image description here&quot;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.stack.imgur.com/BKCks.png&quot; alt=&quot;Shannon/Weaver&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="109" LastEditorUserId="109" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-07-20T16:22:26.397" LastActivityDate="2012-07-20T16:22:26.397" CommentCount="6" />
  <row Id="137" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="135" CreationDate="2012-07-20T16:53:08.637" Score="2" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This is a community wiki to collect sites where to put a &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.stackoverflow.com/2011/05/community-promotion-ads/&quot;&gt;community ad&lt;/a&gt; on.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://stackexchange.com/sites&quot;&gt;Stack Exchange sites&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://scifi.stackexchange.com/&quot;&gt;Science Fiction &amp;amp; Fantasy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;RPG&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Photography&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;...&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Other user communities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;LibraryThing, Shelfari&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Mendeley, Zotero, EndNote, ..&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Grand Comics Database (http://comics.org)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;..&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;journals and groups of professionals&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://code4lib.org&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;http://code4lib.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://curatecamp.org/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;http://curatecamp.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;...&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="109" LastEditorUserId="90" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-07-23T16:50:47.997" LastActivityDate="2012-07-23T16:50:47.997" CommunityOwnedDate="2012-07-20T16:53:08.637" />
  <row Id="138" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-07-23T15:15:43.150" Score="3" ViewCount="35" Body="&lt;p&gt;Would folks be OK with me making a &quot;digital-preservation&quot; tag and appending it to all of the questions related to the subject? With that I might try to do more outreach to get digital preservation folks to follow/participate in those discussions. As &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/50/where-is-the-line-between-the-digital-preservation-and-libraries-stack-exchange&quot;&gt;there seems to be consensus&lt;/a&gt; that digital preservation questions are a good fit here. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="65" LastActivityDate="2012-07-23T16:19:42.887" Title="Creating a digital-preservation tag and adding it back to all the digital preservation questions" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;tags&gt;&lt;retagging&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="139" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="138" CreationDate="2012-07-23T16:19:42.887" Score="3" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Do it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I think the best outreach, however, is to ask more digital preservation questions (myself included).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="90" LastActivityDate="2012-07-23T16:19:42.887" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="140" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="111" CreationDate="2012-07-23T17:09:25.300" Score="2" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Hmmm. Well, I pretty much signed up to SE to figure out how other librarians are dealing with similar issues that I am facing--through a question and answer format.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Given that the &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/386/what-are-some-alternatives-to-fines-that-have-been-successfully-implemented&quot;&gt;highest viewed question on the site&lt;/a&gt; is definitely one of these types of questions under scrutiny, I would suggest that the problem isn't these &quot;types&quot; of questions, but the types of answers they attract. I asked it because I was simply curious, and a lot of people gave a lot of great answers. However, each answer was specific to an organization and ignored the other responses or even a general approach that could be taken. I noticed this and commented on it a while back, but have avoided giving the thread a &quot;best answer&quot; because those who answered were only able to share THEIR solution. I think someone could go onto that thread right now, summarize the responses, (e.g. &quot;Well some people have done this, and some people have done this... and here is a note to consider...&quot;) then I would likely find that to be a &quot;best answer&quot; because that is the type of answer I was expecting when I asked the question.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="90" LastActivityDate="2012-07-23T17:09:25.300" CommentCount="4" />
  <row Id="141" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-07-28T11:10:10.030" Score="2" ViewCount="29" Body="&lt;p&gt;Today the second &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cyclingforlibraries.org/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;cycling for libraries&lt;/a&gt;, a kind of unconference for librarians on bikes has started. During the trip, each participant engages in answers to a library-related question as &quot;homework&quot;. Maybe we can get some of these interesting questions also &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/ask&quot;&gt;asked and answered at libraries.SE&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="109" LastEditorUserId="109" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-07-28T12:23:42.417" LastActivityDate="2012-07-28T12:23:42.417" Title="Questions from cycling for libraries" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;site-promotion&gt;" AnswerCount="1" />
  <row Id="142" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="141" CreationDate="2012-07-28T11:26:56.577" Score="1" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I looked on the site and didn't see any particular copyright information, but I'm assuming as long as you cite your question as &quot;based on &quot; you should be okay.  Ideally, you should observe the &lt;em&gt;topics&lt;/em&gt; and flesh out their one line questions with more details or specific parameters.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Of course, be mindful that some of their questions/topics are not constructive or are too localized, etc.   &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Finally, choose maybe a handful that you are truly interested in (or per person, if multiple users decide to go with this idea), as trying to ask too many will likely decrease the quality of the individual questions. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="127" LastActivityDate="2012-07-28T11:26:56.577" />
  <row Id="143" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-07-29T10:44:16.740" Score="1" ViewCount="27" Body="&lt;p&gt;There have been several questions similar to &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/989/zotero-do-not-get-language-field-of-article-in-coins-citations&quot;&gt;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/989/zotero-do-not-get-language-field-of-article-in-coins-citations&lt;/a&gt; which are inquiries about reference manager-specific issues.  I'd like to get some input from the community as to whether these are seeking information that is pertinent for professional librarians.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Are these too oriented towards the &quot;end user&quot; to be on-topic?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Please use the answers below to vote anonymously, or add your own custom answer to be voted on&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="127" LastEditorUserId="127" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-08-05T13:50:50.650" LastActivityDate="2012-08-05T13:50:50.650" Title="Are questions about specific reference managers for end users appropriate?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;scope&gt;" AnswerCount="2" />
  <row Id="144" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="143" CreationDate="2012-07-29T10:44:40.390" Score="2" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Yes, these should be on-topic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="127" LastActivityDate="2012-07-29T10:44:40.390" CommunityOwnedDate="2012-07-29T10:44:40.390" />
  <row Id="145" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="143" CreationDate="2012-07-29T10:45:25.803" Score="0" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;No, these should not be on-topic for a site with our scope.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="127" LastActivityDate="2012-07-29T10:45:25.803" CommunityOwnedDate="2012-07-29T10:45:25.803" />
  <row Id="146" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="135" CreationDate="2012-07-31T10:23:25.250" Score="2" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Ok, here is are some images with 220x250px and text, to link to &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/&quot;&gt;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/&lt;/a&gt;. Feel free to put them on your websites!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/30ygk.png?1&quot; alt=&quot;Community driven Q&amp;amp;A for libraries and information science&quot;&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/Opsb4.png&quot; alt=&quot;Community driven Q&amp;amp;A for libraries and information science&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="109" LastEditorUserId="109" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-07-31T10:37:59.550" LastActivityDate="2012-07-31T10:37:59.550" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="147" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-08-10T23:04:16.157" Score="1" ViewCount="76" Body="&lt;p&gt;We've reached an all-too-critical stage in our development here on Stack Exchange.  Our chatroom name is boring and we should change that!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Realizing, this would be a minor change, but I think it would provide us some &quot;team spirit&quot; and hopefully make people aware of the chatroom and maybe prompt some folks to jump in and start using it.  Chat topics should be made up of some percentage of site and LIS related discourse, but can certainly include a healthy dose of just shooting the breeze and playing &quot;current events&quot; :)   &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So, if you have a clever (semi-professional, non-offensive) name you'd like to nominate, go ahead and &lt;strong&gt;leave an answer on this question&lt;/strong&gt;, and we'll use the voting to come up with a name everyone likes.  Please do not be hurt if someone downvotes your name, it just means that they disagree with it, not that it's bad!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="127" LastActivityDate="2012-08-14T18:00:45.917" CommunityOwnedDate="2012-08-10T23:04:16.157" Title="Chat room name suggestions" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;chat&gt;" AnswerCount="5" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="148" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="147" CreationDate="2012-08-10T23:04:54.580" Score="0" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;The Stacks&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="127" LastActivityDate="2012-08-10T23:04:54.580" CommunityOwnedDate="2012-08-10T23:04:54.580" />
  <row Id="149" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="147" CreationDate="2012-08-10T23:06:29.947" Score="1" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;The Circulation Counter&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="127" LastActivityDate="2012-08-10T23:06:29.947" CommunityOwnedDate="2012-08-10T23:06:29.947" />
  <row Id="150" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="147" CreationDate="2012-08-12T05:14:35.023" Score="3" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;302.231&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;(It's Dewey for social networking - Communication through digital media))&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="237" LastActivityDate="2012-08-12T05:14:35.023" CommunityOwnedDate="2012-08-12T05:14:35.023" CommentCount="4" />
  <row Id="151" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="147" CreationDate="2012-08-14T04:26:02.730" Score="1" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Authority Control&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;(am I allowed to post twice?)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="237" LastActivityDate="2012-08-14T04:26:02.730" CommunityOwnedDate="2012-08-14T04:26:02.730" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="152" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="147" CreationDate="2012-08-14T18:00:45.917" Score="4" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Library_reference_desk&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Reference Desk&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="109" LastActivityDate="2012-08-14T18:00:45.917" CommunityOwnedDate="2012-08-14T18:00:45.917" />
  <row Id="153" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-08-20T08:17:20.000" Score="1" ViewCount="20" Body="&lt;p&gt;Some may have noticed my edits to tag wikis where I added links to Wikipedia, E-LIS, GND etc.) and links between tags, prefixed with arrows (↓/↑). I &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/nichtich/se2skos&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;wrote a set of scripts&lt;/a&gt; to extract tag wikis from StackExchange and create&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;an SKOS/RDF concept scheme of &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/nichtich/se2skos/blob/master/data/libraries/tags-as-skos.ttl&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;tags at libraries.stackexchange&lt;/a&gt; (in RDF/Turtle).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;a graphical &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/nichtich/se2skos/blob/master/data/libraries/tag-graph.svg&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;visualization of links between tags&lt;/a&gt; (as SVG with hyperlinks).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is how a tag graph looks like:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://github.com/nichtich/se2skos/blob/master/samples/sample-graph.png?raw=true&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I would not, however, create tag wikis for tags will less than two questions. We should not create a top-down thesaurus of tags but let the vocabulary evolve with the questions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;P.S: I have since published the paper and given a presentation:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Jakob Voß. 2012. &lt;strong&gt;Linking Folksonomies to Knowledge Organization Systems&lt;/strong&gt;. In &lt;em&gt;Proceedings of the 6th Conference on Metadata and Semantics Research&lt;/em&gt; (MTSR '12). Springer, pages 89-97. &lt;a href=&quot;http://dx.doi.org/10.1007/978-3-642-35233-1_9&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;[DOI]&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://jakobib.github.com/mtsr2012/paper.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;[HTML]&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://jakobib.github.com/mtsr2012/paper.pdf&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;[PDF]&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://de.slideshare.net/nichtich/linking-folksonomies-to-knowledge-organization-systems&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;[Slides]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="109" LastEditorUserId="109" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-12-02T11:31:15.903" LastActivityDate="2012-12-02T11:31:15.903" Title="Extracting linked data thesaurus structure from tag wikis" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;tags&gt;&lt;controlled-vocabulary&gt;" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="154" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-08-21T21:21:30.897" Score="2" ViewCount="101" Body="&lt;p&gt;You love your site and we love your site, but there is a whole world of people out there who might not even know it exists. When they do find it, their first impression will either scare them away or keep them around. Given this, let's take a hard look at the questions and answers here and make sure newcomers see the site at its best!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Below you'll find several questions randomly selected from this site. What do you think about each of them and their answers? Are they the best they can be or can they be improved? Would they look interesting and inviting to an outsider or are they a little embarrassing?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Upvote the corresponding post here on meta when we're awesome. Downvote when our content just isn't quite up to par.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Oh, and do comment to let everyone know your thoughts and take part in this conversation. :)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="26" LastEditorUserId="26" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-08-31T20:24:09.857" LastActivityDate="2012-08-31T20:24:09.857" ClosedDate="2012-08-31T20:24:14.193" Title="Libraries and Information Science self-evaluation: let's get critical!" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;status-completed&gt;&lt;quality-evaluation&gt;" AnswerCount="6" />
  <row Id="155" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="154" CreationDate="2012-08-21T21:21:30.897" Score="4" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/928/what-tools-are-recommended-for-characterising-assessing-or-appraising-digital-c&quot;&gt;What tools are recommended for characterising, assessing or appraising digital content acquired for preservation by an archive?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What do you think about this question and its answers? Vote and comment to let everyone know.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="26" LastActivityDate="2012-08-21T21:21:30.897" CommentCount="4" />
  <row Id="156" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="154" CreationDate="2012-08-21T21:21:50.867" Score="1" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/940/how-to-catalogue-zines&quot;&gt;How to catalogue zines?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What do you think about this question and its answers? Vote and comment to let everyone know.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="26" LastActivityDate="2012-08-21T21:21:50.867" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="157" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="154" CreationDate="2012-08-21T21:22:07.697" Score="0" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/916/what-is-japans-equivalent-of-the-national-archives-and-records-administration&quot;&gt;What is Japan&amp;#39;s equivalent of the National Archives and Records Administration?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What do you think about this question and its answers? Vote and comment to let everyone know.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="26" LastActivityDate="2012-08-21T21:22:07.697" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="158" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="154" CreationDate="2012-08-21T21:22:17.697" Score="3" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/935/what-makes-a-successful-digital-scholarship-centre&quot;&gt;What makes a successful digital scholarship centre?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What do you think about this question and its answers? Vote and comment to let everyone know.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="26" LastActivityDate="2012-08-21T21:22:17.697" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="159" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="154" CreationDate="2012-08-21T21:22:27.073" Score="3" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/926/establishing-guidelines-for-topical-displays&quot;&gt;Establishing guidelines for topical displays&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What do you think about this question and its answers? Vote and comment to let everyone know.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="26" LastActivityDate="2012-08-21T21:22:27.073" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="160" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="154" CreationDate="2012-08-21T21:22:42.063" Score="-2" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/938/can-someone-suggest-a-good-open-source-document-management-system&quot;&gt;Can someone suggest a good open source document management system?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What do you think about this question and its answers? Vote and comment to let everyone know.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="26" LastActivityDate="2012-08-21T21:22:42.063" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="161" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="121" CreationDate="2012-09-14T18:37:57.677" Score="0" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.asis.org/asist2012/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;ASIS&amp;amp;T is coming up next month&lt;/a&gt; ... and they generally have a message board that people can post stuff to ... but I'm not so great at writing copy.  If someone else wants to make a sign or something, I can post it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="62" LastActivityDate="2012-09-14T18:37:57.677" />
  <row Id="162" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-09-16T12:00:54.033" Score="5" ViewCount="117" Body="&lt;p&gt;I'd like to take a moment and reach out to our userbase and find out if there is anything that you think is missing from the site.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As to not bias any responses, I want to leave this open-ended, and encourage you to answer this question with any &lt;strong&gt;constructive&lt;/strong&gt; (please) and preferably concrete wishes or suggestions as to how we can spur activity on the site.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One suggestion/wish per answer, please.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="127" LastActivityDate="2012-10-03T23:52:15.040" CommunityOwnedDate="2012-09-16T12:00:54.033" Title="What are your &quot;wishes&quot; for the site?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="10" FavoriteCount="1" />
  <row Id="163" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-09-18T16:48:30.293" Score="9" ViewCount="166" Body="&lt;p&gt;Would it be feasible to open the LIS Stack Exchange site up to the types of questions that are not allowed on other Stack Exchange sites? I'm trying to figure out how to make this site more useful to a professional librarian audience.  Right now, it seems like the questions that are most easily accepted are relevant to library users, not the experts that Stack Exchanges tend to try to encourage.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Many of the questions I have don't have the &quot;one true answer&quot;. For instance, I'd love to know things like, &quot;We're planning to migrate to a new ILS in 2014, what are you using and what do you like or dislike about it?&quot; or &quot;What companies would you recommend to provide analysis of your patron base?&quot; or &quot;What's a good way to solicit community feedback for features in our next ILS?&quot; When I do have a yes/no question I either use one of the more generic Stack Exchanges or post to my ILS vendor's listserv.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It's not just me, &lt;a href=&quot;http://gavialib.com/2012/08/qa/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot; title=&quot;Gavia Libraria&quot;&gt;the Library Loon&lt;/a&gt;,  notes that:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Does LIS have such [clear-cut] problems? Of a certainty—common cataloging and metadata problems, for example, or some reference stumpers. But this is a fairly impoverished set of problems, hardly the sum total of the difficulties professionals encounter in LIS. The problems that fall outside that circumscribed area are… messy. Complicated. Fuzzy. Not always susceptible to obvious or easily-evaluable solution. Lacking the One True Answer that StackExchange is engineered to elicit.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Shopping questions are very useful in the library world.  Even some of the questions that get through could be considered &quot;shopping questions&quot; versus objective questions.  Take &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/1067/holiday-decorations-in-a-public-library&quot;&gt;Holiday Decorations in the Library&lt;/a&gt;, it's a tricky, yet necessary, question that gets debated on Library listserves every Christmas.  However, in essence, it's a shopping question.  Why should I &quot;buy&quot; this library policy over that library policy?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="74" LastEditorUserId="74" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-09-18T17:29:01.787" LastActivityDate="2012-12-04T16:04:22.550" Title="How closely does the LIS Stack Exchange need to follow other Stack Exchanges in terms of &quot;appropriate&quot; questions?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" AnswerCount="5" CommentCount="5" />
  <row Id="164" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="163" CreationDate="2012-09-20T02:05:29.790" Score="3" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Just a quick note on Shopping questions...&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This term gets over-used on a lot of sites, to damn perfectly good questions. A shopping question is problematic when they approach a problem with a solution already in hand (a product to buy) and &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.stackoverflow.com/2010/11/qa-is-hard-lets-go-shopping/&quot;&gt;ask someone else to... Well, &quot;go shopping&quot; for them&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;What’s the point of a bunch of labor intensive questions that provide only temporary benefit to a limited (some might say Too Localized) audience?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;They're bad, they waste time, and you should do was much as possible to divert the folks asking them &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.stackoverflow.com/2010/11/qa-is-hard-lets-go-shopping/#howtoask&quot;&gt;in a better direction&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;But not every question looking for a product or service is a &quot;shopping&quot; question!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ask yourself this: can I use my knowledge and experience to provide (or verify) a solution to a real problem faced by the asker, one that might possibly include the mention of one or more things they could purchase in order to meet their needs, &lt;em&gt;without&lt;/em&gt; having to regularly visit the shops or websites of various merchants in order to verify that my answer continues to reflect market conditions?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Then it's probably not a &lt;em&gt;shopping&lt;/em&gt; question. Now, maybe there are other things wrong with it, but forcing answerers to go shopping isn't one of them. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the example you gave, I don't see &lt;em&gt;any&lt;/em&gt; sign that the author wants us to go shopping for her. Presumably, she's perfectly capable of tracking down deals on whatever crepe-paper-and-cardboard adornments her organization requires - she just wants advice on what sort of things &lt;em&gt;she&lt;/em&gt; should be shopping for!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And &lt;em&gt;that&lt;/em&gt; is a perfectly sensible thing to ask.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="144" LastActivityDate="2012-09-20T02:05:29.790" CommentCount="11" />
  <row Id="165" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="163" CreationDate="2012-09-21T08:25:33.710" Score="2" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;This is a very open question in that there's a lot of different types of questions which may require different arguments; I'm going to address three such categories of question in separate sections below.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;On reference, readers' advisory, &amp;amp;c.:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It has always been held that this site is NOT for the answering of reference questions, RA, &amp;amp;c. That is, even if the question is one asked of a librarian and only answerable by crowd-sourcing our collective expert knowledge and wisdom, if it is not itself about LIS, it's not allowed. That's not a bad point; this is an LIS site. On the other hand, some questions really do require librarians to answer (&quot;name that book&quot; springs to mind), and as a site for experts to ask each other the kind of questions that need other experts to answer, I think that we could have a discussion about these questions. Personally, I'd rather try letting the wisdom of the crowd moderate bad questions than refuse an entire category without the experiment and suffer for it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There is a second line of attack that says that these questions will flood the site with non-expert questions if we let them in. I disagree. If we do get questions from non-experts that are best served on other sites, we can direct them there (and if that site is an SE site, questions can be moved directly), but if it's from an expert, I'm betting that they're not going to ask a question of us that it would be faster to find out on their own, especially if they've got a patron waiting on it. Even if it is by an expert but could be answered by a different community, we can still redirect them. As things currently stand, we get so few questions that redirecting a few in order to claim others that are relevant isn't going to tax us much; if that changes, we can re-visit the policy at that time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There is a third line of attack that readers' advisory is subjective, which I feel is slightly insulting to the people who do it and teach it; while it's not perfectly accurate, and therefore not 100% objective, if we couldn't actually predict readers' likely preferences in reality, there wouldn't be any reason to try or anything to teach about the subject, which just isn't true. This line of attack is simply untrue.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I would rather try community moderation to select for good questions than ban entire categories up front, IFF we may be the best community to answer them.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;On shopping questions:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.stackoverflow.com/2010/11/qa-is-hard-lets-go-shopping/&quot;&gt;The original blog post against shopping questions&lt;/a&gt; was oriented around a tech recommendation that would be outdated in a year. The fact that such a small window of relevance made the question Too Localized was bolded to emphasize that it was the real sticking point with the question. For comparison, RPG.SE decided things the other way, I'm guessing in part because even an old edition of an RPG isn't necessarily superseded by later editions for all purposes and in any case the product cycle for a specific product line may be five years, ten years, twenty years, or even infinitely long (i.e., there's only one edition ever). Given that context, it's no wonder that they bucked the trend. What's the situation with library shopping questions? I don't know. It might depend on the question; the ebooks situation is evolving full-steam, but I don't know that that's true for all possible examples.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The other point about shopping questions that was made in the original blog post was they they wanted the answer to be a universal learning experience by discussing what criteria made a good X rather than which products met that criteria at any given time. However, the similar questions that I've asked here have been ones for which I knew which criteria were good ahead of time, I just had no way of researching possible answers that might meet those criteria without crowd-sourcing possibilities. In the engineering and technology world, it's quite possible that asking people what my standard should be is an objective question because mechanical operations have relatively deterministic results, but asking such a question in LIS is easily to open a can of worms you could fill entire journals with (and people frequently do). Similarly, the specs for a wide range of tech items are a quick Google search away and all I need is a filter, whereas I might know what I want for a library item but can't actually find a list of such products anywhere online, much less detailed descriptions of them. Thus, what aspect of the shopping question needs a crowd-sourced answer is very different for us than for the sites that blog post was written about.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I would support shopping questions where the questioner can identify a reasonably objective standard for what they need and the answers are unlikely to change significantly in the next several years (as determined by the wisdom of the crowd using Close —&gt; Too Localized votes).&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;On polls, best practices, and subjectivity:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As has been stated, we are not in a discipline with a lot of provably correct answers, at least outside of some technical areas (physical questions such as book preservation, many information science questions, &amp;amp;c.). We ARE in a discipline in which &quot;How we done it good&quot; (as one of my professors put it) is a valid and common type of professional journal or magazine article. In short, we are in a discipline in which polling the community for how they have tackled a problem, discussing the answers, and then collectively selecting one or more of the answers as &quot;best&quot; is how we arrive at canonical best practices. In SE terms, these steps are called &quot;asking a question,&quot; &quot;answering a question,&quot; &quot;comments,&quot; &quot;voting on answers,&quot; and &quot;accepting a best answer.&quot; They're also called &quot;subjective&quot; and &quot;non-constructive.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Libraries.SE is in a position to not just report canonical answers that everyone already knows and agrees on but to discover for the first time what the canonical answers &lt;em&gt;are&lt;/em&gt;. That is, I think, something that we should embrace. No, we can't write a bright line rule for determining in advance which questions are going to discover a consensus best answer, because we won't know if there's one to discover until the question has been asked and people have started talking about it. Yes, this might be seen as subjective and non-constructive by the standards written for sites where &quot;Does it compile?&quot; is a reasonable test for whether something is a valid answer (whether or not it's correct). However, it's how things work in this discipline and it's constructive in the best possible sense: it can discover hidden knowledge and construct a database of it. Isn't that what we're trying to do here? If SE does not want to support that form of inquiry, SE does not want to support an LIS site, and we need to know that now so that we can go elsewhere.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If a question just wants to know &quot;How do YOU do things?&quot; it's a bad question, but if it wants to know &quot;What's a good way of doing X?&quot; it can be constructive if there's some obvious goal that the answers have to be working towards (i.e., a standard by which to measure an emergent best practice).&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="345" LastActivityDate="2012-09-21T08:25:33.710" CommentCount="10" />
  <row Id="166" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="163" CreationDate="2012-09-23T00:41:34.940" Score="1" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I am going to start with answering the question that you asked in your title. We can’t change the way Stack Exchange works as an established network of question and answer websites, for a variety of reasons. We are not a forum, and thus there are various post types that aren’t going to work well here, no matter how much we want them to.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.libraries.stackexchange.com/a/164/22&quot;&gt;Shog already talked about the confusion around shopping rec questions&lt;/a&gt;, which is awesome.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I think one of the bigger problems we are looking at here is the idea of Stack Exchange not being a forum. A lot of what people seem to want to know revolves around how different libraries do things, which is fantastic and yay, but is also (generally) more suited to a forum setting than a Q and A setting. Some of the things that make it different from a forum are the idea that we want answers to be suitable to a general audience, not just the very specific needs of one poster, and we are also not really open to extended discussions and people’s opinions on things (unless they have fact to back them). There is a stronger focus on actually solving problems rather than just having open ended discussions on the topic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/2/how-do-we-want-to-handle-subjective-questions&quot;&gt;I have written about this idea before&lt;/a&gt; and maybe revisiting some of the answers there might help make this clearer. &#xA;&lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.libraries.stackexchange.com/a/5/22&quot;&gt;Robert’s answer&lt;/a&gt; talks about how &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;the anecdotal style question you mentioned — one that seeks to poll the community — is where you tend to run into the most problems. What is your favorite [X]? What does your library do about [X]? Even if the the answers are not literally one-liners, those types of questions generally do not make great questions for this type of Q&amp;amp;A.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is precisely what we are running into. Generally, these sorts of questions are awesome in a forum or a relaxed getting to know you type setting, but here, where we want to be able to accept answers and such to questions, it becomes impossible - how can I upvote one library's way of doing things over another? Just because they are different, can I say one is inherently better than the other?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;From the &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.stackoverflow.com/2011/01/real-questions-have-answers/&quot;&gt;blog post Robert mentions&lt;/a&gt; - &quot;real questions have answers, not items or ideas or opinions.&quot; If your question is more of a collection of ideas or opinions, it's not going to work well in this format. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Stack Exchange and this sort of model isn’t for everyone, and it isn’t always suited to everything people want to ask, because of the nature of how things work. It’s an unfortunate truth, but like most things in life, it is impossible for Stack Exchange to be all things to all people.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="22" LastActivityDate="2012-09-23T00:41:34.940" CommentCount="4" />
  <row Id="167" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-10-03T11:04:14.600" Score="1" ViewCount="36" Body="&lt;p&gt;If there is a question from an Area51 site that is appropriate also for here is it ethical to ask it?  (it is, of course, unanswered because it is in Area51)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If it is ethical, should I refer back to the original question (example: In genealogical research, what is the difference between &quot;primary information&quot; and &quot;secondary information?&quot;  first asked by Gene J. in Area 51 Genealogy &amp;amp; Family Historyhttp://area51.stackexchange.com/proposals/43502/genealogy-family-history?phase=definition&amp;amp;tab=votes#tab-top  - or would that be considered promoting/advertising?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="714" LastActivityDate="2012-11-02T12:48:57.390" Title="Is it ethical to ask a question from an Area51 site here?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" AnswerCount="1" />
  <row Id="168" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="167" CreationDate="2012-10-03T12:47:07.260" Score="3" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;You can ask it here - in fact, I am pretty sure some of the top voted A51 questions from the proposal for the site got asked here. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The usual rules apply - it still needs to be a good fit for the site (on topic, constructive, etc). We don't want questions pulled from A51 just for the sake of having questions.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That said, if you find something you think would fit here, and it hasn't been asked/answered somewhere else, and it would fit best here (and not some other site, even one not yet in beta), go for it! Ask away! If someone here can answer, awesome! &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As for linking back - I don't think it is necessary to do so - if the site you are pulling from reaches beta, and someone decides to ask that same question there, that is a perfectly okay thing to have happen. Some sites have a weird overlap, and there are ways to move things around if ultimately the question belongs more over there than it would here (such as it being completely off topic here). &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="22" LastActivityDate="2012-10-03T12:47:07.260" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="169" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="163" CreationDate="2012-10-03T23:16:36.283" Score="7" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;The question asks whether the LIS Stack Exchange has to follow other sites in terms of appropriate questions. I participate in another forum (Movies &amp;amp; TV - very entertaining), and almost any question on there can be answered by a librarian using his or her fine research skills. I have answered oodles of questions on movies I have never seen, because I can research. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The folly of creating a Q and A site for librarians that seeks canonical answers is that it would be a website for lazy librarians who want others to do their research for them. What librarians NEED is a site where we can get first-hand information from each other about what is going on in other libraries, what works and what doesn't - stuff you can't find in some definitive source. Maybe our questions won't yield a lot of &quot;accepted&quot; answers - because many answers are helpful to the kinds of questions we ask. (We may have to appeal to Stack Exchange for some exemption on the stats in this arena if we are ever going to graduate out of Beta.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Stack Exchange's mission is to create &quot;libraries of high-quality questions and answers.&quot; Librarians are in the unique position of already having libraries. If the information we are looking for has been written about already, we can probably find it without asking each other. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="237" LastActivityDate="2012-10-03T23:16:36.283" />
  <row Id="170" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="162" CreationDate="2012-10-03T23:52:15.040" Score="6" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;The question asks for input in spurring activity here. I am beginning to agree with @M. Alan Thomas II that this site is just not a good fit for librarians.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Librarians are unlike any other group on StackExchange. First, we don't need canonical answers because we can find those on our own. Second, we appreciate that a good library is full of information, sometimes contradictory, and as librarians we would rather see an assortment of answers and choose the best for ourselves than see a bunch of questions for which some other person identified what is the true and accepted answer. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Third, and perhaps most significant, we have all been educated at the feet of Ranganathan - every book its user, every user his book. Librarians don't care that the answer to a question is only useful to a few people, or even one person. That person has an information need; we try to meet it. If we have room for it in our collection (and web-space is pretty limitless), we should make it available. As it stands, we have a paltry 276 questions here - room is clearly not an issue. If we open up the site to a wider variety of question types, we might have a site that is useful to librarians. What if it blossomed and we had thousands of questions to sort through - how would people find the information that is helpful? We are librarians - we might have to develop a better system of tags.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And fourth, a related point, the process of closing questions and asking people to make the questions better before they are worthy of answering is insulting, and it drives people away. As librarians, we should instead be asking the questioner clarifying questions to improve the question if the question is not clear. If it is clear but perhaps not within preset guidelines, consider just letting it stand to see whether it gets answers that might be helpful to someone. Over time, the &quot;library&quot; can be weeded of questions that never got upticked answers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So those are my suggestions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="237" LastActivityDate="2012-10-03T23:52:15.040" CommunityOwnedDate="2012-10-03T23:52:15.040" CommentCount="9" />
  <row Id="171" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="172" CreationDate="2012-10-09T11:28:59.387" Score="2" ViewCount="30" Body="&lt;p&gt;When I look through the &quot;Unanswered&quot; questions on the main Libraries site, I see many comments that are actually answers.  I think that to follow the format of the Stack Exchange these should be turned into answers by the person/people who made the comment.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Also, on the Stack Exchange meta there was a discussion of people not accepting answers.  I hadn't really realized this was important in the Stack Exchange process.  Librarians are always open to more answers, but for this site to be successful and get out of Beta, I think we need more answers and more acceptance of good answers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="714" LastActivityDate="2012-10-09T16:13:58.003" Title="Comments could be answers &amp; accepting answers" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="172" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="171" CreationDate="2012-10-09T16:13:58.003" Score="2" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;As Jonsca pointed out, we can't force people to post answers instead of comments, nor can we force people to accept answers. This is something that has been brought up on Meta.StackOverflow numerous times, and the general consensus is that it does get somewhat disheartening sometimes when people don't accept answers and the like, but there is not much that can be done. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If there are comments you feel very strongly about in terms of them being better as an answer, feel free to post them as Community Wiki answers. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Other than that,  there isn't really anything we can do. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="22" LastActivityDate="2012-10-09T16:13:58.003" />
  <row Id="173" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-11-01T01:30:37.020" Score="3" ViewCount="65" Body="&lt;p&gt;In talking to &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.libraries.stackexchange.com/users/470/cpikas&quot;&gt;another user on here&lt;/a&gt; at the ASIS&amp;amp;T annual meeting this week ... we lamented that when there were really good questions on here, they tended to be really difficult to answer.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So, my theory is that as we're members of a field that includes tasks such as searching for information, we're not going to ask the questions that are easliy answerable.  Asking for possible sources to find an answer to a objective question would be better than asking the question directly ... as at least then we won't have to ask again the next time a similar question came up.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Am I wrong?  Or are there other issues that we need to consider about this community as a whole that might make using the same limitations on questions as other stack exchange sites problematic?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="62" LastActivityDate="2012-11-08T17:42:39.127" Title="Are we just too good at research?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="174" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="173" CreationDate="2012-11-04T08:38:46.020" Score="3" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Good point: to some degree libraries.SE is too academic. Yes it's called &quot;Libraries and Information &lt;em&gt;Science&lt;/em&gt;&quot; but this should not mean to limit on scientific questions. I'd like to see more how-to-questions, beginning with fundamentals such as &lt;em&gt;&quot;Where do I find a particular book?&quot;&lt;/em&gt;. Members of this community should know the basics, but can we explain to other people?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="109" LastActivityDate="2012-11-04T08:38:46.020" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="175" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="173" CreationDate="2012-11-08T17:42:39.127" Score="5" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Currently this site has a nice bundle of users (nearly 800), but the fact that it is &lt;strong&gt;only generating 0.5 questions per day&lt;/strong&gt; will not keep these users interested or engaged enough to check back in often. On the genealogy beta site, there has been similar discussion on &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.genealogy.stackexchange.com/questions/3/should-we-be-asking-specific-questions-about-helps-with-specific-ancestors-on-th/15#15&quot;&gt;whether or not to include how-to-questions&lt;/a&gt; as @Jakob suggested. The quote I particularly like is, &lt;em&gt;&quot;If we don't address those types of questions in some form then we have no chance of maintaining a viable community. You can only ask so many questions about research methods.&quot;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I've just posed a how-to type question:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/1266/how-to-build-a-dewey-number-for-a-hanukkah-christmas-interfaith-item&quot;&gt;How to build a Dewey number for a Hanukkah/Christmas interfaith&#xA;  item?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This describes a very practical problem that I have been pondering and trying to solve for a few days. Hoping that the community here sees the value in drawing in these types of  information seekers and does not close the question.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="696" LastActivityDate="2012-11-08T17:42:39.127" />
  <row Id="176" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-12-04T13:40:55.240" Score="2" ViewCount="16" Body="&lt;p&gt;I was startled to learn that requests for software recommendations are disallowed, even if they're pertinent to libraries. This seems very strange to me, but I'm new to this forum and perhaps there's a reason. Could someone explain the reasoning behind it? Saying it's a &quot;shopping question&quot; only begs the question.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is in reference to the closing of the question &quot;How to view MARC files in a human readable way?&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Update: I see that this question is part of what's discussed under &quot;How closely does the LIS Stack Exchange need to follow other Stack Exchanges in terms of 'appropriate' questions?&quot; It doesn't look as if I can withdraw a question, but perhaps discussion should remain there instead.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="857" LastEditorUserId="857" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-12-04T15:59:35.080" LastActivityDate="2012-12-04T15:59:35.080" Title="Questions on software recommendations not allowed?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="177" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="163" CreationDate="2012-12-04T16:04:22.550" Score="1" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I posted a question of my own about &quot;shopping&quot; questions, then saw that this discussion covers much of the same ground. What I'm getting out of the discussion is that only questions which have strictly factual answers are appropriate. Yet doesn't &quot;Is there free software which does X?&quot; have a strictly factual answer? The questions currently up include &quot;Is X a viable option,&quot; &quot;Effective presentation,&quot; and &quot;Are there benefits,&quot; which don't sound as if they lend themselves to purely factual answers, yet they weren't disallowed. I'm really confused at this point.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="857" LastActivityDate="2012-12-04T16:04:22.550" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="178" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="179" CreationDate="2012-12-06T20:39:35.223" Score="3" ViewCount="31" Body="&lt;p&gt;I am beginning to get involved in creating taxonomies for our organisation that go beyond the simple three-layer product hierarchies that I've been dealing with until now. Is this an appropriate forum to ask questions about such things?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="867" LastActivityDate="2012-12-06T21:19:53.830" Title="Are questions on taxonomies/hierarchies on topic?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" AnswerCount="1" />
  <row Id="179" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="178" CreationDate="2012-12-06T21:19:53.830" Score="4" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;We have had a few questions already on the topic of taxonomy and hierarchies, such as&#xA;&lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/q/334/22&quot;&gt;Reference on document types&lt;/a&gt;, for example. As long as they follow the Stack Exchange conventions on what makes a good quality question (see the &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/faq&quot;&gt;FAQ&lt;/a&gt; for more information), I don't see why they can't at least be considered for inclusion. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Feel free to ask questions as you have them!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="22" LastActivityDate="2012-12-06T21:19:53.830" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="180" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2013-02-13T12:06:25.783" Score="3" ViewCount="36" Body="&lt;p&gt;I've recently seen two questions that on LIS Stack that moderators felt were not in scope, but the &quot;rules&quot; behind these decisions are not captured anywhere in the FAQ (eg. the position on &quot;shopping questions&quot; and the position on &quot;list questions&quot;). This makes it difficult (particularly for new users) to understand the scope for this site, and work within it's rules. Having a question closed due to scoping issues that are not described anywhere can be somewhat discouraging for new users. This is not good for a site in beta, which is looking to build it's user base.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The current situation is leading to confusion and inconsistency. So for example, &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/1392/what-skill-sets-should-students-interested-in-digtial-preservation-careers-focus&quot;&gt;this question&lt;/a&gt; is a &quot;list question&quot; according to Jonsca, and was turned into a &quot;community wiki&quot;. But &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/964/what-preservation-risks-are-associated-with-the-pdf-file-format&quot;&gt;this question&lt;/a&gt; received no such treatment, but as far as I can see, is no different in requiring some degree of list in its answers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Is it possible for the moderators to specify exactly what the scope and rules are in the FAQ? At the moment the only real detail reads as follows...&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;You should only ask practical, answerable questions based on actual&#xA;  problems that you face. Chatty, open-ended questions diminish the&#xA;  usefulness of our site and push other questions off the front page.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;...which doesn't really give a lot of guidance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="158" LastActivityDate="2013-02-13T12:06:25.783" Title="The FAQ doesn't seem to capture the moderators sense of what is in scope and what isn't" Tags="&lt;support&gt;&lt;moderation&gt;" CommentCount="8" />
  <row Id="181" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2013-02-18T01:30:05.607" Score="2" ViewCount="30" Body="&lt;p&gt;I understand that some questions are not perfect the first time they are posted, but users and moderators of this site should be attempting to improve questions through the use of comments and by editing them &lt;em&gt;before they vote to close.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here are some concerns:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Questions asked/day are extremely low - only &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://area51.stackexchange.com/proposals/12432/libraries-information-science&quot;&gt;0.3 questions asked/day&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. As shown in the link, SE believes that 15 questions asked/day is a good, thriving site.  &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Two out of three of the most resent questions asked have been closed (image attached).  &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;In both instances there were no attempts made to edit the questions to make them more acceptable.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I suggest that we begin attempting to edit the questions to a format that works within the scope of the L&amp;amp;IS SE site before voting to close. Comments were left that offered recommendations on how the question might be turned into something that fit within the scope. After offering such a recommendation, the writer may wish to give the OP some time to consider them and make the requested changes, but this waiting period is not necessary. The community is welcome and encouraged to make wiki-like edits themselves to improve all questions asked.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.stack.imgur.com/7FYMH.png&quot; alt=&quot;enter image description here&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="696" LastActivityDate="2013-02-18T01:45:46.123" Title="Recommendation to attempt to edit questions before voting to close" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;editing&gt;&lt;vote-to-close&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="182" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="181" CreationDate="2013-02-18T01:45:46.123" Score="2" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Closing is not forever.  It's not meant to be &quot;Ha HA, I'm slamming the door shut on your question&quot;, it's meant to be &quot;let's prevent anyone from taking their valuable time to write a long, detailed answer to a poor, ill-formed, or unanswerable question.&quot; and &quot;let's not clutter up the site with stuff that isn't pertinent to the target audience&quot;  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Both of those were closed for different reasons, and suggestions were left on the earlier one for how it could be improved.  So, if the author isn't going to do it, please go for it, and flag it to be reopened!  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I tried for quite some time to reframe that latter question in a way that made it relevant to librarians.  As it is, it's a &quot;consumer&quot; question, which is not at all in scope.  I thought about reworking it to what should libraries do with old publications, but that would shatter the original intent of the question.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We don't like closing questions, but we don't want to have to stage a massive cleanup for poor quality content further on down the line.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I appreciate you bringing this to our attention, and please do challenge these things when you think that something isn't right.  As I've mentioned in the comments of another post, Ashley and I are in active communication with the Community team to determine the proper scope and course for the site.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="127" LastActivityDate="2013-02-18T01:45:46.123" CommentCount="4" />
  <row Id="183" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="50" CreationDate="2013-02-25T13:26:21.203" Score="1" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;So the &lt;a href=&quot;http://area51.stackexchange.com/proposals/39787/digital-preservation&quot;&gt;Digital Preservation stack has finally reached 100% commitment&lt;/a&gt; and it's been a few months since this question has been considered. So what do we do now? Having previously sat on the fence, I'm now more in favour of going with a dedicated DP site. I think this would have the dual benefits of making it easier to expand the user base to some of the other communities mentioned above in Trevor's post, while allowing moderation and scope to be tuned more appropriately for the specific needs of a DP stack.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="158" LastActivityDate="2013-02-25T13:26:21.203" />
  <row Id="184" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2013-04-08T18:52:17.103" Score="-1" ViewCount="14" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I asked this question &lt;a href=&quot;http://writers.stackexchange.com/&quot;&gt;writers.stackexchange.com&lt;/a&gt;, they closed my question and told me to try and post it here. So if it doesn't belong on this site, please close my question.I'm asking on the meta section, if you say that this question is acceptable, please migrate it to the main site.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I have to do a presentation in my university, I chose to do a presentation and a write a paper about minimalism and minimalist lifestyle.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I need some books, in french and english, my paper is written in french but i can translate quotes from english books.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;i found some english books on amazon, but couldn't find any french book. Is there any book about minimalism vs consumerism, or the minimalist lifestyle? (French or English, the more books i find, the more references i have).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1050" LastActivityDate="2013-04-08T19:14:35.027" ClosedDate="2013-05-29T14:10:28.270" Title="Books about minimalism vs consumerism (in French &amp; English)" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" AnswerCount="1" />
  <row Id="185" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="184" CreationDate="2013-04-08T19:14:35.027" Score="3" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately this question is not on topic here - we deal with the professional side of Libraries, and are not a service for finding books on a particular topic. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I would suggest trying your local library - the people at the reference desk might be able to help you, or just searching their catalogue might lead to some results. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="22" LastActivityDate="2013-04-08T19:14:35.027" />
  <row Id="186" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2013-04-17T21:54:41.783" Score="8" ViewCount="119" Body="&lt;p&gt;For the last two months, we have been seeking an additional moderator for this site. Your community has grown and you need a new person to help assist the current moderation team in nurturing and monitoring your site! Unfortunately, I have had a bit of trouble finding this additional enthusiastic soul. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So, I am turning to the community and issuing a call to arms. &lt;strong&gt;This community needs people to lead it!&lt;/strong&gt; Moderation is about accepting edits and handling flags, yes, but it's also about serving as a role model to the community. It's about helping shape the site, policy-wise and scope-wise, into something that can -- nay, will! -- be truly successful, valuable, and &lt;em&gt;makes the internet better!&lt;/em&gt; The many things a moderator does are covered at greater length in &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.stackoverflow.com/2009/05/a-theory-of-moderation/&quot;&gt;A Theory of Moderation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This position  may seem like a tall order, but I am confident that there is someone who is dedicated to this site enough that he or she wants to take on the role. Furthermore, &lt;em&gt;you would not be going at it alone&lt;/em&gt;. Moderators work as a &lt;em&gt;team&lt;/em&gt; to address issues, move the site forward, and clarify the breadth of the site itself. It is a privilege (and a joy!) to be able to look at a community and know you've had a direct hand in building it. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I'll stress this much: this is a voluntary activity. If you opt to step in and then find yourself overwhelmed by Real Life or work or some such, you're free to leave or take a leave of absence, but you'd need to let the Community Managers and your fellow moderators know. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This site needs someone willing to stand up and say, &quot;I want to make this place better!&quot; If you're that person, &lt;em&gt;please leave an answer!&lt;/em&gt; We'd love to have you. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="77" LastActivityDate="2013-04-30T17:10:26.670" Title="A Leadership Vacuum: Please Step Up" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;moderation&gt;" AnswerCount="0" CommentCount="10" />
  <row Id="188" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="189" CreationDate="2013-05-06T03:01:02.010" Score="0" ViewCount="41" Body="&lt;p&gt;We all love &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com&quot;&gt;Libraries &amp;amp; Information Science Stack Exchange&lt;/a&gt;, but there is a whole world of people out there who need answers to their questions and don't even know that this site exists. When they arrive from Google, what will their first impression be? Let's try to look at this site through the eyes of someone who's never seen it before, and see how we stack up against the rest of the 'Net.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/review/site-eval&quot;&gt;Site Self-Evaluation review queue&lt;/a&gt; is open and populated with 10 questions that were asked and answered in the last quarter. Run a few Google searches to see how easy they are to find and compare the answers we have with the information available on other sites.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Rating the questions is only a part of the puzzle, though. Do you see a pattern of questions that should have been closed but are not? Questions or answers that could use an edit? Anything that's going really well? &lt;strong&gt;Post an answer below to share your thoughts&lt;/strong&gt; and discuss these questions and the site's health with your fellow users!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="-1" LastEditorUserId="982" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2013-06-01T07:13:32.160" LastActivityDate="2013-06-01T07:13:32.160" Title="Let's get critical: May 2013 Site Self-Evaluation" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;site-evaluation&gt;" AnswerCount="1" />
  <row Id="189" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="188" CreationDate="2013-05-14T03:00:55.847" Score="0" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;h1&gt;Final Results&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/1421/migrating-a-repository-content-to-a-different-platform&quot;&gt;Migrating a repository content to a different platform&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Net Score: 0&lt;/strong&gt; (Excellent: 1, Satisfactory: 2, Needs Improvement: 1)  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/1456/how-do-you-control-for-objects-generated-invisibly-by-os-x-windows-linux-etc&quot;&gt;How do you control for objects generated invisibly by OS X, Windows, Linux, etc?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Net Score: -2&lt;/strong&gt; (Excellent: 1, Satisfactory: 0, Needs Improvement: 3)  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/1426/are-electronic-court-records-available-through-university-libraries&quot;&gt;Are electronic court records available through university libraries?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Net Score: -2&lt;/strong&gt; (Excellent: 0, Satisfactory: 2, Needs Improvement: 2)  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/1425/best-starting-point-for-a-uncatalogued-library&quot;&gt;Best Starting Point for a Uncatalogued Library&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Net Score: -1&lt;/strong&gt; (Excellent: 1, Satisfactory: 0, Needs Improvement: 2)  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/1427/what-repositories-are-exposing-information-about-research-data-sets-as-linked-da&quot;&gt;What repositories are exposing information about research data sets as Linked Data?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Net Score: -1&lt;/strong&gt; (Excellent: 1, Satisfactory: 0, Needs Improvement: 2)  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/1430/where-to-find-previous-titles-of-serials&quot;&gt;Where to find previous titles of serials?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Net Score: 1&lt;/strong&gt; (Excellent: 1, Satisfactory: 2, Needs Improvement: 0)  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/1445/tools-for-identifying-obfuscated-files-specifically-password-protected-and-encr&quot;&gt;Tools for identifying obfuscated files, specifically password protected and encrypted formats?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Net Score: 1&lt;/strong&gt; (Excellent: 1, Satisfactory: 2, Needs Improvement: 0)  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/1453/any-tools-or-processes-for-deleting-slack-space-from-donated-storage-media&quot;&gt;Any tools or processes for deleting slack space from donated storage media?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Net Score: 0&lt;/strong&gt; (Excellent: 1, Satisfactory: 1, Needs Improvement: 1)  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/1446/public-domain-issn-list&quot;&gt;Public domain ISSN list?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Net Score: -2&lt;/strong&gt; (Excellent: 0, Satisfactory: 1, Needs Improvement: 2)  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/1465/is-google-books-subscribable-to-librarians&quot;&gt;Is Google Books subscribable to librarians?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Net Score: -2&lt;/strong&gt; (Excellent: 0, Satisfactory: 1, Needs Improvement: 2)  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="-1" LastActivityDate="2013-05-14T03:00:55.847" />
  <row Id="190" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2013-05-29T10:36:22.630" Score="4" ViewCount="250" Body="&lt;p&gt;After over a year in beta, it has become evident that Libraries SE simply can not sustain itself. We'll be closing the site in ten days, at which point a dump of the content will be available on the &lt;a href=&quot;http://area51.stackexchange.com/proposals/12432/libraries-information-science&quot;&gt;site's Area 51 page&lt;/a&gt;. Please take this time to take stock of your content and flag any great questions that might have a suitable home on another site for moderator attention to be migrated. I'll go into some detail of what went, or is going wrong and then close with some advice on what another generation could do differently for this topic to work.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Think of this as an opportunity for analysis and a more focused try in the future. This was a hard topic to hit in Q&amp;amp;A format, and those that participated gave it a good try.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;What went wrong?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In short, those that actively participated in building Libraries SE did an excellent job, there simply wasn't enough active participation to sustain forward momentum. The site received barely one question a day, which in and of itself isn't a show stopping problem, but compounds quite disturbingly with the additional following concerns:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;We were unable to source leadership from within this community. While two moderators were handling the extremely light load that tasked them rather well, we found it alarming that we could not &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/186/a-leadership-vacuum-please-step-up&quot;&gt;fill a vacuum&lt;/a&gt; when another left. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The average time that it takes for a user to receive at least one answer to a question wildly fluctuates. While some questions receive answers in just a few minutes, many take days, weeks or months. A hallmark of a thriving Q&amp;amp;A site is the fulfillment of the expectation that a question will be answered quickly and satisfactorily, even when it doesn't receive very many questions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;This, your Meta site has not seen very much participation, especially recently. There's no evidence that a sufficient amount of people are still vested in the site.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This essentially echos our worst fears around &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.stackoverflow.com/2012/04/when-a-site-grows-quiet/&quot;&gt;a site going quiet&lt;/a&gt;, something that presents us with no choice but to act. There are, however, new beginnings. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;What could be done differently?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The common denominator of the concerns we have is definitely a lack of interest in, and evangelism &lt;em&gt;of&lt;/em&gt; this community. For another generation to tackle this topic in Q&amp;amp;A form, they'll need to be &lt;em&gt;excruciatingly&lt;/em&gt; committed to a bit of a long haul. Long term evangelism and promotion within the industry will be absolutely &lt;em&gt;essential&lt;/em&gt; for this topic to succeed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Additionally, the &lt;em&gt;right&lt;/em&gt; people just weren't finding your content through search engines. Long term manicuring of questions (in particular, titles) after doing comparative searches will definitely be needed in order to help ensure like minds searching for knowledge actually find you so you can engage them. Self-evaluations are designed in part to encourage this, more skilled eyes on them should help to ensure success.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt;Thank you!&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While this attempt didn't make it, there was enough &lt;em&gt;good&lt;/em&gt; here to show that the topic is definitely viable if a small but already established, cohesive community wants to take it on in the future. To all of the users that stayed and continued to work on the site, in particular the remaining appointed moderators that stayed faithfully at their posts, we'd like to extend our thanks. You folks have laid the ground work for this topic in Q&amp;amp;A format.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Please use the answers below for discussion on what &lt;em&gt;you&lt;/em&gt; feel could have gone better with Libraries SE and any ideas you have for trying again over the next few days. We look forward to seeing those that remained active on the site trying again, with the help of new and passionate people.   &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="982" LastEditorUserId="982" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2013-05-29T12:56:11.047" LastActivityDate="2013-06-02T03:15:12.983" Title="Libraries &amp; Information Science will be closing on June 7, 2013" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;featured&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="1" FavoriteCount="1" />
  <row Id="191" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="190" CreationDate="2013-05-31T02:37:43.290" Score="3" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Well, it's been fun. Personally, I think the main issue with a Q&amp;amp;A site for librarians is that we are all researchers by training, so there just isn't a burning need. A future site might attempt to recruit membership among library school students, who are still learning and need answers that are based not only on research but also on experience.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="237" LastActivityDate="2013-05-31T02:37:43.290" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="192" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="190" CreationDate="2013-06-02T03:15:12.983" Score="5" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I echo Tim's &quot;Thank you&quot;.  Thank you to everyone who asked/answered a question or flagged a question or performed an edit (etc., etc.).  Thank you for your enthusiasm for the site.  Thank you to the Comm Team for your continue support, Meta answers (especially shog9), and the whole shebang.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As things began to dwindle, I knew that this moment might be inevitable, but I hope that the site can find new life on Area 51 with an enthusiastic group of overseers (I'm nodding in your direction, Mary Jo, not to single you out, but I think you were a leader here more than you could imagine), and perhaps with a slightly different scope.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I hope that for people that were new to Stack Exchange that this is the end of the beginning, not the beginning of the end for your participation on the network.  Join Area 51 and make a new/better proposal, or find another site on SE that you can enjoy and give your passion to.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Lastly, but definitely not least, I want to thank Ashley for being a fantastic co-mod.  We faced some difficult decisions all along about scope, and we addressed them well.  It was a fun ride, and I'm sad that it's over (for now).  Would I mod with you again? YBYA, IAHB.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="127" LastActivityDate="2013-06-02T03:15:12.983" CommentCount="7" />
</posts>