<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<posts>
  <row Id="1" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2013-02-27T01:55:27.227" Score="10" ViewCount="75" Body="&lt;p&gt;I would like to say yes to this. I think this is a great place for very technical discussion and Q&amp;amp;A and thus would like this to be a place where people can ask and answer questions about software applications typically used in digital preservation work. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We should try and avoid shopping list questions, however, I think it is completely relevant to ask for advice on which particular tools do a good job addressing particular preservation risks or threats. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Further, when it comes to digital preservation software applications (JOVE, Fedora, DSpace, Archivematica, etc) or content management systems that are used as defacto digital preservation systems (ex. ContentDM, Omeka, etc) I think it is relevant to ask those questions here. Granted, there will be questions that are so detailed with these applications that the would be better fielded on application specific support-email lists. In my mind, the litmus test should be if the questions and answers would be useful things for folks working in digital preservation to potentially know about or be aware of. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="76" LastActivityDate="2013-02-28T19:36:24.570" Title="Are questions about particular software applications relevant here?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" AnswerCount="6" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="2" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1" CreationDate="2013-02-27T04:53:01.623" Score="3" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Yeah. That all sounds pretty reasonable, and it's consistent with the practice on other sites (I &lt;em&gt;know&lt;/em&gt; music.SE works like this). &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I think the central issue for &lt;em&gt;good&lt;/em&gt; shopping-list questions is &quot;Is it constructive?&quot;. It's all about the details. How to use particular software for &lt;em&gt;on-topic&lt;/em&gt; purposes, should be on-topic. What software exists for &lt;em&gt;on-topic&lt;/em&gt; purposes, should be on-topic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="62" LastActivityDate="2013-02-27T04:53:01.623" />
  <row Id="3" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2013-02-27T11:35:07.440" Score="6" ViewCount="150" Body="&lt;p&gt;There have already been a couple of questions focused on digitisation rather than digital preservation. I would assume that these are actually off topic and should be closed? The boundary is of course a little fuzzy.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I would propose that this community should be involved in decisions related to the results of a digitisation initiative. For example, the file formats and metadata schemas used, where/how the results are stored, and so on. However, questions focused on how to engage in digitisation, what types of scanners should be used or resolution to digitise at, will be off topic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://digitalpreservation.stackexchange.com/questions/1/converting-our-printed-genealogies-into-digital-form&quot;&gt;This question&lt;/a&gt; is about OCR, although is phrased in the title as a more general digitisation question. Is this in scope? Its a tough call.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As many of us in the digitisation community are well aware, confusing digital preservation for digitisation is a common mistake. I'd suggest adding some clear scoping detail on this to the &quot;What kind of questions should I not ask here?&quot; section of the FAQ. Examples may well be necessary to keep things clear.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="94" LastEditorUserId="94" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2013-02-27T12:56:01.973" LastActivityDate="2013-03-01T18:58:11.557" Title="Is digitisation on topic?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;scope&gt;" AnswerCount="7" CommentCount="2" FavoriteCount="1" />
  <row Id="4" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1" CreationDate="2013-02-27T13:53:57.767" Score="9" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I agree that questions about software apps &lt;strong&gt;are&lt;/strong&gt; relevant here. Software tools are a critical part of the digital preservation field, so must be covered.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Completely open ended and non specific &quot;shopping&quot; style questions should be pushed towards re-writes to ensure they are useful and constructive. I would not like to see a really strict interpretation of the wider Stack approach of being very anti-&quot;shopping&quot; question, which is seen on many (though not all) Stack sites.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="94" LastActivityDate="2013-02-27T13:53:57.767" />
  <row Id="5" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="8" CreationDate="2013-02-27T14:35:02.860" Score="9" ViewCount="79" Body="&lt;p&gt;It's fortunate that Jordan Merchner's &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jmechner/Prince-of-Persia-Apple-II&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;source code for Prince of Persia on the Apple II&lt;/a&gt; that he wrote back in 1985 was successfully preserved and posted to Github.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;He does mention that it would have not been possible without the aid of Jason Scott and Tony Diaz and their well maintained vintage macs. It got me thinking as to whether or not we could possibly cover the preservation of hardware, within a reasonable scope.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="68" LastActivityDate="2013-03-07T17:00:54.537" Title="Should we cover preservation of hardware too?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;scope&gt;" AnswerCount="2" />
  <row Id="6" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1" CreationDate="2013-02-27T15:46:06.807" Score="8" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I'll echo the already existing &lt;strong&gt;YES&lt;/strong&gt;, but also add &lt;em&gt;another&lt;/em&gt; aspect to the issue.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It becomes pretty hard to discuss digital preservation without mentioning the file formats of various specific products (see e.g. &lt;a href=&quot;http://digitalpreservation.stackexchange.com/q/6/97&quot;&gt;How can I recover old digital formats whose readers are no longer extant?&lt;/a&gt; which specifically mentions WordPerfect 5.1. Specific product advice then becomes somewhat hard to &lt;em&gt;avoid&lt;/em&gt; in a complete answer to a question as asked, and a fully generalized question may not do the OP much good.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="97" LastActivityDate="2013-02-27T15:46:06.807" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="7" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="3" CreationDate="2013-02-27T16:32:09.800" Score="9" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;(updated to reflect a more careful consideration of the subject)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It occurred to me that the answer should be a conditional yes, rather than an unqualified yes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If someone is just interested in digitizing audio, video, or photographs, they should probably be asking in Audio and Video Production or Photography.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If someone is asking about digitizing as part of a digital preservation project or with the intention of digitally preserving their material, then I think that it should definitely be on-topic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It seems to me that if someone wants to digitally preserve something, and they have a legitimate question about the digitization process, especially if it relates to the preservation aspect, then we shouldn't be turning them away. They're a legitimate part of the constituency of this site and we should be taking their questions seriously.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="42" LastEditorUserId="42" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2013-02-27T23:32:10.847" LastActivityDate="2013-02-27T23:32:10.847" CommentCount="10" />
  <row Id="8" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="5" CreationDate="2013-02-27T16:51:29.710" Score="11" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I think that some questions relating to hardware preservation should probably be in scope, but finding an appropriate balance will not be straightforward. Testing the water by first posting the question on meta, might be a good approach.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;High level questions might well be in scope. Asking what kind of capacitor to use in a particular circuit would be more suited to the &lt;a href=&quot;http://electronics.stackexchange.com/&quot;&gt;Electrical Engineering Stack&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="94" LastActivityDate="2013-02-27T16:51:29.710" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="9" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1" CreationDate="2013-02-27T18:53:30.680" Score="5" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;This is another yes, but from yet another angle. I think this could be a 'safe' place where people could ask questions about particular software and tools they may not feel completely comfortable asking in the application-specific email lists, which can be intimidating for even the most savvy users.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="32" LastActivityDate="2013-02-27T18:53:30.680" />
  <row Id="10" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="3" CreationDate="2013-02-27T19:17:19.490" Score="9" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I agree that the &lt;em&gt;mechanics&lt;/em&gt; of digitization are not in scope of this site, but think that the preservation of the results are well within scope, and that includes the formats that one creates in the course of digitization projects since those formats may determine the course of preservation activities.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="32" LastActivityDate="2013-02-27T19:17:19.490" />
  <row Id="11" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="13" CreationDate="2013-02-27T21:20:47.117" Score="13" ViewCount="63" Body="&lt;p&gt;Some stack exchange sites get lots of both upvotes and downvotes for question and answers. Others get much fewer votes.  Do we want to be a high-voting site?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here is one perspective from &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.tex.stackexchange.com/users/77/scott-morrison&quot;&gt;Scott Morrison&lt;/a&gt; over on &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.tex.stackexchange.com/questions/12/vote-early-and-often&quot;&gt;meta.Tex.SE&lt;/a&gt; that I would support here:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Every Stack Exchange site will eventually end up with a different&#xA;  &quot;base level&quot; of voting --- that is, the expected number of upvotes for&#xA;  a question of a given level of excellence. (This effect occurs because&#xA;  people see a good question, but already with a certain number of&#xA;  votes, and think &quot;oh, I would have upvoted this, but it already has&#xA;  enough&quot;.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;p&gt;It's easy for us to affect this &quot;base level&quot; by encouraging high&#xA;  levels of upvoting now. We're setting the standards, and this really&#xA;  will have an effect.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;p&gt;(On MathOverflow, we were very active about this early on,&#xA;  specifically encouraging all the initial round of users to vote early&#xA;  and often. You can compare statistics, and see that the average vote&#xA;  total for a MathOverflow question is much higher than on any of the&#xA;  other SE 1.0 sites.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;p&gt;In case it's not obvious: the rationale for wanting this base level to&#xA;  be high is that it provides better positive feedback to good&#xA;  contributors.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="64" LastActivityDate="2013-02-27T22:14:26.697" Title="Do we want to be a high-voting site?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;voting&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="12" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="3" CreationDate="2013-02-27T21:58:18.487" Score="1" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;If you're not &lt;em&gt;digitizing&lt;/em&gt;, how can you be doing &lt;em&gt;digital preservation&lt;/em&gt;?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Seems like it &lt;em&gt;has&lt;/em&gt; to be on-topic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="30" LastActivityDate="2013-02-27T21:58:18.487" CommentCount="6" />
  <row Id="13" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="11" CreationDate="2013-02-27T22:14:26.697" Score="13" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Oh, yes, please! There is nothing more discouraging than writing a really good question or a really good answer - and then getting one, or maybe two votes. On SO, I've had accepted answers that got ZERO upvotes - not even one from the person who asked the question and accepted the answer.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Which brings up another point - encouraging people asking questions to accept one of the answers. It doesn't have to be right away - perhaps a later answer will be better - but if the question has gotten at least one good answer then one of them should be accepted no more than a week or two later.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="42" LastActivityDate="2013-02-27T22:14:26.697" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="14" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1" CreationDate="2013-02-28T00:35:07.283" Score="2" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I vote for &lt;em&gt;yes&lt;/em&gt;, with no limitation on &quot;what software&quot;, but the question should clearly explain how the particular usage of the software is useful for digital preservation purposes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;e.g. &quot;how to use ms word to save docs in future-proof formats&quot; - OK, &quot;here is super duper library software, how do I promote it&quot; - not OK.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="70" LastActivityDate="2013-02-28T00:35:07.283" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="15" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="3" CreationDate="2013-02-28T00:37:40.997" Score="5" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I think digitization of analog objects with the goal of digitally preserving them, or keeping them easily-preservable in the future is on topic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Digitization by itself, however, may better be discussed elsewhere.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="70" LastActivityDate="2013-02-28T00:37:40.997" />
  <row Id="16" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="23" CreationDate="2013-02-28T08:45:17.250" Score="4" ViewCount="48" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://digitalpreservation.stackexchange.com/questions/87/preserving-website-content&quot;&gt;Preserving website content&lt;/a&gt; asks about the legality of maintaining private copies of web sites in order to protect against the possiblity that a new domain owner puts up a robots.txt invalidating access to old content stored in the archive (or causing it to be deleted).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Given that legality questions by definition are &lt;em&gt;localized&lt;/em&gt; (they are both &lt;em&gt;only relevant to a small geographic area&lt;/em&gt; -- one political area, such as a country or in some cases smaller areas -- and &lt;em&gt;a specific moment in time&lt;/em&gt; -- since laws change all the time), do we consideer them on topic on DP.SE?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I would argue that based on the established definitions, legality questions by definition are off topic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="97" LastActivityDate="2013-02-28T15:59:29.560" Title="Are legality questions on topic?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;scope&gt;" AnswerCount="3" />
  <row Id="17" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="16" CreationDate="2013-02-28T10:23:31.120" Score="4" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.stackoverflow.com/q/4818/183032&quot;&gt;Per meta.so&lt;/a&gt;, &quot;too localized&quot; is more about having a discrete focus too narrow to be interesting to the site's users. The operative word, then, would be the &quot;too&quot; because &quot;localized&quot; by itself is all right.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If a series of similar questions arise for laws in every world country, I can see the rationale for closing as too localized, but if the jurisdiction is limited to a reasonable area, the nature of making copies (ownership, copyright) and digital archiving are too intertwined to reject all legal questions outright, especially on the basis of the &quot;too localized&quot; flag.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="54" LastActivityDate="2013-02-28T10:23:31.120" />
  <row Id="18" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2013-02-28T10:41:51.347" Score="2" ViewCount="25" Body="&lt;p&gt;I see that &lt;a href=&quot;http://digitalpreservation.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/publishing&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'publishing'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;publishing&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://digitalpreservation.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/future-proofing&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'future-proofing'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;future-proofing&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://digitalpreservation.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/imaging&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'imaging'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;imaging&lt;/a&gt; and similar verb tags end in &quot;ing&quot; to make the action a noun. (Not counting verb tags with established noun forms like &lt;a href=&quot;http://digitalpreservation.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/data-curation&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'data-curation'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;data-curation&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://digitalpreservation.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/corruption&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'corruption'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;corruption&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://digitalpreservation.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/organization&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'organization'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;organization&lt;/a&gt;.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Should &lt;a href=&quot;http://digitalpreservation.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/digitize&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'digitize'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;digitize&lt;/a&gt;, which refers to the action, rename to &lt;a href=&quot;http://digitalpreservation.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/digitizing&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'digitizing'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;digitizing&lt;/a&gt; (or &lt;a href=&quot;http://digitalpreservation.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/digitization&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'digitization'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;digitization&lt;/a&gt;)?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Should &lt;a href=&quot;http://digitalpreservation.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/archive&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'archive'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;archive&lt;/a&gt; (the action) → &lt;a href=&quot;http://digitalpreservation.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/archiving&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'archiving'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;archiving&lt;/a&gt;?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;And so on&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="54" LastEditorUserId="54" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2013-02-28T11:03:37.967" LastActivityDate="2013-02-28T15:41:29.380" Title="Should verb tags become gerunds?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;tags&gt;&lt;retagging&gt;&lt;tag-synonyms&gt;" AnswerCount="1" />
  <row Id="19" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="16" CreationDate="2013-02-28T14:24:35.723" Score="4" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Too localized makes sense, but I would think about just straight up calling such questions off-topic, if for no other reason than it's what we did at &lt;a href=&quot;http://workplace.stackexchange.com/&quot;&gt;The Workplace SE&lt;/a&gt; and it allowed us to put a clear statement in our &lt;a href=&quot;http://workplace.stackexchange.com/faq&quot;&gt;FAQ&lt;/a&gt; that (most) people understand immediately: &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;If a question requires a lawyer to answer it, we can't help. These&#xA;  situations are simply too specific and too complex to definitively&#xA;  answer on our site.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Because SE sites are about practical, &lt;em&gt;answerable&lt;/em&gt; questions, and anything related to the law is often both too localized in terms of location and case specifics, &lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt; unanswerable unless someone is a lawyer (who probably would be careful to answer in ways that did not constitute actual legal advice), we declared questions off-topic to avoid discussions as to why things are/are not localized, can/cannot be suitably answered by a lawyer, etc.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;(Source: I was an original Workplace moderator)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="43" LastActivityDate="2013-02-28T14:24:35.723" />
  <row Id="20" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="3" CreationDate="2013-02-28T15:08:10.913" Score="8" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;As Donald and Courtney have pointed out, there's a continuum of relevance here. &quot;What's the best scanner to use&quot; and &quot;what DPI should I scan at&quot; seem obviously out of scope, &quot;should I save as TIFF or JPG&quot; less so, &quot;how should I organize and describe the files once I've scanned them&quot; clearly on-topic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My experience on archives listservs and discussion groups is that basic scanning guidelines are a perennial topic of inquiry from small LAM institutions trying to bootstrap a digitization program. Perhaps the answer is to link to some good introductory digital imaging resources from the FAQ, with a newbie-friendly explanation of why these types of questions are out of scope.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A distinction that might be useful: is the question about creating an authentic representation of an analog object (&quot;will this file format capture all the details of my book/manuscript/photograph?&quot;), or is it about ensuring the sustainability of the resulting digital object (&quot;will my institution be able to read this file format in ten years?&quot;). This might be a workable guideline for determining relevance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="17" LastEditorUserId="17" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2013-02-28T15:16:06.960" LastActivityDate="2013-02-28T15:16:06.960" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="21" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2013-02-28T15:40:28.057" Score="5" ViewCount="32" Body="&lt;p&gt;One of the things that I like about SFF.SE (Science Fiction and Fantasy) is that many of the more active members and mods regularly hang out in chat. This provides at least three benefits:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chat is a place where people can discuss related topics that would otherwise be off-topic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chat is a place to hold long-running discussions related to a specific topic, rather than a huge comment thread attached to either a question or an answer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hanging out with other members of the site can create a sense of community, encouraging polite and friendly behavior.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I plan on hanging out in chat on a regular basis, but perhaps it might be helpful to get things started by scheduling some town hall or meet and greet events.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="42" LastActivityDate="2013-02-28T15:40:28.057" Title="Should we have regular &quot;town hall&quot; chat sessions and/or encourage folks to hang out in chat?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" CommentCount="6" />
  <row Id="22" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="18" CreationDate="2013-02-28T15:41:29.380" Score="2" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Yes. I'd also suggest changing &quot;archive-format&quot; to &quot;archival-format&quot; and &quot;out-of-date-format&quot; to &quot;obsolete-format&quot;. A bit of maintenance of tags early on should help these to develop in a sensible way. Is there anyone with the authority to do this yet?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="94" LastActivityDate="2013-02-28T15:41:29.380" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="23" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="16" CreationDate="2013-02-28T15:59:29.560" Score="5" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;No, please do not close these questions on the basis of &lt;em&gt;&quot;too localized&quot;.&lt;/em&gt; You still need to &lt;strong&gt;decide if the &lt;em&gt;subject&lt;/em&gt; is on topic at all.&lt;/strong&gt; But too localized has been widely (mis)used to close just about any question that mentions a place or time. An entire country, city, state or any legal jurisdiction is &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; too localized. The timeframe for a law in force is &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; too localized. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Too localized was designed for questions that cannot possibly be answered because the situation is so&amp;hellip; sooooooo unique that :&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Who cares?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Is this even still an issue? and &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Is there even a chance it would ever benefit anyone else?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For the most part, just ignore the &quot;too localized&quot; close reason. You'll know when it is needed. But we're working on some closed-question changes that will mitigate this issue.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="101" LastActivityDate="2013-02-28T15:59:29.560" />
  <row Id="24" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1" CreationDate="2013-02-28T19:36:24.570" Score="2" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Coming from Michael's angle as well, allowing questions about preserving software-specific formats can hopefully surface some migration chains necessary to migrate formats into something legible/preservable. It would link up nicely to the &lt;a href=&quot;http://fileformats.archiveteam.org/wiki/Main_Page&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Just Solve the Problem&lt;/a&gt; project from Archive Team.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="29" LastActivityDate="2013-02-28T19:36:24.570" />
  <row Id="25" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="3" CreationDate="2013-02-28T21:31:15.487" Score="2" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Yes. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The phrasing is key however and it should be focused on the results of digitization - the formats, the metadata associated with it, the storage etc. and beyond that, errors that appear in the data stream.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I would be interested in seeing questions about the digitization process, Sean Martin's work at the BL for example comes to mind re: the difference lenses make between scans of the same document in the same position etc. Also DPI questions. These are questions that affect the value of the digital data being created and impact whether or not this data becomes an asset that we do want to preserve. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It might not start as a digital preservation question but it will become one. Best to start with preservation in mind. Some records are not kept after digitization - that makes these new digital records quasi-born digital.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The compromise would be to discuss just the results of the digitization process. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Incidentally in my mind it is clear the OCR question referenced in the OP is NOT a digital preservation question. It belongs on the libraries Stack Exchange. My rationale is simple - OCR can be done over and over again. The OCR output is data associated with the digital object we're interested in, almost a second-layer of metadata. The error is an artifact of the current OCR process that doesn't impact preservation. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A few naive OCR DP questions (not having handled OCR much in the past) might be:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Q. What standard formats are there for storing OCR data?&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Q. What long term metrics should I maintain about my OCR that will be useful to future users of the data?&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Q. How do I tie my OCR data to my digital images for long term access?  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Those may not be perfect so happy to discuss in the comments below, I'm eager to find the boundary here too. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I think the site has to be carefully moderated. It is a Q&amp;amp;A site so ensuring the same digitization question isn't repeated over and over will be important and moderators, maybe via the discussion forum should have a clear FAQ about what constitutes an acceptable digitization question before closing anything.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Hope that helps. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="120" LastEditorUserId="120" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2013-02-28T21:37:12.267" LastActivityDate="2013-02-28T21:37:12.267" />
  <row Id="26" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2013-02-28T21:53:39.013" Score="2" ViewCount="33" Body="&lt;p&gt;I see a consensus forming against scanner and resolution recommendation questions in &quot;&lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.digitalpreservation.stackexchange.com/q/3/54&quot;&gt;Is digitisation on topic?&lt;/a&gt;&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;...questions focused on how to engage in digitisation, what types of scanners should be used or resolution to digitise at, will be off topic.&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.digitalpreservation.stackexchange.com/q/3/54&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;p&gt;&quot;What's the best scanner to use&quot; and &quot;what DPI should I scan at&quot; seem obviously out of scope...&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.digitalpreservation.stackexchange.com/a/20/54&quot;&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I know that SE has a contentious relationship with recommendation and &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.digitalpreservation.stackexchange.com/a/4/54&quot;&gt;&quot;shopping&quot;&lt;/a&gt; questions, usually supported by a lack of expert interest in giving recommendations and that recommendation-giving is subjective, which doesn't lead to creating definitive answers (a flag-able offense). I would like to confirm what kinds of recommendations are off-limits.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="54" LastEditorUserId="54" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2013-03-01T02:16:43.037" LastActivityDate="2013-03-01T14:35:15.323" Title="What recommendations are on topic?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;scope&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="0" />
  <row Id="27" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2013-03-01T00:35:01.270" Score="8" ViewCount="38" Body="&lt;p&gt;I recently closed a question called &lt;a href=&quot;http://digitalpreservation.stackexchange.com/q/113/101&quot;&gt;Studies on media failure rates&lt;/a&gt;. I'd like to elaborate on exactly &lt;em&gt;why&lt;/em&gt; these types of questions are closed for being unusually broad.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Please contribute! Links to studies on tape and DVD/Bluray media are especially welcome&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Stack Exchange is not a search engine or a collection of links. We're here to provide definitive answers to questions about digital preservation, &lt;strong&gt;not questions about where to &lt;em&gt;find&lt;/em&gt; things on the Internet.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If the question stood, the &lt;em&gt;&quot;perfect answer&quot;&lt;/em&gt; would just link to another site. I appreciate the effort, but there are two problems with this:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;It's not a real question. It doesn't reflect an actual problem that someone is &lt;em&gt;searching&lt;/em&gt; for. All we've done is set up another stumbling block to folks looking for that information&amp;hellip; elsewhere. &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Catch-all questions will displace a &lt;strong&gt;lot&lt;/strong&gt; of good, specific questions that will be closed as a duplicate; &quot;This has already been answered [here]&quot; &amp;mdash; except it &lt;em&gt;hasn't.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Remember that search is the lifeblood of this site &amp;mdash; and if someone is searching for the &quot;failure rate of CD-RWs&quot;,  I sure would like them to find &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;this&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; site. But overly generic questions do not help curate the type of detailed answers where this site should excel &amp;mdash; specific, long-tailed questions with intriguing answers &amp;mdash; questions that will attract and hold the interest of the experts we are trying to appeal to. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="101" LastEditorUserId="101" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2013-03-01T00:55:06.823" LastActivityDate="2013-03-01T00:55:06.823" Title="About that &quot;link to studies&quot; question" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;closed-questions&gt;" />
  <row Id="28" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="26" CreationDate="2013-03-01T02:01:05.770" Score="3" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Recommendation&lt;/strong&gt; isn't the problem at all in this case. The reason these questions were flagged is that they sought advice on &lt;em&gt;digitization&lt;/em&gt;, not digital preservation. Amazingly, even in the archival profession, &lt;em&gt;digitization&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;digital preservation&lt;/em&gt; are often conflated.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dpconline.org/advice/preservationhandbook/introduction/definitions-and-concepts&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Digital Preservation Coalition&lt;/a&gt; so concisely puts it:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&quot;Digital Preservation Refers to the series of managed activities&#xA;  necessary to ensure continued access to digital materials for as long&#xA;  as necessary.&quot;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While digital preservation ought to be a consideration in any digitization effort, these questions did not seem to be asked for the purpose of gaining knowledge that would support towards maintaining long term access to the digital objects – they simply seemed to seek best practices for digitization.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="119" LastEditorUserId="119" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2013-03-01T02:09:41.067" LastActivityDate="2013-03-01T02:09:41.067" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="29" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="26" CreationDate="2013-03-01T14:35:15.323" Score="2" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Another area declared that so-called &quot;shopping&quot; questions are off-limits, resulting in a ban on questions about what software would do a given task. This was enforced in spite of repeated protests, and a lot of people (including me) just quit that area. I don't want to see that happen here.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="14" LastActivityDate="2013-03-01T14:35:15.323" />
  <row Id="30" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2013-03-01T16:49:50.540" Score="6" ViewCount="77" Body="&lt;p&gt;There are currently &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/digital-preservation&quot;&gt;44 digital preservation tagged questions&lt;/a&gt; on the libraries SE. Many of these were posted by folks who worked to get this site up and running. I think all of them are in scope and a better fit for this site. We have already seen some questions pop up here that have been asked and answered in that set of 44 questions and it would be great if those were showing up in our &quot;questions that may already have your answer&quot; list. So, do folks here think those questions should come over here? If so, does anybody know what process there is to bring them over. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="76" LastActivityDate="2013-03-02T15:42:11.260" Title="Moving the Digital preservation questions from Stack Libraries Here" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;scope&gt;&lt;questions&gt;" AnswerCount="3" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="31" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="30" CreationDate="2013-03-01T17:11:14.160" Score="2" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Definitely. Lets get them moved over. I think we need some admin help from LIS Stack to do this.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="94" LastActivityDate="2013-03-01T17:11:14.160" />
  <row Id="32" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="3" CreationDate="2013-03-01T18:58:11.557" Score="1" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Let's think about it in narrow terms as creation of digital content from a preservation perspective. Questions about optimal design of a prospective website in connection with formats, metadata and architecture presumably would be in scope. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Someone undertaking digitization could ask the same kinds of questions, as long as they were focused on how best to create preservable output. The same could be true of any digital creation activity--photographs, videos, data sets and so on. Anything that doesn't relate to creating content for clear-cut preservation purposes (equipment, throughput, QC) would be out of scope.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="133" LastActivityDate="2013-03-01T18:58:11.557" />
  <row Id="33" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="30" CreationDate="2013-03-01T19:31:51.247" Score="4" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;While it's technically possible to migrate questions, the migration paths are not set up until a site becomes well-established. But beyond that technical limitation, building this community from the old, pre-answered questions of &lt;em&gt;another&lt;/em&gt; site would do &lt;strong&gt;this&lt;/strong&gt; site a terrible disservice. &lt;strong&gt;That's not how you want to build this site.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Forget for a moment that other site may not &lt;em&gt;want&lt;/em&gt; their content removed like that (along with the the knowledge and reputation earned). Consider that, from day one, your brand new site will be &lt;strong&gt;filled with old, pre-answered anonymous questions,&lt;/strong&gt; as the original authors are off on another site. Your tags will be inherited from another site, regardless of how this community wants to organize content here. Comments would be largely meaningless and scattered with links to another site. Voting wont reflect the activity on &lt;em&gt;this&lt;/em&gt; community, which makes it difficult to build an avid higher-reputation community to watch over this site &amp;mdash; &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.stackoverflow.com/2010/10/vote-early-vote-often/&quot;&gt;Vote Early, Vote Often&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The idea of creating a site dedicated to Digital Preservation is to build a community was supposedly not being well-served by &lt;em&gt;another&lt;/em&gt; site. I wouldn't rush to simply migrate someone else's content content. Focus on building your &lt;em&gt;own&lt;/em&gt; community. Give yourselves some time to figure out the scope and culture of &lt;strong&gt;this&lt;/strong&gt; site. You should focus on building your &lt;em&gt;own&lt;/em&gt; content with properly curated content, built with the community and expertise that genuinely belongs here. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That was the point of creating this site in the first place.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="101" LastActivityDate="2013-03-01T19:31:51.247" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="34" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2013-03-01T20:28:01.227" Score="2" ViewCount="42" Body="&lt;p&gt;I'm thinking specifically about discussions regarding user experiences with tools. I've seen some suggestions that COPTR could serve as a forum for this kind of thing, which is great (and something we haven't seen enough of). If we want to see discussions happening both places, do we want to guide things in any way? For example, should discussions between developers and &quot;super users&quot; be encouraged within the registry environment rather than here?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="133" LastActivityDate="2013-03-02T15:52:13.850" Title="What function should this site serve in relation to the proposed Community Owned digital Preservation Tool Registry?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="35" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="30" CreationDate="2013-03-02T15:42:11.260" Score="1" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I had wondered this too. There's some really useful DP questions and answers over there, which lots of people now on this site contributed to. If we don't move them over, it's quite likely we'll see them being asked again. I wonder if people will spend the same time answering them (and therefore building rep here) if they have been done already. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Those questions would also give people a better idea of the type of question that's suitable here, especially as there's been quite a few 'off topic' questions asked already and closed. A list of too many closed or off topic questions might put other folk off. Having a more comprehensive set of answered and legitimate questions helps even things out.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="93" LastActivityDate="2013-03-02T15:42:11.260" />
  <row Id="36" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="34" CreationDate="2013-03-02T15:52:13.850" Score="5" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;In part it depends on exactly what COPTR will do - will it purely be a registry of tools, will there be associated user experiences, will there be a user forum, etc.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Strictly speaking though, discussions should probably be directed to a proper discussion forum rather than a Q&amp;amp;A stack. Extracted from the FAQ - &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;*'If your motivation for asking the question is “I would like to participate in a discussion about &lt;strong&gt;_&lt;em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;”, then you should not be asking here. However, if your motivation is “I would like others to explain &lt;strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;_&lt;/strong&gt; to me”, then you are probably OK. (Discussions are of course welcome in our real time web chat.)'*&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That suggests questions about specific tools could be answered here and a link provided to the relevant section of COPTR, for example.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="93" LastActivityDate="2013-03-02T15:52:13.850" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="37" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2013-03-02T20:47:02.000" Score="6" ViewCount="40" Body="&lt;p&gt;Swiped directly from Q5. of &quot;The 7 Essential Meta Questions of Every Beta,&quot; which states&quot; The elevator pitch is a brief sentence that describes what your site is about.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="133" LastActivityDate="2013-03-05T20:02:07.063" Title="What’s the “elevator pitch” for our site?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" AnswerCount="2" />
  <row Id="39" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="40" CreationDate="2013-03-03T17:07:34.680" Score="4" ViewCount="38" Body="&lt;p&gt;We're seeing lots of good questions on the new site but we're also seeing lots of entry level questions, particularly ones that aren't actually based on a real life problem the poster is facing. I realise that people may be doing this to build up the site contet, but they're missing the context to make them really useful and they're often fairly open ended. This limits their value.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The private beta invite says the following:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;'Remember, you get the site you build! &lt;strong&gt;Ask difficult, specific questions&lt;/strong&gt; — the kind of questions pros and experts ask each other, not the kind of questions novices ask pros, because a site full of pros and experts will attract everybody, but a site full of novices rapidly becomes boring. No easy questions, no survey questions, no polls, no intro-level/basic questions, no unanswerable hypothetical questions.'.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;How can we encourage our community to focus on more specific, high quality questions? &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="93" LastActivityDate="2013-03-03T17:48:55.543" Title="How can we encourage more specific questions?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" AnswerCount="1" />
  <row Id="40" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="39" CreationDate="2013-03-03T17:48:55.543" Score="6" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;we're also seeing lots of entry level questions, particularly ones&#xA;  that aren't actually based on a real life problem the poster is&#xA;  facing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;High quality questions can be encouraged through the following actions:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Upvote examples of good questions&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Downvote questions that are not helpful to the community&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If a question that falls under #2 just needs a bit of work, you should comment on it with suggested edits. If you have editing rights, you should simply improve the question yourself. If the question is beyond help, you should show no hesitation in voting that the question be closed (link beneath question). Questions can be closed for any of the following reasons:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;duplicate&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;off topic&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;not constructive&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;not a real question&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;too localized&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More importantly though&lt;/strong&gt;, the best way that we can ensure high quality questions, is to rely on this stack exchange heavily in the work that we do. When you have specific, expert level questions that you would typically bring to a colleague or trusted peer in the community – bring it here instead. Send beta invites to people you would usually email questions to. Furthermore – if you work through a problem &quot;offline&quot; with one of your colleagues, and you think that it is a question that is not too specific and will be useful to the community, post the original question here, and have your colleague answer the question. I've &lt;a href=&quot;http://stackoverflow.com/questions/12934528/recursive-wget-with-hotlinked-requisites&quot;&gt;done this on SO&lt;/a&gt; with problems we've worked through at Rhizome.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="119" LastActivityDate="2013-03-03T17:48:55.543" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="41" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="37" CreationDate="2013-03-04T15:07:18.843" Score="3" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I'll kick things off with a rough first attempt:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Digital Preservation Stack provides expert answers to questions about &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Digital_preservation&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;preserving digital data for the long term&lt;/a&gt;, with relevance from personal digital archiving, right through to the work of libraries, archives and other memory institutions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="94" LastActivityDate="2013-03-04T15:07:18.843" />
  <row Id="42" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="44" CreationDate="2013-03-04T19:22:01.493" Score="3" ViewCount="35" Body="&lt;p&gt;The site FAQ says 'You should only ask practical, answerable questions based on actual problems that you face.' Can we or should we include research questions in that (perhaps depending on how much contextual information the OP provides), or should they be ruled off topic? &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="93" LastActivityDate="2013-03-05T13:31:59.667" Title="Are research questions acceptable?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;questions&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="43" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="42" CreationDate="2013-03-04T21:20:32.283" Score="2" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;The proper constituency of this site does not consist entirely of professional preservationists. Therefore, the scope of allowable questions does not consist entirely of those questions relating to &quot;professional, working&quot; contexts.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I see no reason why research questions would now be welcome. I also think that amateur questions should also be welcome. I can't see any reason why we should exclude members of any group that have questions that are otherwise on topic.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="42" LastActivityDate="2013-03-04T21:20:32.283" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="44" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="42" CreationDate="2013-03-05T13:31:59.667" Score="5" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I think research questions, in the sense defined in your clarifying comment, are definitely on topic, all other factors allowing. I further agree that the FAQ should not say this area is professionals-only. If we don't allow students, where are future preservationists going to go?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="14" LastActivityDate="2013-03-05T13:31:59.667" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="45" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="37" CreationDate="2013-03-05T20:02:07.063" Score="1" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Digital Preservation SE is dedicated to answering the tough questions on preserving digital data over time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="4" LastActivityDate="2013-03-05T20:02:07.063" />
  <row Id="46" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2013-03-06T21:33:29.057" Score="1" ViewCount="12" Body="&lt;p&gt;This is a spin-off from the discussion of the question &quot;Are research questions acceptable?&quot; Currently the FAQ says: &quot;Digital Preservation - Stack Exchange is for professionals working to ensure long term access to digital objects.&quot; Do we really want it to be &lt;em&gt;only&lt;/em&gt; for professionals, or should the characterization be broadened, e.g., by saying &quot;professionals and students&quot;? Should any other groups be included?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="14" LastActivityDate="2013-03-06T21:33:29.057" Title="How should the FAQ define the target audience?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;" CommentCount="4" />
  <row Id="47" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="5" CreationDate="2013-03-07T17:00:54.537" Score="1" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Emulation of old cpus should be entirely in scope. It's probably the only reliable way to run old software, especially if we can collect HDL implementations to be used with FPGAs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="105" LastActivityDate="2013-03-07T17:00:54.537" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="48" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="49" CreationDate="2013-03-10T02:53:29.837" Score="4" ViewCount="35" Body="&lt;p&gt;While the this SE is seeing much activity, I have noted a significant amount of questions with high activity, and many good answers, yet lacking a selected &lt;strong&gt;best&lt;/strong&gt; answer.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I wonder if this is due to the complexity of many of the questions, and the asker's reluctance to accept one perspective as the &quot;final word&quot; so to speak – or if it is due to the fact that many of the digital preservation practicioners here may be new to the SE format, and do not realize that they are actually obliged as the asker to select the best answer. Otherwise this SE becomes a pile of unanswered questions – not an invaluable knowledge base.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So – the question (and the purpose of this question is partially to simply call attention to the problem) is: What constitutes a &lt;strong&gt;best&lt;/strong&gt; answer?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="119" LastActivityDate="2013-03-11T16:36:04.053" Title="What constitutes an accepted answer?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;accepted-answer&gt;&lt;best-answer&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="49" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="48" CreationDate="2013-03-11T15:24:01.790" Score="7" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Have a look at this blog post &amp;mdash; &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.stackoverflow.com/2008/09/ok-now-define-answered/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;OK, Now Define “Answered”&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. The &quot;accepted answer&quot; feature does serve the purposes you are attributing to it, although it's not uncommon for users to conflate these unrelated issues:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Accepted' is not &lt;em&gt;answered&lt;/em&gt; &amp;mdash;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;The site isn't filled with &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;unanswered&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; questions if the author does not tick one of them off. A question is considered &quot;answered&quot; when it receives an answer with at least one up-vote&amp;hellip; at least as far as the 'unanswered' tab goes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Accepted' is not &lt;em&gt;best&lt;/em&gt; &amp;mdash;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;The author doesn't determine the &quot;best answer&quot; by ticking it off. The &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;best answer&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; is determined by the community vote.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;'Accepted' is only &lt;em&gt;thanks&lt;/em&gt; &amp;mdash;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;The &quot;accepted answer&quot; is simply the answer the author found most &lt;strong&gt;helpful to &lt;em&gt;them&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. This is a simple social convention we use to close the loop between the person asking and the person answering. Accepting an answer is not meant to be a definitive and final statement indicating that the question has now been answered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Personally, &lt;strong&gt;I really dislike the &quot;accepted answer&quot; feature&lt;/strong&gt; precisely because of the misunderstandings you've raised. First, despite the community voting/vetting of the answers, &lt;strong&gt;one user&lt;/strong&gt; pushes an answer to the top &amp;mdash; pushed by the user &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;least&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; likely equipped to recognize the best answer in the first place. That's what the community vote is supposed to be for. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Second, when an answer is accepted, it gives &lt;em&gt;every&lt;/em&gt; indication that the issue has been resolved and &lt;strong&gt;no further input is needed.&lt;/strong&gt; The lifecycle of a question and its answers are supposed to go well beyond helping the original author. Answers can (and should) continually be improved. But when the author selects the &lt;em&gt;best answer&lt;/em&gt; (sic) or the &lt;em&gt;correct answer&lt;/em&gt; (sic), it tells everyone who comes after &lt;em&gt;&quot;thanks, your help is no longer needed here &amp;mdash; I've moved on.&quot;&lt;/em&gt; That's not what it is &lt;em&gt;supposed&lt;/em&gt; to do, but that's the reality of how it is perceived. &lt;em&gt;&quot;Why should I add an answer? One has already been accepted.&quot;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So, to answer your question &amp;mdash; an 'accepted answer' is nothing more than the original author checking in and picking which answer best helped &lt;em&gt;them&lt;/em&gt; personally; nothing more.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="101" LastEditorUserId="101" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2013-03-11T16:36:04.053" LastActivityDate="2013-03-11T16:36:04.053" />
  <row Id="50" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2013-03-12T00:56:20.210" Score="4" ViewCount="183" Body="&lt;p&gt;We are coming up on two weeks in private beta. I regret having to say this, but based on the current Q&amp;amp;A and activity levels it doesn't look like this site is going to make it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Why? Well, we see a couple of primary issues here:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The turnout and the activity are very low.&lt;/strong&gt; Only 24% of the folks who committed to this proposal actually joined the site. Only about a fifth of those people are actually posting questions and answers. When we look at meta, that number gets even lower. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A Stack Exchange site cannot thrive unless there's a dedicated and passionate community behind it. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;There doesn't seem to be a clear direction for the site's scope&lt;/strong&gt; and there is a fair amount of disagreement within the community here on what actually belongs on the site. Out of the 79 questions currently posted, only 57 are still open. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Normally scope issues could be something worked out during beta. However, the purpose of the private beta is to set up a site that's ready to welcome users from the general public and has worked out all but a few minor issues. The concerns here, unfortunately, are more fundamental than that.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Judging by the meta discussions and the example questions on the Area 51 proposal, it seems fairly clear that this proposal was backed by several distinct groups of people, and &quot;digital preservation&quot; means something different to all of them. To some, it means asset management within a company. To others, it's about preserving legacy software. To others still, it is about manipulating file formats. The end result is that none of these groups is served well by the site we have now.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We have sites that may welcome the different factions of Digital Preservation. For example, general questions about file formats could likely land on &lt;a href=&quot;http://superuser.com/questions/tagged/file-format&quot;&gt;Super User&lt;/a&gt;, while issues of long-term preservation of content would not be out of place on &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/tags/digital-preservation/info&quot;&gt;Libraries and Information Science&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That doesn't mean that there cannot or should not be a separate site handling these topics, but unfortunately, as it stands, &lt;em&gt;this site isn't it&lt;/em&gt;. Barring any act-of-god scenarios, the site will be closed on March 18th and the data archived for download. That should give you sufficient time to save your favorite posts and discuss ideas about how to move forward.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This doesn't have to be the end. If you still believe this subject can work, feel free to try again through Area 51. We simply have to explore the harder questions of what this site is about, and to figure out how to regain (and retain!) all the support lost from the original proposal. If the support is there, your efforts should go quickly the second time around. If not, perhaps it wasn’t meant to be. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Good luck!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="10" LastActivityDate="2013-03-14T20:26:41.487" Title="Digital Preservation SE will close on March 18" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;featured&gt;" AnswerCount="4" CommentCount="8" />
  <row Id="51" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="50" CreationDate="2013-03-13T14:40:49.510" Score="6" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;As expressed a few times in the comments above:&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&quot;&amp;hellip;given how long the Area 51 proposal was given to develop&quot;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That is likely part of the problem. Less than a third of the folks &lt;em&gt;&quot;committed&quot;&lt;/em&gt; to this site showed up for the beta. That is a new, &lt;strong&gt;all-time low!&lt;/strong&gt; in participation and support.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To build a successful site, you'll definitely need more of a running start to make it viable. This subject is all over the place. By time we start slicing off the stuff that doesn't belong here, there's even &lt;em&gt;less&lt;/em&gt; to work with.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you still believe your site will work, restart the proposal. I mean that sincerely; this is not busy work. &lt;strong&gt;It is a proven way&lt;/strong&gt; to re-capture the focus, the enthusiasm, and the support lost somewhere along the way.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="101" LastEditorUserId="101" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2013-03-13T19:53:42.567" LastActivityDate="2013-03-13T19:53:42.567" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="52" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="50" CreationDate="2013-03-13T16:53:53.790" Score="13" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I'm very disappointed with this outcome and decision. A lot of the enthusiasm we need has happened here: &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/digital-preservation&quot;&gt;Digital Preservation Questions on LIS Stack&lt;/a&gt; (the most popular topic on that stack). &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/50/where-is-the-line-between-the-digital-preservation-and-libraries-stack-exchange&quot;&gt;We had been under the impression&lt;/a&gt; that &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.digitalpreservation.stackexchange.com/questions/30/moving-the-digital-preservation-questions-from-stack-libraries-here&quot;&gt;moving this earlier work across to the DP stack&lt;/a&gt; would be a good thing. But then nothing happened.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I thought the scoping issues we're being worked through with lots of lively but positive debate. I was putting lots of effort into helping with this. It would have been useful to have had some moderator help to enable editing of the FAQ and a formalisation of the result of meta discussions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Regardless, with such a small follow through from the Area 51 commit, to seeing it through and getting involved, these other issues are academic. I guess us enthusiastic types have to just go back to &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/questions/tagged/digital-preservation&quot;&gt;LIS Stack&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="94" LastActivityDate="2013-03-13T16:53:53.790" />
  <row Id="53" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="50" CreationDate="2013-03-14T08:41:48.680" Score="5" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I don't have easy access to the numbers, but let's look at what you are saying in your post.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Only 24% of the folks who committed to this proposal actually joined the site.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is arguably a very poor turnout no matter how you slice it. In raw numbers, that's right around 90 people.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Only about a fifth of those people are actually posting questions and answers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I take it you mean about 20% of the people who committed. So 75 people are actually active on the site. That's close to 85% of the people who actually did join, which doesn't sound too bad to me. Certainly there are more than 20-ish people who have posted questions or answers here.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;When we look at meta, that number gets even lower.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Isn't that a common theme, though? Especially given that if someone has already stated what amounts to your opinion, an upvote on the question and/or answer expresses that?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Out of the 79 questions currently posted, only 57 are still open.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;75 people have posted 79 questions in two weeks, and of those, 57 are still open. That's about 0.4 still open questions per active participant per week (or about 0.5 questions asked per active participant per week). I certainly don't ask one question every two weeks on StackOverflow.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It seems to me like a two week private beta period is much too short&lt;/strong&gt; from which to draw any firm conclusions about the site's long-term viability. Right around three weeks from when I received the private beta invitation email and the announced closure date.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Judging by the meta discussions and the example questions on the Area 51 proposal, it seems fairly clear that this proposal was backed by several distinct groups of people, and &quot;digital preservation&quot; means something different to all of them. To some, it means asset management within a company. To others, it's about preserving legacy software. To others still, it is about manipulating file formats.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The only real guidance thus far is the FAQ (and those very meta discussions). The FAQ simply says that &quot;Digital Preservation - Stack Exchange is for &lt;code&gt;professionals working to ensure long term access to digital objects&lt;/code&gt;.&quot; I'd argue that the examples you list all pretty much fall into that category, given appropriate form. You can't find something efficiently without some form of asset management in place, and an unsearchable archive is effectively useless. Preserving legacy software may be an inherent part of the ability to ensure that information is useful, not just accessible as bits of data, in the future. Discussions about file formats fall well into that, too; if you're going to migrate data to another file format for long-term preservation, you don't want to have to re-do that work in five or ten years if you can avoid it, &lt;em&gt;particularly&lt;/em&gt; if the conversion is &lt;em&gt;potentially&lt;/em&gt; lossy.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Of course, one could always argue that asset management is equally applicable to libraries regardless of the type of asset in question (and thus a &quot;better&quot; fit for LIS), that questions about various file formats is a general computer question (making it a &quot;better&quot; fit for e.g. SuperUser) and so on. But that assumes that there are no DP-specific issues at hand because, frankly, how many digital preservation experts hang out on SuperUser on the off chance that someone asks about the &lt;a href=&quot;http://digitalpreservation.stackexchange.com/q/32/97&quot;&gt;century-long prospects of various image file formats&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;http://digitalpreservation.stackexchange.com/q/151/97&quot;&gt;long term storage of disk images&lt;/a&gt;? (Shameless plug; taking two examples of questions I have answered and which are still open on DP.SE.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I do believe this site deserves more than two weeks of private beta before being declared non-viable.&lt;/strong&gt; Maybe it'll turn out that it indeed isn't viable as-is, or that the scope is too broad. But it seems much too early to make such a firm statement. If the site needs more work before going public beta, I'd argue that a longer private beta period to actually hash out those issues is a better alternative than killing it outright.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="97" LastActivityDate="2013-03-14T08:41:48.680" CommentCount="5" />
  <row Id="54" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2013-03-14T08:48:27.713" Score="3" ViewCount="25" Body="&lt;p&gt;According to &lt;a href=&quot;http://meta.digitalpreservation.stackexchange.com/questions/50/digital-preservation-se-will-close-on-march-18?cb=1&quot;&gt;the announcement this beta will close on 18 March&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Is it possible to migrate the best questions to either &lt;a href=&quot;http://superuser.com/&quot;&gt;Super User&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;http://libraries.stackexchange.com/&quot;&gt;Libraries and Information Science&lt;/a&gt;, with answers, comments etc.?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;According to the announcement such questions would be on-topic on that site, so it would be better to migrate them with answers than to re-ask them.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="74" LastActivityDate="2013-03-14T08:48:27.713" Title="How to migrate questions to other SE?" Tags="&lt;discussion&gt;&lt;support&gt;" />
  <row Id="55" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="50" CreationDate="2013-03-14T20:26:41.487" Score="7" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Like many users who were &quot;regulars&quot; during the public beta, I'm disappointed in this outcome. If there's a statistical threshhold beneath which proposed sites are considered not viable, I understand, but the quality of discussion here was IMO quite high and worth reflecting on. (Disclaimer: I'm a StackExchange noob, so I don't know if similar issues have been discussed in the context of other stacks.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Even during its short lifespan, I learned a great deal from this stack, and I agree with Ben's objection to the description of differing views as &quot;factions.&quot; Given time, I think that we could have developed a clear and reasonable definition of the site's scope.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Digital preservation is an emerging field that overlaps with a number of different disciplines and skill sets. Different practitioners understand the field differently -- but it's very helpful to be able discuss and apply these understandings &lt;em&gt;in the context of practice&lt;/em&gt;. This is an opportunity to move the field forward and (perhaps) resolve some of those differences. Direct engagement with other practitioners' day-to-day problems helps reveal and clarify the underlying assumptions of our shared discipline.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As the title of a recent symposium put it, there's a &quot;&lt;a href=&quot;http://sils.unc.edu/events/2013/closing-digital-gap&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Digital Curation Gap&lt;/a&gt;&quot; between researchers at large institutions and the on-the-ground practice of working LAM professionals. I'm an archivist in a small repository with limited resources. Although I try to keep up with the professional literature, I'm not directly involved with any major academic or governmental research projects. I found participation in the stack useful both in sharpening my own understanding and in confirming the correctness of my practice by helping to solve other people's problems.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I realize that Stack Exchange isn't the best forum for thornier questions of professional identity, but I do think that (as Ross and other commenters have alluded to) this stack had the potential to provide a service beyond simply being a problem-solving resource. I'm not aware of any other spaces in which this sort of informed but practical discussion is taking place. (If there are, let me know and I'll join!)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If there's an attempt to restart the stack in the future, I'd be happy to up the level of my involvement. In the meantime, I'll monitor the digital preservation tag on the LIS stack.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="17" LastActivityDate="2013-03-14T20:26:41.487" />
</posts>